<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>

<LanguageData>
	<SettingsMMCategory>Memory Monitor</SettingsMMCategory>
	<SettingsMMBarLabel>Visualize memory usage percentage</SettingsMMBarLabel>
	<SettingsMMBarTip>The RuntimeGC tab will be filled with a bar to indicate how many percent of the memory is occupied, similar to  the Research tab. You can further specify an interval you wish to monitor.

*Note: The memory usage shown here is the .NET VM working set of RimWorld, which is the space currently used by program codes. Unity framework and bulk game assets use unmanaged memory out of .NET VM, so they are not counted here (but occupy a stable portion of memory). Both part contributes to the total memory usage shown in taskmgr.exe.
This memory usage also helps to indicate overall game performance and monitor possible dead loops or memory leaks. </SettingsMMBarTip>
	<SettingsMMTipLabel>Append memory usage to the tooltip</SettingsMMTipLabel>
	<SettingsMMTipTip>Memory usage will be added into the tooltip, hover your mouse to inspect.

*Note: The memory usage shown here is the .NET VM working set of RimWorld, which is the space currently used by program codes. Unity framework and bulk game assets use unmanaged memory out of .NET VM, so they are not counted here (but occupy a stable portion of memory). Both part contributes to the total memory usage shown in taskmgr.exe.
This memory usage also helps to indicate overall game performance and monitor possible dead loops or memory leaks. </SettingsMMTipTip>
	<SettingsMMRangeLabel>Monitoring interval (Mb)</SettingsMMRangeLabel>
	<SettingsMMRangeTip>This setting only affects the percentage bar filling the RuntimeGC tab.</SettingsMMRangeTip>

	<SettingsMMIntervalLabel>Update frequency (interval)</SettingsMMIntervalLabel>
	<SettingsMMIntervalTip>How frequent the Memory Monitor should update.
Update frequency (interval) is based on UI ticks and the actual timespan between updates may vary according to your CPU performance.

*Note: Too frequent updates can create many memory garbages.</SettingsMMIntervalTip>
	<SettingsDevOnScreenMemoryUsageLabel>Dev: Replace "RuntimeGC" with memory usage data</SettingsDevOnScreenMemoryUsageLabel>

	<SettingsAutoCleanupCategory>Auto-Cleanup</SettingsAutoCleanupCategory>
	<SettingsACModMetaDataLabel>Clear unnecessary Mod info</SettingsACModMetaDataLabel>
	<SettingsACModMetaDataTip>During startup, remove Mod info that is used only when you click "Mods" button.
If you accessed that button after startup, you can still execute this cleanup by shift-clicking "Reclaim Memory" in RuntimeGC tab.

Mod files are not affected.</SettingsACModMetaDataTip>
	<SettingsACLanguageDataLabel>Clear unused translations</SettingsACLanguageDataLabel>
	<SettingsACLanguageDataTip>During startup, remove translation data that are neither English nor your current language, eg. remove Korean, Thai,... if you are using Russian or all other language translations if you are using English.

Translation files are not affected.
*Note: If you want to switch your language, you must disable this item, restart and then change language settings, or RimWorld will fail to find the data. It is suggested that all translators disable this item if frequent switching of languages is needed.</SettingsACLanguageDataTip>
	<SettingsACDefPackageLabel>Clear cached DefPackage</SettingsACDefPackageLabel>
	<SettingsACDefPackageTip>During startup, remove load cache of DefPackage for each Mod.
**Note: If you are using mods that can customize stack limits or introduce generic materials, it is suggested you disable this item in case the mods are trying to access these data and raise errors (even though this behavior itself is not recommended).**

Mod files are not affected.</SettingsACDefPackageTip>

	<SettingsMuteCategory>Mute/Replace Functionalities</SettingsMuteCategory>
	<SettingsMuteGCLabel>Replace/enchance vanilla GC</SettingsMuteGCLabel>
	<SettingsMuteGCTip>**HIGHLY Recommended to enable**
Replace vanilla GC cleaner with RuntimeGC to avoid periodic lag (4 times a day in-game) and potential save-breaking glitches.
You don't have to enable MuteGC mod, which is the standalone version of this item.</SettingsMuteGCTip>
	<SettingsMuteBLLabel>Mute battle logs</SettingsMuteBLLabel>
	<SettingsMuteBLTip>*Not recommended unless you are too desperate to get your game back to life*
Completely disable Battle logs so that no such logs will be generated, saved or loaded.
You don't have to enable MuteCL mod, which is the standalone version of this item.</SettingsMuteBLTip>

	<SettingsGeneralCategory>General Settings</SettingsGeneralCategory>
	<SettingsArchiveGCLabel>Archive WorldPawn cleanup result</SettingsArchiveGCLabel>
	<SettingsArchiveGCTip>Save the result of each sucessful WorldPawn cleanup into your save. You can check it via History - Messages tab.
*Note: This Message tab has a limit of 200 entries and is shared with in-game notifications and letters. Old entries will be removed if exceeded limit.</SettingsArchiveGCTip>
	<SettingsArchiveGeneralLabel>Archive all RuntimeGC notifications</SettingsArchiveGeneralLabel>
	<SettingsArchiveGeneralTip>*Not recommended*
Save all the notifications from RuntimeGC mod into your save. This may kick many in-game message logs out of the archive pool.</SettingsArchiveGeneralTip>

	<SettingsReset>Reset to Default</SettingsReset>

	<UITicks>{0} UI ticks</UITicks>

	<DlgTitleRestart>Restart Required</DlgTitleRestart>
	<DlgTextRestartNotice>The change to this setting will be validated only after restarting your game.

RimWorld will resatrt after exiting Mod Settings page.</DlgTextRestartNotice>
	<DlgTextRestartRequest>One or more settings of RuntimeGC has been changed and RimWorld needs to restart in order to apply them.

Restart RimWorld now?</DlgTextRestartRequest>
	<UndoChange>Undo Change</UndoChange>
</LanguageData>