<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<LanguageData>

	<ClickToJumpToProblem>Click to jump to problem</ClickToJumpToProblem>

  <BreakRiskMinor>Minor break risk</BreakRiskMinor>
  <BreakRiskMajor>Major break risk</BreakRiskMajor>
  <BreakRiskExtreme>Extreme break risk</BreakRiskExtreme>
  <BreakRiskMinorDesc>These colonists are in a poor mood and may have a minor mental break at any time:\n\n{0}</BreakRiskMinorDesc>
  <BreakRiskMajorDesc>These colonists are in a very poor mood and may have a major mental break at any time:\n\n{0}</BreakRiskMajorDesc>
  <BreakRiskExtremeDesc>These colonists are critically stressed and may have an extreme (and possibly violent) mental break at any moment:\n\n{0}</BreakRiskExtremeDesc>
  <BreakRiskDescEnding>Check these colonists' Needs tab to see what's bothering them.\n\nTo make colonists feel better, you can do things like make them fancy meals, give them more joy hours per day and nicer joy objects, place them in beautiful environments, have them drink and smoke, and much more.</BreakRiskDescEnding>
  
  <ColonistNeedsRescue>Colonist needs rescue</ColonistNeedsRescue>
  <ColonistsNeedRescue>Colonists need rescue</ColonistsNeedRescue>
  <ColonistsNeedRescueDesc>  These colonists are incapacitated on the ground:\n\n{0}\nSend another colonist to rescue them and carry them back to bed.\n\n(To rescue, select another colonist, then right click on the victim and select Rescue.</ColonistsNeedRescueDesc>

  <NeedDefenses>Need defenses</NeedDefenses>
  <NeedDefensesDesc>You've been here some time and have probably been seen. Pirate raids will start soon.\n\nYou should prepare defenses, whether they're traps, sandbags, or turrets.</NeedDefensesDesc>

  <NeedDoctor>Need doctor</NeedDoctor>
  <NeedDoctorDesc>These colonists need medical care, but you have no healthy colonists assigned as doctors.\n\n{0}\nAssign a healthy colonist to the Doctor work type. If left untreated, wounds may never heal properly and may become permanent.</NeedDoctorDesc>

  <NeedMiner>Need miner</NeedMiner>
  <NeedMinerDesc>You have designated some rocks to be mined, but no colonist has the Mining work type.\n\nAssign a colonist the Mining work type.</NeedMinerDesc>

  <NeedWarden>Need warden</NeedWarden>
  <NeedWardenDesc>You have a prisoner, but no colonist has the Warden work type.\n\nAssign a colonist the Warden work type.</NeedWardenDesc>

  <LowFood>Low food</LowFood>
  <LowFoodDesc>You are dangerously low on food.\n\n    Full bars worth of food in storage: {0}\n    Colonists and prisoners getting food: {1}\n    Days worth of food in storage: {2}\n\nGrow, buy, find, or kill some food.</LowFoodDesc>

  <LowMedicine>Low medicine</LowMedicine>
  <LowMedicineDesc>You only have {0} medications left in storage.\n\nBuy more medicine from traders.</LowMedicineDesc>
  <NoMedicineDesc>You have no medicine left in storage.\n\nBuy more medicine from traders.</NoMedicineDesc>
  
  <NeedColonistBeds>Need colonist beds</NeedColonistBeds>
  <NeedColonistBedsDesc>You have more colonists than you have colonist beds. Someone will lack a place to sleep.\n\nEither make more beds, or change a prisoner bed to a colonist bed.\n\nIf you have no resources, sleeping spots are free and can be placed instantly.</NeedColonistBedsDesc>

  <HunterLacksWeapon>Hunter lacks ranged weapon</HunterLacksWeapon>
  <HunterLacksWeaponDesc>A colonist is assigned as a hunter but does not have a ranged weapon.\n\nThey will not hunt until they are carrying a ranged weapon.</HunterLacksWeaponDesc>

  <AlertTatteredApparel>Tattered apparel</AlertTatteredApparel>
  <AlertTatteredApparelDesc>These colonists are wearing tattered apparel, which is making them sad:\n\n{0}\nGet them some apparel that isn't so badly damaged.\n\nYou can tailor apparel at a tailoring table, or buy it from traders.</AlertTatteredApparelDesc>

	<AlertUnhappyNudity>Unhappy nudity</AlertUnhappyNudity>
	<AlertUnhappyNudityDesc>These colonists are nude and not happy about it:\n\n{0}\nGet them some clothes.\n\nYou can tailor apparel at a tailoring table, or buy it from traders.</AlertUnhappyNudityDesc>

	<Starvation>Starvation</Starvation>
  <StarvationDesc>These colonists are starving:\n\n{0}\nGet them some food.</StarvationDesc>

  <StarvationAnimals>Animal starvation</StarvationAnimals>
  <StarvationAnimalsDesc>These colony animals are starving:\n\n{0}\nGet them some food.</StarvationAnimalsDesc>

  <Exhaustion>Exhaustion</Exhaustion>
  <ExhaustionDesc>These colonists are exhausted and need rest:\n\n{0}\nGet them some rest. They'll need a bed marked for colonist use. Also, make sure they're not drafted.</ExhaustionDesc>

  <NeedFoodHopper>Need food hopper</NeedFoodHopper>
  <NeedFoodHopperDesc>You have a nutrient dispenser with no hopper next to it.\n\nTo work, paste dispensers must draw from an adjacent hopper filled with raw food.\n\nBuild a hopper adjacent to the dispenser.</NeedFoodHopperDesc>

  <NeedMealSource>Need meal source</NeedMealSource>
  <NeedMealSourceDesc>You have no way of preparing proper meals from raw food.\n\nBuild a stove, campfire, or nutrient dispenser.\n\n(It cannot be in a prison cell, otherwise colonists cannot use it.)</NeedMealSourceDesc>

  <NeedJoySource>Need joy source</NeedJoySource>
  <NeedJoySourceDesc>Your colonists need to fulfill their joy need, but you haven't built any joy sources.\n\nHelp them by building a horseshoes pin, chess table, or other joy source.</NeedJoySourceDesc>

  <NeedBatteries>Need batteries</NeedBatteries>
  <NeedBatteriesDesc>You have a solar or wind generator, but no batteries. This means you'll lose power every time the sun goes down or the wind calms.\n\nBuild a battery or two to guarantee sustained power.</NeedBatteriesDesc>

  <BrawlerHasRangedWeapon>Brawler has ranged weapon</BrawlerHasRangedWeapon>
  <BrawlerHasRangedWeaponDesc>One of your colonists has the Brawler personality trait, but is carrying a ranged weapon. This will make them very unhappy.</BrawlerHasRangedWeaponDesc>

  <ShieldUserHasRangedWeapon>Shield user has ranged weapon</ShieldUserHasRangedWeapon>
  <ShieldUserHasRangedWeaponDesc>One of your colonists has a shield belt and is carrying a ranged weapon. They will not be able to fire their weapon through the shield (except at targets who are already touching them).</ShieldUserHasRangedWeaponDesc>

  <NeedResearchProject>Need research project</NeedResearchProject>
  <NeedResearchProjectDesc>You have the equipment to do research but have not selected a project.\n\nOpen the research menu and select a project.</NeedResearchProjectDesc>
  
  <ColonistsIdle>{0} colonists idle</ColonistsIdle>
  <ColonistsIdleDesc>These colonists are wandering idly:\n\n{0}\nYou should probably find them something productive to do.</ColonistsIdleDesc>

  <ColonistNeedsTreatment>Colonist needs treatment</ColonistNeedsTreatment>
  <ColonistNeedsTreatmentDesc>These colonists need medical treatment. Without it, they may die of their wounds, or their wounds may become permanent.\n\n{0}\nTreat them by sending them to a medical bed.\n\n(First, assign a medical bed by selecting it and toggling it into a medical bed. Then, select the wounded colonists and right-click on the medical bed to make them a patient.)</ColonistNeedsTreatmentDesc>

  <AlertHypothermia>Hypothermia</AlertHypothermia>
  <AlertHypothermiaDesc>These colonists are suffering from hypothermia.\n\n{0}\nMake sure their clothing is appropriate for the season and that indoor spaces are properly heated.</AlertHypothermiaDesc>
  
  <PatientsAwaitingMedicalOperation>{0} patients await medical operation</PatientsAwaitingMedicalOperation>
  <PatientsAwaitingMedicalOperationDesc>These patients await medical operation:\n\n{0}\nMake sure you have all necessary medical tools and a free doctor available.</PatientsAwaitingMedicalOperationDesc>

  <FireInHomeArea>Fire!</FireInHomeArea>
  <FireInHomeAreaDesc>There is a fire in the home area.</FireInHomeAreaDesc>

  <PawnsWithLifeThreateningDisease>Severe illness</PawnsWithLifeThreateningDisease>
  <PawnsWithLifeThreateningDiseaseDesc>People are at risk of death because of severe illness:\n\n{0}\nMake sure that they get the best medical possible.</PawnsWithLifeThreateningDiseaseDesc>
  <PawnsWithLifeThreateningDiseaseAmputationDesc>People are at risk for death because of severe illness:\n\n{0}\nIf possible, consider amputating or replacing infected limbs in order to keep colonists alive.</PawnsWithLifeThreateningDiseaseAmputationDesc>

  <BilliardsNeedsSpace>Billiards needs space</BilliardsNeedsSpace>
  <BilliardsNeedsSpaceDesc>One of your billiards table is adjacent to an obstruction that will prevent colonists from using it.\n\nA billiards table needs clear space around it on all sides to be usable.</BilliardsNeedsSpaceDesc>

  <HunterHasShieldAndRangedWeapon>Hunter has shield and ranged weapon</HunterHasShieldAndRangedWeapon>
  <HunterHasShieldAndRangedWeaponDesc>One of your hunters is using a ranged weapon and wearing a shield belt which prevents shooting at range.\n\nThey won't be able to hunt unless the shield is removed.</HunterHasShieldAndRangedWeaponDesc>

  <NeedWarmClothes>Need warm clothes</NeedWarmClothes>
  <NeedWarmClothesDesc1>At least {0} of your colonists will lack warm clothes when the cold season comes.</NeedWarmClothesDesc1>
  <NeedWarmClothesDesc1All>All of your colonists will lack warm clothes when the cold season comes.</NeedWarmClothesDesc1All>
  <NeedWarmClothesDesc2>The outdoor temperature is going to reach {0}.\n\nYou can tailor warm clothes at the tailoring bench, or buy them from traders.</NeedWarmClothesDesc2>
  
  <ImmobileCaravan>Immobile caravan</ImmobileCaravan>
  <ImmobileCaravanDesc>One of your caravans is immobile because it carries too much.\n\nYou can make the caravan mobile again by abandoning some items in the ITEMS tab.</ImmobileCaravanDesc>
  
</LanguageData>