<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>HMC Vile's Pre-Industrial Overhaul</name>
	<author>VileHeathen</author>
	<supportedVersions><li>1.3</li><li>1.4</li></supportedVersions>
	<packageId>ViTech.MedievalOverhaul</packageId>
	<description>
Overhauls weapons, artillery, apparel, and armor, up until Industrial Tech.		
Please let me know if you find bugs or have feedback!

Discord: Vile Heathen#4792
Patreon/Blog: http://patreon.com/vileheathen

CHANGE LOG 4.7 - January 22, 2022 - Retextured cheval de frise and added "Sudes" which are components used to build cheval de frise, but more importantly Ancient Roman-style stake walls and hadgehog defenses. They are essentally modular and be broken down without losing their parts so they can be rebuild elsewhere. You'll start with several sudes with the new Legionary scenario, as well as several tents to build your marching camp. Sudes are made from logs at the woodcutting bench.

CHANGE LOG 4.6 - January 16, 2022 - Added new Legion scenario.

CHANGE LOG 4.5 - September 6, 2021
	-Updated for 3.1 - Because 3.1 renders pawns differently, apparel texures now look like butt if you're zoomed in too much. I recommend setting zoom no lower than 3% in Camera+ settings for now.
	-Added new research prerequisites so you can't breeze through musket techs.
	-Updated some recipe names to include quantity
CHANGE LOG 4.4 - July 5, 2021
	-Updated for the research overhaul. 
	-Added neolithic wicker "pack basket" apparel, and the medieval backpack is called "rucksack" and uses the tribal backpack texture.
	-Retextured the blazer and renamed it "dinner jacket", which is now available in industrial tech. Wear it over a nice shirt. 	
	-Renamed the ammo for the arbalest MkII "quarrels" to avoid confusion with the light crossbow bolts, and rebalanced said ammo with a broadhead quarrel for hunting and a bodkin-head quarrel for armor piercing, and removed poison ammo (which is still available for light crossbows)	
	-New hand mending workbench added for repairing pre-industrial apparel and melee weapons.
	-Fixed poncho texture.
	-Nerfed Tsar Cannon shots slightly to decrease chances of friendly fire. Increased loading time, decreased aiming time.
		
CHANGE LOG 4.2 - May 31, 2021	
	-Fixed bug where some blueprints weren't shoing up.		
	-Recipe changes and other fixes
		
CHANGE LOG Quickfix 4.1 - April 20, 2021		
	-Work Tunic was onSkin layer - was supposed to be middle. You might get an apparel layer error when loading a save, but other than that, shouldn't be a problem. CannonParts texture path fixed. Deleted some unnecessary files.
CHANGE LOG Update 4.0 - April 19, 2021
	-Lots of broken and unbalanced recipes fixed (straw cape is now made of straw, Scutum shield is now actually buildable etc)
	-Recipes are moved around to different workbenches now. Most black powder weapons, ammunition and crates are made at the assembly table. Melee weapons and armor are still at the smithy and tailoring benches.	
	-Cannon crates now require the new "cannon component" as an ingredient
	-Gunpowder is required instead of FSX for ammo. Realized the vanilla hsk recipe is actually for "black powder" gunpowder, so I'll be adding nitrocellulose later on for modern ammo recipes.
	-You can make gunpowder at the *MILLING STONE* now.	
	-Grapeshot ammo can be made at stonecutting tables.
	-Research requirements for many guns and cannons. Smithing, Throwing Weapons, and Technology are the important ones.
	-The new Metallurgy update is coming soon. Just waiting on some incoming core HSK changes, and that will completely overhaul steelmaking as well as adding a new casting mechanic.	
		
CHANGE LOG Update 3.2 - March 16, 2021 - Oops, fixed ammo recipes so you can make them at the smithy.
CHANGE LOG Update 3.1 - Raised pistolet price so tribes will stop spawning with them.
CHANGE LOG Update 3 - apparel update
	-Patches some pawnkinds defs so now raider factions and starting neolithic colonists will wear clothes and armor that makes sense.
	-Updated apparel tags, for better searching
	-Added New categories and apparel sets for outfit-making.
	
	Again, save games still work, though you may see some weird stuff, for instance you might have a pawn wearing a piece of clothing with higher HP than its max HP, but I don't believe this will cause any problems.	
		
CHANGE LOG  Update 2
		
	NeoLithic Era / Bronze age:
	-Armors and apparel overhaul: Wicker and wood slat armor, straw cape, hide coat, bronze helm etc. 
	-Bows reimagined: Easy-to use flat blow and more advanced longbow.
		
	Medieval Era:
	-Reimagined apparel (many new textures, some are just cleaned-up and lightened for now)
	-Third bow type is the recurve bow, which is only effective in the hands of experts. 
	-Three crowssbows include the Light Crossbow, the slow, heavy Arbalest, and the inaccurate Nu Gong repeating crossbow. -
	-Crossbows are easy to use for unskilled fighters, but shorter range than a recurve or longbow. 
	-New Light Crossbow Bolts for the light crossbow and Nu Gong. Metallic and poison only.
	-Tsar Cannon: immobile giant bombard artillery which launches stone grapeshot over a wide area.
	-New Scutum shield	
		
	Early Modern Era
	-Black Powder muskets: Brown Bess, Charleville M1777, Jezail sniper musket, Pistolet. Easy-to-use and extremely deadly, but very inaccurate and slow-loading.
	-Round shot and buck shot in .69-in
	-Turret: 38mm swivel gun, available with grapeshot and round shot. 
	-New cannon/gun sounds
	-Some muskets come equipped with bayonets which turn them into formidable melee weapons	
	
	Industrial Revolution era
	-Black Powder Rifles: Springfield M1861, Sharps Carbine, Winchester 1866 lever-action, Colt Peacemaker
	-Turret: Gatling Gun
	-Field Cannon: 3-in Ordinance Rifle (with shotgun-like canister shot, and explosive shells)
	-Siege Cannon: 200-Pounder (with explosive shells and Greek Fire incendiary shells)
	-New cannon/gun sounds
		
	-New weapons and armors have detailed descriptions on how they're best used.	
		
	PLANS FOR NEXT UPDATE
	-Foundary building for casting tools, components, and cannon barrels, Bloomery building for producing cast iron and wrought iron, Possibly a water-powered trip hammer for producing weapons and tools.	
	-New production building for producing black powder firearms
	-New black powder ingredient.	
				
	KNOWN ISSUES / BUGS
	-Currently most of this exists in the medieval tech era, which makes everything avaialable all at once.
	-I have not yet updated the pawnkinds defs which means you may see a neolith NPC wearing a medieval sallet or something weird like that.
	-Save games should work, but you may suddenly have pawns wearing weird clothes/armor.
	-There may be balance issues, or random bugs. Please report any feedback to me! Thx!
		
Vile Heathen#4792 on Discord for comments/feedback
	
		
CHANGE LOG  Update 1

	-Retextured every single armor.
	-Some textures are masked, mainly plate armors, so they can have material colors without looking dull. 
	-Bonuses/Penalties are more what you would expect
	-Better balanced – no more useless armors
	-Armor stats are more diverse - each one has something it's good at which is noted in descriptions.
	-Layer system streamlined with more options (eg. Gambeson + Hauberk + Plate), but there are still two-layer armors.
	-New Mail Coif which can be worn under most helmets and matches chainmail hauberk.
	-Armors more realistic / historically accurate
	-Defs listed in organized order so recipes are grouped together nicely in production buildings
	-New Pavise shield, which is a portable stationary defense for archers/crossbowmen to carry with them.

	-New thematic armors that can mix-and-match or work as sets: 
		-Horde (warlord) armors have a Golden Horde / Genghis Khan feel.
		-Legion armors in a Roman legionnary style
		-Tatami+Kabuto Samurai-style armor
		-Rennaisance style set which fare a bit better against firearms.
		-Feral Plate armors now have post-apocalyptic / Mad Max sorta feel

	NOTES / ROADMAP / DISCLAIMERS
	-You may get "duplicate def" errors, but it should without problems work nonetheless. If you want to remove the errors, delete (and backup) the CoreSK / Defs / ThingDefs_Apparel folder. 	

	-This is essentially in alpha, but should be fairly balanced. All armors have been tested to fit the colonists, but I haven't tested every combination. Please let me know if you find that some armor setups look awkward.		

	-All armors are craftable, so HMC-AllArmorsCraftable shoudln't be needed.

	-Mail Coif uses a CombatExtended body layer that only shows up in list view, which is pointed out in the item's description. So go to list view in the gear tab to unequip. I'm not sure how to fix that mod or if it's an easy fix.

	-Will be redoing a few non-armor apparel items and primitive items, but that is “Part Two”, which I'm working on now. Also planning to retexture some Royalty apparel in the future. Planning a small weapons retexture and also add matchlock guns in a later update to go with the Renaissance armors. 

	-Disclaimer: This is hardcore, so some recipes are slightly more complex. Many use metal components or patch leather. Feral armors use things from salvaged wrecks.

	-Still need to retexture shields. Pavise needs north/east textures added. Will be in next update.

	-Masks add considerably more PNG files (probably less than 1 MB). 

	-May need translation help once this comes out of alpha.	






</description>
<url></url>
</ModMetaData>

