<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>While You're Up (with add-on for PUAH)</name>
  <packageId>CodeOptimist.JobsOfOpportunity</packageId>
  <author>CodeOptimist</author>
  <url>https://discord.gg/pnZGQAN</url>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.1</li>
    <li>1.2</li>
    <li>1.3</li>
    <li>1.4</li>
    <li>1.5</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <modDependencies>
    <li>
      <packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
      <displayName>Harmony</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
      <downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
    </li>
  </modDependencies>
  <incompatibleWith>
    <li>hoodie.whileyoureup</li>
    <li>kevlou127.WhileHYouOreHUpHQ1V0S</li>
  </incompatibleWith>
  <loadBefore/>
  <loadAfter/>
  <description><![CDATA[<b>Opportunistic hauling. Haul-to-inventory improvements (only if <color=grey><b>Pick Up And Haul</b></color> is installed).</b>
A must-have with PUAH. Compatible with existing saves. Any load order.

The following description is for RimWorld <b>1.5</b>.


Much of this mod is improving <i>Pick Up And Haul</i> (optional; installed separately). If you already use PUAH, you want this mod too.

"But my pawns are walking farther!"
Yes. A slightly longer journey now to avoid a <i>much</i> longer journey next time.

<color=teal><i>Pick Up And Haul+</i>: Better unloading</color>
We enhance all inventory hauling by unloading only once at each storage destination, in closest order.
We cache haulable destinations to improve performance.

<color=teal>Opportunistic hauls</color>
Vanilla has support for opportunities, but with limitations: haulable near your <b>start</b> position, and storage near your job.
We prefer these, but drop them as requirements to include hauls along the path.

We skip opportunities when bleeding or forming a caravan.

<i>Pick Up And Haul+</i>
Modified to grab only surrounding things whose unload path is also opportunistic.

<color=teal>Haul extra supplies & ingredients closer</color>
If hauling resources to storage would bring them closer to their job, do that first (grabbing extra).

<i>Pick Up And Haul+</i>
Modified to grab extra things headed to the same storage (when higher priority) unless bleeding.
Grab extra supplies & ingredients headed to the same storage (when equal priority).

<color=teal>Storage building filters for mod compatibility</color>
Permit or deny for any storage building through settings, or leave automatically managed with mod updates.

]]></description>
  <incompatibleWithByVersion>
    <v1.3>
      <li>Mlie.PickUpAndHaul</li>
    </v1.3>
  </incompatibleWithByVersion>
</ModMetaData>
