<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Defs>

    <HelpDef>
        <defName>TRST</defName>

        <category>SKHelp</category>

        <label>Trouble starting</label>

        <description>
Q. When i load savegame, i have a black screen or multicolored flashing menu.
A1. Try before load game change language. There is a bug in A11 version.
A2. You casually turn on or off any mod. Check the mods with which you start the game with this savegame.
A3. Possibly damaged files, it happens when computer  shut down not properly. Don't be afraid to reinstall rimworld and modpack. For saves, no matter where game located, no matter removed the game or reinstall. Saves need that version of the rimworld and that mods that you first start playing!

Q. Can I install modpack over old version?
A. NEVER reinstall mod pack over previous version! You hear me?! NEVER. You must  DELETE all from Mods folder except Core folder,  then pack off new version of HK SK with rewrite of Core folder, after - repack ModsConfig.xml.

And after you run RimWorld - you MUST check your mods queue, add CrashLanding, if you need it, then CREATE NEW WORLD, and then CREATE NEW SETTLE! Every new version requires this steps. You must understand, that with new version of modpack you must start new colony, no old saves and worlds.

Q.  If i run savegame from old version modpack, will this break my save?
A. When i made new version, this means that automatically old version savegames not compatible. If i made a,b,c subversion - this means - savegame compatible to "A" version. But sometimes there are exceptions, because A11 compared with A10 less stable to changes.</description>

    </HelpDef>

    <HelpDef>
        <defName>BLDN</defName>

        <category>SKHelp</category>

        <label>Buildings</label>

        <description>
Q. How to choose different material for buildings?
A. Right click on icon with building in menu and choose suitable.

Q.  Can't choose materials for buildings.
A.  So you have no needed materials for this building- you need right amount of them in your storage. 

Q.  I have walls from logs, but no from planks.
A. Choose another icon in build menu and right click on it for materials selecting, cause wall from logs have own icon.

Q.  My building vanishing after construction.
A. Just try reinstall game and modpack (with full clearing AppData and game folder!)

Q.  How can I use air conditioning system?  I have Industrial Cooler  in room, but it shows me only blue(cold) direction.. I can't figure out what Duct Opening I need to use and how.
A.  In coolers blue cell is target. Duct Openings allow you to withdraw hot air from cooler system, so you  need to build them close to your cooler from another side to blue cells in suitable directions. So after that you just need to select proper temperature in cooler.
Vents with two red cells allow you to equalize temperature between rooms.

Q.  How can I use Communication Relay? 
A. In fact, the Communication Relay summons random events , such as arrival trader or attack . It stores energy to 10k and then sends a signal, though the signal cannot reach the destination, reflected by the atmosphere or by calling the "white noise".

Q.  Did you mess up with Plasma Reactors? It provides 1200W is despite the fact that a bunch of resources needs to be charged + long study. And the issue turns even less than one solar generator!
A. The beauty of the plasma generator in an infinite clock work and the development of useful and useless temperature (but in large quantities).

Q.  Nutrient paste dispenser eating resources, but does not produce a paste.
A. The dispenser gives out food only when colonist comes to get it , and it appears in the hands of the colonist.

Q.  Where can I find hoppers for soylent machines and dispensers? I can’t put food direct in them, and there is no hoppers for food at all, just generator hopper only.
A. You can find it in Architect menu "Misc" named Hopper/Refrigerated Hopper (Hot key H).

Q.  Where can I find Comms Console? I have only Orbital Trade Beacon.
A. You need special research for it now. Called Advanced Communications in version 1.10 or higher.</description>
    </HelpDef>


    <HelpDef>
        <defName>CRFT</defName>

        <category>SKHelp</category>

        <label>Crafting</label>

        <description>
Q.  Where can I produce plasteel bars?
A. You need to build Electric Smelter.

Q.  Where can I find mulch?
A. You need to build Composter, there you also can produce some seeds for crops if  there is some amount of fresh food (like seeds of coffee or potato)

Q.  Can't figure out where I can make some cloth from cotton?
A. There is Tailor's Loom in "Production", it's bigger than normal work bench - 2x3 cells.

Q.  Where can I make sulphates?
A. In Petrochemical Plant when refining crude oil.

Q.  What do I need to make some synthetic materials?
A.  Firs you need to build Drilling Rig, then Mine Extractor, choose there Crude Oil. Then you will need Petrochemical Plant. Search on Assembling Workbench what exact resources you need to produce in Plant for synthetic materials.

Q.  Where can I find synthread cloth?
A. On Tailor's Loom, you will need some cotton and syntetic fibres (v1.11).

Q. And what about synthetic materials?
A. On Assembling Workbench, where you also can produce some components, etc.

Q.  How can I recycle Aloe?
A. On Canningstove you can make some Herb Med Kit from it.

Q. And what about raw xergium?  
A.  On Medical Table -Herb medicine.

Q.  Where can I craft Vancidium?
A. In it's own building - Vancidium Refinery,  you need to research Construction lvl 4.

Q.  Where can I find weapon components?
A. You can earn them by smelting needless weapon on Weapon Crafting Workbench or by them from trader.
</description>

    </HelpDef>


    <HelpDef>
        <defName>MISC</defName>

        <category>SKHelp</category>

        <label>Misc</label>

        <description>
Q.  I have lots of corpses/cloth/weapons littering ground, what can I do?
A. 1. You can use Slate crematorium to burn down corpses and cloth, needed to research
2. Burn down all this stuff with Firegun/Molotov cocktails.
3. Human corpses can be refined in biomatter in Bio Refinery or in Organ Vat. Armor and weapons can be mend on Mending Table and sold to traders.

Q.  Colonists somehow began to take time off from work, most of the day meditating and praying diverted mainly for food and sleep. If forced to point out the matter, they do it and go back to meditating. Some may get stuck at work to exhaustion and did not produce anything.
A. 1. In the Overview, there is a function of the schedule in Restrictions tab, where you can set the time for sleep? work and time for lunch/rest.
2. Check equipping new guns on the colonists (such as RPG, minigun etc.), if there is any of them-unequipp.
3. Try several times to restart the last save.
4. Check the absence of the prisoners legs \ feet \ thighs and put the prosthesis. If everything is OK, try to disable interaction with them. If this does not help - free / kill them.

Q.  There is no seed drops from pants!
A. You must wait until they are fully grown and then harvest them.

Q.  How can I treat colonists Torso (scars, cuts, bites, etc.)?
A. The scars, cuts, bites can be treated with biomatter, if the spine is damaged it can be replaced.
You need to produce some biomatter in Organ Vat or by it from traders, then click colonist menu "Health"- "operation" and there should be able operations with the biomaterial .

Q.  Where can I find AI persona core?
A. You can buy it from a trader or drop at the destruction of shipwrecks (mechanoids event).

Q.  Why do I need AI persona core?
A. To create droids.

Q.  The guns fired through the embrasure?
A. Yes, if you have enough of the affected area of weapons.

Q.  How to understand what clothes need? Especially in hot bioms.
A. By the terms of the heat in armor description you need "+", then it will be better insulation, and cold "-". I.e. +6 on armor stat to +26 basic colonist stat, so our colonist now can handle +32 temperature without any dangerous effect. With cold - same.

Q.  How to force the colonists to carry weapons and armor of one quality on one storage, and other quality - on another?
A. Under the button "Remove all" and "Allow all" setting in the warehouse has 2 sliders. One adjusts the integrity and quality of the second.

Q.  What about the quality of weapons? How it works?
A. The quality of weapons does not affect the range and damage, but significantly affect the accuracy. For the colonists with a low shooting parameter is rather important aspect.

Q.  Maybe someone already gained experience, which weapon in what situations is better to use?
A. It depends on the type of defense:
1. If it is close range - than plasmagun or flamethrower.
2. if you can stop the opponent in the pile away from the RPG itself (knocks on the area).
3. if you have a defense deep (60 meters to zero) the sense sniper rifles and close turrets. 
4. If you love the farm (you have many settlers) then I would advise tactical rifle (you need to minimize the time to recharge).
5. Do not forget about the turrets and their use can also not bad on the defensive, and in the hands of the settlers just give things that do not slow down work time (still standing arms gives debuff on speed, but all kinds of chips such as chainsaws -no).

Q. Can I craft details of the weapons parts and heavy weapons, or I can just buy them from the traders?
A. You can get them at dismantling weapons in the tables and buying them from traders. When it comes to the boxes that unfold in the turrets, howitzers, etc., then they just bought, or they can be grabbed at sieges events. Their production is not possible.
</description>

    </HelpDef>


    <HelpDef>
        <defName>ABT</defName>

        <category>SKHelp</category>

        <label>About</label>

        <description>Frequently Asked Questions (FAQ) for Rimworld Hardcore SK presented by Hardcore SK team: Rey and skyarkhangel.</description>

    </HelpDef>

</Defs>
