<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Defs>
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef Abstract="true" Name="UpdateFeatureBase">
		<modNameReadable>Dubs Bad Hygiene</modNameReadable>
		<modIdentifier>DubsBadHygiene</modIdentifier>
		<linkUrl>https://www.patreon.com/dubwise56</linkUrl>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

  <HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>DubsBadHygiene_2_7_1055</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>2.7.1055</assemblyVersion>
		<content>
New stuff:
|img:DBH/UI/swimmingpool|caption:Added a swimming pool.
|Added survival mode which limits the shallow water grid to tiny patches and reduces the size of the deep grid.
Added water bottles for use with thirst need.
Added a drink def extension to drinks from VGP &amp; RimCuisine which allows them to be used for filling the thirst need.
Pawns will pack water bottles from water sources, or drinks from VGP &amp; RimCuisine or any other modded drinks that add the water extension with patches.
Added rain irrigation option, rain will irrigate fertile terrain like sprinklers do.
Added hydroponics link option which adds water usage to any powered growing buildings like hydroponics, plants will start to take damage from dehydration instead of power loss.
Added hydrotherapy as a joy type, hot tubs and swimming pools count as hydrotherapy.
Biosolid fertilizer is now placed using an area system instead of building fertilizer patches.
Pawns will automatically replenish fertilizer in fertilized areas.

Major Changes:
Combined the Hygiene and hygiene/Misc tabs into 1.
Changed the projects from short chains of research to individual projects allowing you to research only buildings that you actually want, which also reduces clutter in the architect menu.
New system for finding fixtures and water sources.
Pawns now find and sort water sources and drinks by the shortest path rather than the shortest distance.
Pawns will gradually look greater distances for fixtures as their need to use one grows.
Pawns will now visit a basin for water before washing a patient.
Pawns will now use carried drinks to feed to patients or find a drink to carry to them.
Food now directly adds 20% of the nutritional value to the thirst bar instead of the thirst bar raising when the food bar is above 50%.
Added some more stages to medieval research.
Pawns will now ignore fixtures with contaminated water supply unless they are in urgent need of water.
New method for applying diseases from contaminated water, untreated water has a small chance of only diarrhea, contaminated water has a very high chance of giving diarrhea, and small chances for dysentery or cholera.
Removed the paint fixtures tool, Dubs Paint Shop replaces this feature.

Minor Changes:
Added missing pump, missing well, and missing water tower alerts.
Added warning to thermostats if hot water tanks aren't set to thermostat mode.
Added more values to the need rate options for more control.
Fixed a bug that prevented the thermostat mode on hot water tanks working correctly without a room thermostat.
Added a patch to prevent any bad hygiene related items appearing in resource pods.
Litter boxes now hidden when animal bladders is disabled.
Fountains are now hidden when thirst is disabled.
Animals of any size will now be able to use litter boxes.
Pawns will now use toilets, showers, and drink during parties.
Combined the different size ceiling fans into 1 button.
Changed water tank drain to a designated job.
Baths can be heated by placing both a log boiler or a camp fire in an adjacent cell, other defs can be added as heat source for the bath.
Drinking dirty or clean water now gives a debuff or buff.
Empty water towers no longer become contaminated.
Changed irrigation and fire sprinklers placement to work like ceiling fans.
Reduced the cost of some research projects.
Hot tubs and swimming pools can be used during parties.
Sewage outlets are now stuffed.
General refactoring and code optimization.
</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
</Defs>