<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Defs>

	<!--===================== Concepts taught through the learning readout, with no opportunity needed ===================-->

	<ConceptDef>
		<defName>CE_InventoryWeightBulk</defName>
		<label>CE: Mass and bulk</label>
		<priority>19</priority>
		<helpText>You can order your colonists to pick up items and store them in their inventory. They are limited in this by their carry weight and bulk capacity.\n\nCarry weight is determined by movement capacity and the more weight a colonist is carrying, the slower they are.\n\nBulk represents the space in your colonists' pockets and can be increased by equipping loadbearing gear like backpacks and tactical vests. The more stuffed their pockets are, the slower they'll work, so only pick up things you actually need.\n\nYou can check a colonist's load by selecting them, clicking the INVENTORY button and hovering over the displayed bars.\n\nTo order a colonist to pick something up, select him, right-click an item and select the 'Pick up' option.</helpText>
		<highlightTags>
			<li>ITab-Gear-Closed</li>
		</highlightTags>
	</ConceptDef>

	<ConceptDef>
		<defName>CE_Loadouts</defName>
		<label>CE: Loadouts</label>
		<priority>18</priority>
		<helpText>Colonists can be told to automatically pick up certain items to avoid inventory micromanagement. For example you can tell them to keep ammo for their primary weapon and they will stock up after a firefight.\n\nOpen the ASSIGN tab and press the 'Manage loadouts' button. Create a new loadout and set the items and quantity you want your colonists to keep. Then you can assign that loadout to your colonists and they will automatically manage their inventories.</helpText>
		<highlightTags>
			<li>MainTab-Assign-Closed</li>
			<li>CE_ManageLoadouts</li>
		</highlightTags>
	</ConceptDef>

	<ConceptDef>
		<defName>CE_AmmoCrafting</defName>
		<label>CE: Ammo crafting</label>
		<priority>8</priority>
		<helpText>Ensuring your colonists are supplied with quality ammo is vital to surviving on a Rimworld. Simple stone arrows can be obtained from the crafting but perform very poorly against opponents with advanced armor and clothing.\n\nSteel and plasteel arrows offer better penetration and can be made at the smithing bench once smithing is researched.\n\nResearch gunsmithing to unlock the loading bench, where you can craft ammo for most firearms. Artillery shells and grenades are made at the machining table.\n\nWhile most conventional ammo types can be made from simple raw materials, advanced ammo requires more exotic ingredients such as components, FSX or Prometheum.</helpText>
	</ConceptDef>

	<ConceptDef>
		<defName>CE_ObtainingFSX</defName>
		<label>CE: Obtaining FSX</label>
		<priority>3</priority>
		<helpText>FSX is the main ingredient for explosives such as frag grenades and mortar shells. You can obtain it either through traders or by taming boomrats and boomalopes, then harvesting the volatile chemicals they produce.\n\nOnce tamed they will produce a steady stream of FSX that your colonists will automatically harvest similar to other animal resources like wool and milk.\n\nYou can see your animal's current chemical fullness by selecting it and checking the readout in the lower-left corner.</helpText>
	</ConceptDef>

	<ConceptDef>
		<defName>CE_ObtainingPrometheum</defName>
		<label>CE: Obtaining Prometheum</label>
		<priority>2</priority>
		<helpText>Prometheum is used in most incendiary weapons such as incendiary mortar shells, AP-I rounds and molotovs. It is a highly flammable liquid that is harvested from the blazebulb plant.\n\nTo grow blazebulb, simply select a growing zone and set it to plant blazebulb.\n\nWarning: Blazebulbs are highly sensitive and have a chance to ignite if the surrounding temperature exceeds 28°C/82F. They will also leak puddles of Prometheum when damaged, which ignite on contact with air.\n\nMake sure your plantation has good climate control and is fire-proofed, otherwise it might quickly turn into a blazing inferno!</helpText>
		<highlightTags>
			<li>GrowingZoneSetPlant</li>
		</highlightTags>
	</ConceptDef>

	<ConceptDef>
		<defName>CE_CentipedeArmor</defName>
		<label>CE: Fighting Mechanoids</label>
		<priority>1</priority>
		<helpText>Warning: It is only a matter of time before Mechanoids take notice of your arrival and start attacking. The larger models have heavy armor that is impervious to small-arms fire.\n\nFighting them requires powerful weapons such as heavy machine guns or explosives. You should keep a healthy stockpile of these weapons if you hope to survive for long.</helpText>
	</ConceptDef>

</Defs>