<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Defs>
	
	<!--===================== Concepts taught through the learning readout, when opportunities arise ===================-->

  <!-- defName and highlight tags for reloading concepts must be identical for reload gizmo to recognize them -->
	<ConceptDef>
		<defName>CE_ReusableNeolithicProjectiles</defName>
		<label>CE: Reusable projectiles</label>
		<priority>50</priority>
		<needsOpportunity>True</needsOpportunity>
		<helpText>Several projectiles can be re-used after they impact something. This applies to such projectiles as arrows, great arrows, slingshot stones and crossbow bolts. Re-usable ammo is initially forbidden, and re-usability follows a tiered progression: stone arrows will break on impact more often than plasteel ones.\n\nIf you prefer to go without this feature, turn off "Re-use neolithic projectiles" in the mod settings menu (Settings -> Mod settings -> CombatExtended).</helpText>
	</ConceptDef>
	
	<ConceptDef>
		<defName>CE_Reload</defName>
		<label>CE: Reloading guns</label>
		<priority>50</priority>
		<needsOpportunity>True</needsOpportunity>
		<helpText>Guns have limited magazine capacity and display their current ammo amount when selecting the gun or its wielder. Once a magazine is empty your colonist needs to spend time reloading. This can take quite a long time for some weapons and consumes ammo from the shooter's inventory.\n\nIn addition to the magazine count guns display their currently loaded ammo type. Different types of ammo can have significantly different performance. It's important to select the appropriate ammo for the enemy you're fighting.\n\nYou can manually order a reload or change the selected ammo type by selecting a colonist and clicking the RELOAD button. This will bring up a menu with a reload command and a list of ammo types in the colonist's inventory.\n\nThe 'Unload' command can be used to dump the currently loaded ammo into the inventory. Ordering a reload with a partially filled magazine will do this automatically.</helpText>
		<highlightTags>
			<li>CE_Reload</li>
		</highlightTags>
	</ConceptDef>

  <ConceptDef>
    <defName>CE_ReloadNoMag</defName>
    <label>CE: Weapons without magazine</label>
    <priority>50</priority>
    <needsOpportunity>True</needsOpportunity>
    <helpText>Some weapons such as bows have no magazine that can be loaded. They instead consume ammo directly from their wielder's inventory.\n\nYou can select a pawn and use the RELOAD button to select which of the currently carried ammo-types to use.</helpText>
    <highlightTags>
      <li>CE_ReloadNoMag</li>
    </highlightTags>
  </ConceptDef>

	<ConceptDef>
    <defName>CE_ReloadAuto</defName>
    <label>CE: Reloading auto-turrets</label>
    <priority>50</priority>
    <needsOpportunity>True</needsOpportunity>
    <helpText>Auto-turrets have a limited ammo capacity and no means of reloading themselves. Colonists assigned to the 'Haul' worktype will automatically refill auto-turrets' magazines once they haven't fired for a while.\n\nYou can also order a manual reload by selecting a hauler and right-clicking the turret.\n\nTo select which ammo type your colonists should load, select the turret and click the RELOAD button to bring up a list of all possible ammo types.</helpText>
    <highlightTags>
      <li>CE_ReloadAuto</li>
    </highlightTags>
  </ConceptDef>

  <ConceptDef>
    <defName>CE_ReloadManned</defName>
    <label>CE: Reloading manned turrets</label>
    <priority>50</priority>
    <needsOpportunity>True</needsOpportunity>
    <helpText>Manned turrets require reloading just like regular guns. Whenever there is a pawn manning them they will automatically use ammo from their inventory to reload or fetch ammo from a nearby stockpile if they're not carrying any.\n\nYou can select a turret and use the RELOAD button to order a manual reload or change the ammo type for that turret. You can also use the 'Unload' command to dump the currently loaded ammo out.\n\nNote that the turret needs to have someone manning it to execute reload commands.</helpText>
    <highlightTags>
      <li>CE_ReloadManned</li>
    </highlightTags>
  </ConceptDef>

  <ConceptDef>
    <defName>CE_FireModes</defName>
    <label>CE: Fire modes</label>
    <priority>50</priority>
    <needsOpportunity>True</needsOpportunity>
    <helpText>Fully-automatic weapons can be fired in multiple ways. You can choose between single, burst and full-auto fire. Longer bursts have increased damage and can suppress more easily but the longer the burst, the more accuracy is lost to recoil. They also deplete magazines much more quickly.\n\nUse lower shot counts for far-away enemies you want to hit and longer bursts for suppression, close range and clumped up enemies.\n\nTo change a colonist's fire mode select him, then click the FIRE MODE button to cycle through the available modes. The button also displays the currently selected mode.</helpText>
    <highlightTags>
      <li>CE_FireModeToggle</li>
    </highlightTags>
  </ConceptDef>
  
  <ConceptDef>
    <defName>CE_AimModes</defName>
    <label>CE: Aim modes</label>
    <priority>50</priority>
    <needsOpportunity>True</needsOpportunity>
    <helpText>Depending on the weapon, your colonists can use up to three different aim modes when shooting: aimed shot, snapshot, and suppress.\n\nAimed shot reduces weapon sway, increasing the likelyhood of hitting a target, but requires two aiming cycles before firing a shot, with the exact aim time depending on the distance to the target. The further away a target is, the longer the shooter has to aim. The bonus provided by aimed shot depends on the shooter's aiming accuracy. A skilled sharpshooter can eliminate nearly all sway by using aimed shot, whereas a low-skilled shooter gains only very little benefit.\n\nSnapshot requires only one aiming cycle before firing, and is ideal in cases where weapon sway isn't as impactful (such as close-range gunfights) or for low-skill shooters where shooting more often is generally preferable to the negligible benefit they'd get from aimed shot.\n\nSuppress is mechanically identical to Snapshot, except it allows shooting at targets that have hunkered down behind cover and are no longer visible by the shooter. While those shots will not realistically hit their target due to obstructions, they are effective at keeping enemies pinned down, preventing them from returning fire.\n\nTo cycle between the fire modes select a colonist and click the AIM MODE button. The button will change to display the currently selected mode.\n\nPawns affected by suppression cannot use aimed shot, regardless of what setting is selected (they will use snapshot if set to aimed shot). Mechanoids and auto-turrets on the other hand always use aimed shot.</helpText>
    <highlightTags>
      <li>CE_AimModeToggle</li>
    </highlightTags>
  </ConceptDef>
    
  <ConceptDef>
    <defName>CE_Spotting</defName>
    <label>CE: Artillery spotting</label>
    <priority>50</priority>
    <needsOpportunity>True</needsOpportunity>
    <helpText>You can have colonists act as spotters for artillery. To do this, equip a pair of binoculars, then order your colonist to target an enemy or a spot on the ground.\n\nAfter a while the target will be marked with a red 'x'. Now select your mortar and order it to fire at the marked target.\n\nThis not only removes indirect fire penalties, it will also use the spotter's aiming accuracy instead of the mortar operator's. Use skilled spotters with sharp eyes to direct artillery directly onto your enemies.</helpText>
  </ConceptDef>
  
  <ConceptDef>
    <defName>CE_MortarDirectFire</defName>
    <label>CE: Artillery direct fire</label>
    <priority>50</priority>
    <needsOpportunity>True</needsOpportunity>
    <helpText>Mortars are much more accurate when firing at targets they can see. If your mortar operator is within sniper rifle range of the target and has direct line of sight to it they will be able to direct fire directly.\n\nWhen firing at targets they can't see mortars need spotters or they suffer hefty accuracy penalties. You can check your hit chances by selecting the mortar and hovering over a target.</helpText>
  </ConceptDef>

  <ConceptDef>
    <defName>CE_AimingSystem</defName>
    <label>CE: New aiming system</label>
    <priority>50</priority>
    <needsOpportunity>True</needsOpportunity>
    <helpText>Combat Extended uses a new physics-based projectile system. Projectiles follow a ballistic flight path and use hitboxes for collision detection. Several factors determine how close a bullet will fly near it's target:\n\n-Visibility: Darkness, bad weather and smoke make it harder to see the target.\n-Movement: shooter has to lead a moving target. Lead error means the shooter might aim too far forward or back in the direction of movement.\n-Range: shooter needs to correctly estimate how far away the target is. Range error means the shooter will aim as if target was x cells closer/further than it actually is.\n-Sway: Weapons will sway in the hands of the shooter. Reduced by aimed shot mode (reduction depends on skill and sights efficiency).\n-Recoil: Shots within a burst gradually become less accurate\n-Weapon spread: Bullets randomly deviate in a cone (e.g. shotgun pellets).\n-Cover height: Cover obscures parts of the target's hitbox. Can block line of sight for smaller targets (e.g. squirrels behind sandbags).\n-Body size\n-Stance: Downed or hunkering pawns are harder to hit.\n\nYou can get a detailed breakdown by selecting a shooter and hovering the mouse over a target. Given measurements are the maximum deviation in cells/degrees and target/cover hitbox dimensions in cells.</helpText>
  </ConceptDef>
  
  <ConceptDef>
    <defName>CE_Stabilizing</defName>
    <label>CE: Stabilizing injuries</label>
    <priority>50</priority>
    <needsOpportunity>True</needsOpportunity>
    <helpText>When a living creature is downed its wounds can be stabilized using medicine. This will temporarily reduce the amount of blood loss but does nothing to actually treat the wound.\n\nSelect a colonist with medicine in his inventory and right-click the creature you want to stabilize, then click the 'Stabilize' option.\n\nThe amount of bleed reduction depends on medicine skill and medicine used. Internal injuries are harder to treat than external ones and missing body parts can't be stabilized at all.</helpText>
  </ConceptDef>
  
  <ConceptDef>
    <defName>CE_Shields</defName>
    <label>CE: Shields</label>
    <priority>50</priority>
    <needsOpportunity>True</needsOpportunity>
    <helpText>Shields can provide protection against projectiles and melee attacks at the cost of being unable to use two-handed weapons. They are divided into two categories: regular shields and ballistic shields.\n\nRegular shields will deflect projectiles impacting the torso and have a chance to deflect melee attacks depending on the attacker's and defender's melee skills.\n\nBallistic shields are large and cumbersome, inflicting penalties to melee and ranged combat but they also cover the entire head area and can be crouched behind to protect most of the legs.\n\nShields don't make you invincible however, taking offensive actions will expose the weapon arm while high-penetration rounds will punch through or damage the shield. Don't expect a wooden shield to deflect gunfire!</helpText>
  </ConceptDef>

  <ConceptDef>
    <defName>CE_ArmorSystem</defName>
    <label>CE: New armor system</label>
    <priority>50</priority>
    <helpText>Combat Extended replaces the vanilla armor system with a penetration-based model. Blunt and sharp type weapons have armor penetration values which determine how much their damage is reduced by armor.\n\nArmor values above the attacker's armor penetration are deflected entirely, whereas values below will reduce damage based on the ratio of armor to AP. (e.g: if a 8mm RHA armor is hit by a 10mm RHA projectile, the armor will block 80% of the damage)\n\nIn the case of a deflection, a sharp attack is converted into blunt (preventing bleeding and internal organ damage), and rolling against the armor's blunt rating.\n\nEnvironmental damage such as fire/electricity has no penetration and is simply reduced by the % of armor against that type.</helpText>
  </ConceptDef>

  <ConceptDef>
    <defName>CE_SuppressionReaction</defName>
    <label>CE: Suppression</label>
    <priority>50</priority>
    <helpText>All humans have a suppression meter, based on their mental break threshold and current mood. Any time gunfire passes by them, it will add to the meter based on projectile power and (lack of) worn armor. \n\nWhen someone's suppression threshold is reached they will panic, run for the nearest cover and become incapable of using aimed shot mode, making it a good tool to break up melee charges or reduce sniper accuracy. It will also impart a mood penalty, making them easier to suppress in the future.\n\nYou can recognize suppressed pawns by the yellow downwards arrow they're emitting.</helpText>
  </ConceptDef>

  <ConceptDef>
    <defName>CE_Hunkering</defName>
    <label>CE: Hunkering</label>
    <priority>50</priority>
    <helpText>If someone's suppression meter maxes out they will hunker in panic. This causes them to run for the nearest cover and lie down, unable to shoot back or take any action until their suppression ticks down, essentially removing them from the fight.\n\nHunkering pawns are marked by an orange downwards arrow.</helpText>
  </ConceptDef>
  
  <ConceptDef>
    <defName>CE_WornBulk</defName>
    <label>CE: Bulky clothing</label>
    <priority>50</priority>
    <helpText>Certain clothing items are very bulky and will hinder your colonists in their daily tasks, lowering work speed when worn. These items include things like armor and regular clothing made from certain materials such as hyperweave.\n\nYou can check the info-menu of a particular apparel to see its 'worn bulk' stat to see how much bulk it adds when equipped on a colonist.</helpText>
  </ConceptDef>

  <ConceptDef>
    <defName>CE_Crouching</defName>
    <label>CE: Crouching</label>
    <priority>50</priority>
    <helpText>Any drafted human will crouch when they are not moving, making them a smaller target. You can get a detailed breakdown by selecting a shooter and hovering the mouse over a target.\n\nCrouched pawns will make efficient use of nearby cover, only revealing enough of their head to aim and shoot.</helpText>
  </ConceptDef>
  
</Defs>
