<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>Fluffy Breakdowns</name>
  <author>Fluffy</author>
  <url>https://ludeon.com/forums/index.php?topic=16120.0</url>
  <targetVersion>0.16.1393</targetVersion>
  <description>

[English]

Replaces random breakdowns with a maintenance requirement.

&lt;size=24&gt;Important&lt;/size&gt;
This mod requires HugsLib to be installed, and loaded before it.

&lt;size=24&gt;Features&lt;/size&gt;
Buildings using components will now gradually deteriorate. The odds of a breakdown happening (and requiring replacement components), is directly linked to the amount of deterioration. 

To keep your machinery in top shape, your colonists with the construction work enabled will periodically maintain components. As long as components are properly maintained, they cannot randomly break down. 

&lt;size=24&gt;Notes&lt;/size&gt;
I’m very interested in any feedback on how these changes affect the difficulty of the game. I’ve tried to balance it so that it’s not too hard/easy - but I’m just one person with one playstyle.

&lt;size=24&gt;Contributors&lt;/size&gt;

duduluu:    Chinese translations

[Russian]

Вмсто случаных поломок механизмов - постоянное естественное старение и плановое техобслуживание.

&lt;size=24&gt;Предупреждение&lt;/size&gt;
Этот мод требует, чтобы HugsLib был установлен и загружен до него.

&lt;size=24&gt;Особенности&lt;/size&gt;
Сооружения, использующие компоненты, теперь будут постепенно ухудшаться. Шансы на случай отказа (и требующие техобслуживания (ТО)) напрямую связаны с величиной ухудшения.

Чтобы ваша техника была в отличной форме, ваши колонисты-ремонтники будут проводить периодическое ТО. Пока механиз мы обслуживаются по графику, они не могут случайно сломаться.

&lt;size=24&gt;Замечание&lt;/size&gt;
Мне очень интересны любые отзывы о том, как эти изменения влияют на сложность игры. Я пытался сбалансировать мод так, чтобы он не был слишком сложным / легким, - но я всего лишь один человек с одним стилем игры.

</description>
</ModMetaData>
