<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <PRFHelp>도움말</PRFHelp>
  <PRFHelpDesc>도움말 열기.</PRFHelpDesc>
  <PRFViewOrdo>Ordo Historia: {0}</PRFViewOrdo>

  <PaperclipFactory_HelpText>The EMC factory doesn't just take in steel - it can make EMC from any item by manipulating its subatomic structure. The number of EMC produced is equivalent to 1/4 of the combined mass of the ingredients.</PaperclipFactory_HelpText>
  <PaperclipFactory_OrdoText><![CDATA[<b>Ordo Historia Standardization Archive - OHS 15616 - A paperclip used as feedstock for a standard atomic 3d printing device(OHS 6011)</b>
Section 1.1 - Physical properties
- A single paperclip must weigh 1.0 ± 1*10^-8 grams.
- It can be made out of any form of matter, including exotic matter(OHS 11279) such as Dalekanium, Unobtainium or Vibranium; however, the end product has to exhibit the properties of a metal such that it is pliable, ductile and malleable.
- Paperclips must have a positive real mass.
- For instructions about how to manufacture a paperclip, see the Lantz-Foddy method for producing paperclips from matter(OHS 58281)
- Paperclips mus<color=red><b>[TRANSMISSION ABORTED - POTENTIAL SECURITY BREACH DETECTED]</b></color>
]]>  </PaperclipFactory_OrdoText>
  <PRFPaperclipPowerGenerator_HelpText>The EMC power generator is just like a normal power generator, except it runs off EMC and has 2 extra features:\n1. You can adjust the fuel consumption rate to ramp up/down the power production.\n2. After unlocking "EMC power generator: self-improvement" in research, power production efficiency can slowly ramp up, as long as the building has fuel and is powered at all times.</PRFPaperclipPowerGenerator_HelpText>
  <AtomicReconstructor_HelpText>The atomic reconstructor turns EMC into items. Simply fuel it up, add power, set the item you want to produce and wait. You can also make it work faster by adjusting the slider. Note that the speed is directly proportional to the square of the EMC cost, for example if you set the speed to 2x, it will use 4x more EMC.\n\nGenerally, items that are more expensive take longer to make, and items that are heavier cost more EMC.\n\nNote: The atomic reconstructor cannot make any items that have to be made from a material (for example, steel longsword)</AtomicReconstructor_HelpText>
  <PRFPaperclipDuplicator_HelpText>Think of the EMC duplicator as a bank: it stores EMC and gives you a set interest on those EMC. The Duplicator tab provides an interface for you to deposit/withdraw EMC. Note that you need to provide a cargo platform as an item source for depositing/withdrawing EMC.\n\nThe formula that is used for calculating the current EMC amount is:\nCurrentBalance = 1.05^(DaysPassed) * InitialBalance</PRFPaperclipDuplicator_HelpText>



  <!--================================ Industry (simple assemblers) ==============================-->
  <PRF_Recycler_HelpText>This machine can recycle crushing and sorting almost any apperal and weapon back to useable raw resources in a cost of some lost materials. Remember to clear output so new stuff can be spit out.</PRF_Recycler_HelpText>
  <PRF_PartAssembler_HelpText></PRF_PartAssembler_HelpText>
  <PRF_FurnaceI_HelpText></PRF_FurnaceI_HelpText>
  <PRF_FurnaceII_HelpText></PRF_FurnaceII_HelpText>
  <PRF_FurnaceIII_HelpText></PRF_FurnaceIII_HelpText>
  <PRF_MetalRefinery_HelpText></PRF_MetalRefinery_HelpText>
  <PRF_StoneWorks_HelpText></PRF_StoneWorks_HelpText>


  <!--================================ Assemblers ==============================-->
  <PRF_RecipeDatabase_HelpText>To start importing recipes, place this near a powered worktable, go to "Import recipe...", and select the recipe you want to import.\n\nAfterwards reinstall this near assembler(s) to share recipes.\n\nCan store multiple recipes from different workbenches.</PRF_RecipeDatabase_HelpText>
  <PRF_TypeOneAssembler_I_HelpText>To get any assembler building set up, go to its "Bills" tab and add the bills you want in order. Then configure its output so that the yellow cell is where you want the products to go. Finally, place the required ingredients around it (if you're using a smart hopper, remember to check "toggle allow forbidden"), and give it power.\n\nTo feed recipes into this assembler, build a recipe database and place it next to the work table you want to copy bills from(See the recipe database help for additional instructions). Once finished with the import(s), reinstall it near this building.\n\nPlease note max level recipes for this assembler is: 10, art level is 9</PRF_TypeOneAssembler_I_HelpText>
  <PRF_TypeTwoAssembler_I_HelpText>This assembler is special in that it gets faster and better quality at its recipes the more it works on them. Over time, however, this skill also decays exponentially.\n\nTo get any assembler building set up, go to its "Bills" tab and add the bills you want in order. Then configure its output so that the yellow cell is where you want the products to go. Finally, place the required ingredients around it (if you're using a smart hopper, remember to check "toggle allow forbidden"), and give it power.\n\nTo feed recipes into this assembler, build a recipe database and place it next to the work table you want to copy bills from. See the help for the recipe database for additional instructions. Once finished with the import(s), reinstall it near this building.\n\nPlease note max level recipes for this assembler is: 20, art level is 12</PRF_TypeTwoAssembler_I_HelpText>


  <!--================================ Misc. ==============================-->
  <Lighting_FloorLampArrow_HelpText>Signs to indicate what direction things going or just decorate your room? Someone spilled glowy goo from bugs while making it so it have a slight glow to it</Lighting_FloorLampArrow_HelpText>
  <Lighting_RedFloorLampArrow_HelpText>Signs to indicate what direction things going or just decorate your room? Someone spilled glowy goo from bugs while making it so it have a slight glow to it</Lighting_RedFloorLampArrow_HelpText>
  <Lighting_GreenFloorLampArrow_HelpText>Signs to indicate what direction things going or just decorate your room? Someone spilled glowy goo from bugs while making it so it have a slight glow to it</Lighting_GreenFloorLampArrow_HelpText>
  <Lighting_FloorLampX_HelpText>Signs to indicate what direction things going or just decorate your room? Someone spilled glowy goo from bugs while making it so it have a slight glow to it</Lighting_FloorLampX_HelpText>

  <!--================================ Animal Stations ==============================-->
  <PRF_Shearer_HelpText>Animal harvesters automatically harvest animals when they come near the vicinity of the building. Store food at those stations to coerce animals to come to the stations so they can be harvested.</PRF_Shearer_HelpText>
  <PRF_Milker_HelpText>Animal harvesters automatically harvest animals when they come near the vicinity of the building. Store food at those stations to coerce animals to come to the stations so they can be harvested.</PRF_Milker_HelpText>
  <PRF_GenericAnimalHarvester_HelpText>Animal harvesters automatically harvest animals when they come near the vicinity of the building. Store food at those stations to coerce animals to come to the stations so they can be harvested.</PRF_GenericAnimalHarvester_HelpText>
  <PRF_Slaughterhouse_HelpText>A slaughter house that can manage and auto kill animals if they exceed a specified number, age or gender. good in combination with "Auto Meat Grinder" and "Animal stations"</PRF_Slaughterhouse_HelpText>
  <PRF_GenericAnimalHarvester_II_HelpText></PRF_GenericAnimalHarvester_II_HelpText>

  <!--================================ Miners ==============================-->
  <PRF_BillTypeMiner_I_HelpText>This is a Highly costumizable Miner that can be set for your need with newest spacer technolgy in your hands</PRF_BillTypeMiner_I_HelpText>
  <PRF_DeepQuarry_mkIII_HelpText>This quarry will extract random rare ores from ground from steel to gold, please note if any mod is added that adds ores those will be mined here too including stone type, that will need a patch to fix</PRF_DeepQuarry_mkIII_HelpText>
  <PRF_DeepQuarry_mkII_helpText>The deep quarry is used for extraction of random mineral resources from underground, and produces a resource on average once every 6 hours. It functions like a colonist miner would - it randomly selects a rock or compacted resource (Granite, compacted steel) according to commonality and returns its mined products. Hence, rock chunks are the most common products of deep quarries, followed by the various commonalities of other resources.</PRF_DeepQuarry_mkII_helpText>
  <PRF_DeepQuarry_mkI_HelpText>The deep quarry is used for extraction of random mineral resources from underground, and produces a resource on average once every 6 hours. It functions like a colonist miner would - it randomly selects a rock or compacted resource (Granite, compacted steel) according to commonality and returns its mined products. Hence, rock chunks are the most common products of deep quarries, followed by the various commonalities of other resources.</PRF_DeepQuarry_mkI_HelpText>


  <!--================================ Cooking ==============================-->
  <PRF_SelfPrepper_HelpText>This is a Automatic food prepping table made originally for VGP Gourmet but will be featured in other mods and maybe vanilla too. input raw food and get out ingredient to make food</PRF_SelfPrepper_HelpText>
  <PRF_MeatGrinder_HelpText>This Dangerous looking machine works by putting in dead animals, and out will come meat, hide and any other part? Remove fast from output to avoid clogging, as only one item can output at time.</PRF_MeatGrinder_HelpText>
  <PRF_SelfCookerI_HelpText>To get any assembler building set up, go to its "Bills" tab and add the bills you want in order. Then configure its output so that the yellow cell is where you want the products to go. Finally, place the required ingredients around it (if you're using a smart hopper, remember to check "toggle allow forbidden"), and give it power.\n\nPlease note max level recipes for this assembler is: 10</PRF_SelfCookerI_HelpText>
  <PRF_SelfCookerIII_HelpText>To get any assembler building set up, go to its "Bills" tab and add the bills you want in order. Then configure its output so that the yellow cell is where you want the products to go. Finally, place the required ingredients around it (if you're using a smart hopper, remember to check "toggle allow forbidden"), and give it power.\n\nPlease note max level recipes for this assembler is: 20</PRF_SelfCookerIII_HelpText>
  <PRF_FermentingBarrel_HelpText>To get this building set up, go to the “Bills” tab and aldd the bills you want in order. Then configure the output so that the yellow cell is where you want the beer to be placed after fermentation. Finally, place wort around it (if you are using a smart hopper, remember to check toggle “allow forbidden”), and give it power.</PRF_FermentingBarrel_HelpText>


  <!--================================ Storage ==============================-->
  <PRF_WoodCrate_I_HelpText></PRF_WoodCrate_I_HelpText>
  <PRF_WoodCrate_II_HelpText>To output to crates and cargo platforms with the "Industrial Rollers" mod, remember to use a roller pusher at the end.</PRF_WoodCrate_II_HelpText>
  <PRF_SteelCrate_I_HelpText>Tiny Steel crate usefull for tight spaces</PRF_SteelCrate_I_HelpText>
  <PRF_SteelCrate_II_HelpText>To output to crates and cargo platforms with the "Industrial Rollers" mod, remember to use a roller pusher at the end.</PRF_SteelCrate_II_HelpText>

  <PRF_DigitalStorageUnit_I_HelpText>The Industrial Storage unit (DSU) functions like any other storage building, but all items put inside are moved to the middle cell, allowing for virtually infinite storage capacity. There’s a limit set in mod setting, if set too high it might lag.\n\nTo prevent considerable lag in heavily used cargo platforms, the item readout in the "Items" tab only displays the first 500 items. You can, however, search for the item you want using the search bar.\n\nNOTE: To output to crates and cargo platforms with the "Industrial Rollers" mod, remember to use a roller pusher at the end.\nTo set direct DSU output right-click the desired output item in the DSU item list to have it move to the DSU output cell. \nYou can also right click and select a pawn and force wear to equip items from storage\n\n Pawn acces button forbid pawn to go directly into DSU and only use I/O</PRF_DigitalStorageUnit_I_HelpText>
  <PRF_IOPort_I_HelpText>To configure the storage unit I/O port, set the mode (input or output), and the unit you want to connect to. If you choose output, remember to also select the item that you want to pull.\nYou can use right click on storage tab to directly output that item/stack eq. a weapon, into selected I/O port.</PRF_IOPort_I_HelpText>

  <PRF_IOPort_IFridge_HelpText>This works like I/O port \n IT have a strange behavior with RimFridge comp i need to look at, if not working try set cargo platform again and swap in/out and make sure settings are ok, it should work with some fiddeling. (looking for a fix)</PRF_IOPort_IFridge_HelpText>


  <!--================================ Belts and pullers ==============================-->
  <PRF_Conveyor_Simple_I_HelpText>Conveyor belt, it can be placed and automaticly connect if it go together, if you need to split out you will need a Belt Splitter to do so.\n\n Items that will run over the end will fill cell in front of it or stockpile, it does not obey Filter settings as its not that smart. Use a Puller instead for that.\n\nYou can set them as "end belt" in each ones setting this will make item on that belt STOP an can be used in assembler and such, instead of a shelf/hopper.</PRF_Conveyor_Simple_I_HelpText>
  <PRF_Conveyor_Wall_I_HelpText>Conveyor belt, it can be placed and automaticly connect if it go together, if you need to split out you will need a Belt Splitter to do so.\n\n Items that will run over the end will fill cell in front of it or stockpile, it does not obey Filter settings as its not that smart. Use a Puller instead for that.\n\nYou can set them as "end belt" in each ones setting this will make item on that belt STOP an can be used in assembler and such, instead of a shelf/hopper.</PRF_Conveyor_Wall_I_HelpText>
  <PRF_Conveyor_UG_I_HelpText>underground belt: 'a segment of belt that goes underground. machines on the surface will not be able to pull from underground belts. you must use a Underground Starter to begin a length of underground belts, and an Underground Exit to re-emerge for use</PRF_Conveyor_UG_I_HelpText>
  <PRF_Conveyor_Connector_To_UG_HelpText>UG Entrance: begins a length of underground belt.  machines on the surface will not be able to pull from underground belts. you must use a Underground Starter to begin a length of underground belts, and an Underground Exit to re-emerge for use</PRF_Conveyor_Connector_To_UG_HelpText>
  <PRF_Conveyor_Connector_To_Floor_HelpText>UG Exit. ends a lenght of underground belt.  machines on the surface will not be able to pull from underground belts. you must use a Underground Starter to begin a length of underground belts, and an Underground Exit to re-emerge for use</PRF_Conveyor_Connector_To_Floor_HelpText>
  <PRF_Conveyor_Splitter_I_HelpText>Cenveyor Belt Splitter is used when you want to split your resources in different directions. Its not Just a splitter it also capable of sorting which goes which directions in its setting tab.</PRF_Conveyor_Splitter_I_HelpText>

  <PRF_FuelingMachine_HelpText>The fueling machine is quite easy to use. Point the robotic arm (yellow cell) at the building/cannon you want to fuel, place fuel next to it(white cells) and give it power.\nCan normal generators, and refuelables like that.\nIts also capable of fueling mortars and some modded mortar/turrets.\nSupport CE turrets.\nSupports SoS Torpedos! yay.</PRF_FuelingMachine_HelpText>
  <PRF_SimplePuller_I_HelpText>Simple item Puller, slower than later versions.\nIt can pull from Crates, DSU, Stockpile zones, Shelfs, Smart hopper. and can fill same type in the other end.\n\nYellow cell = output\nWhite cell = Input\nRemember to Toggle Pulling before it starts!\nSet filters and settings to get better control over it. Remember it will not output if item is not allowed in target destination or if output is blocked by a wall or another item.</PRF_SimplePuller_I_HelpText>
  <PRF_GrowzonePuller_I_HelpText>Works same as other pullers but this one only able to pull from Growzones.</PRF_GrowzonePuller_I_HelpText>

  <PRF_SimplePuller_II_HelpText>A Second Tiered Pusher That have some more options then Industrial roller version, this can properly connect if IR cant.</PRF_SimplePuller_II_HelpText>
  <PRF_SimplePuller_II_Wall_HelpText>This is walled version of the Second Tiered Pusher That have some more options then Industrial roller version, this can properly connect if IR cant.</PRF_SimplePuller_II_Wall_HelpText>
  <PRF_SimplePuller_II_Side_HelpText>A Angled puller that can pull to in left/right direction, might be usefull in some cases</PRF_SimplePuller_II_Side_HelpText>

  <PRF_SmartHopper_HelpText>The Smart Hopper pulls in nearby items from ground or stockpile cells onto itself and hold until a assembler can use it.\n\n If you want to use it on a assembler, remember to enable the assembler's "toggle allow forbidden" option to allow assembler to pull from hopper.</PRF_SmartHopper_HelpText>

  <!--================================ Batteries ==============================-->
  <PRF_4k_Battery_HelpText></PRF_4k_Battery_HelpText>
  <PRF_16k_Battery_HelpText></PRF_16k_Battery_HelpText>
  <PRF_64k_Battery_HelpText></PRF_64k_Battery_HelpText>
  <PRF_256k_Battery_HelpText></PRF_256k_Battery_HelpText>


  <!--================================ Cultivators ==============================-->
  <!-- Drone ones -->
  <PRF_DroneCultivator_I_HelpText>Tier 1 Drone cultivator, your gateway to fully automated agriculture.\n\nThis one works by placing it within range of growing zones or hydroponics. It will work on all zones and crops in range without a problem.  Tier 1 models will NOT autohaul harvested crops into storage, this is available at higher tier models after conducting the required Research.\n\nBase Stats:\nDrones: 1\nWorkArea: 11x11\nJobtypes: Growing\nWorktime: 1hour shifts\nSkill lv.: 10</PRF_DroneCultivator_I_HelpText>
  <PRF_DroneCultivator_II_sun_HelpText>The cultivator operates automatically if it is given power. It will sow and harvest crops in growing zones and output them into ground, use a growzone puller to collect. If you also have the mod SeedsPlease installed, the cultivator requires seeds to be placed next to it for sowing to work.</PRF_DroneCultivator_II_sun_HelpText>
  <PRF_DroneCultivator_II_HelpText></PRF_DroneCultivator_II_HelpText>
  <PRF_DroneCultivator_III_HelpText></PRF_DroneCultivator_III_HelpText>
  <!-- Mecha ones-->
  <PRF_OldTypeCultivator_I_HelpText>The cultivator operates automatically if it is given power. It will sow and harvest crops in growing zones and output them into a nearby cell. If you also have the mod SeedsPlease installed, the cultivator requires seeds to be placed next to it for sowing to work.</PRF_OldTypeCultivator_I_HelpText>
  <PRF_OldTypeCultivator_Sun_HelpText>The cultivator operates automatically if it is given power. It will sow and harvest crops in growing zones and output them into a nearby cell. If you also have the mod SeedsPlease installed, the cultivator requires seeds to be placed next to it for sowing to work.</PRF_OldTypeCultivator_Sun_HelpText>
  <PRF_OldTypeCultivator_Xl_HelpText></PRF_OldTypeCultivator_Xl_HelpText>
  <!-- Sprinklers -->
  <PRF_Sprinkler_I_HelpText>The sprinkler randomly boosts the growth of crops and plants by 1 hour each round. You can see which cell it is currently working at by selecting it.</PRF_Sprinkler_I_HelpText>
  <PRF_Sprinkler_II_HelpText></PRF_Sprinkler_II_HelpText>


  <!--================================ S.A.L ==============================-->
  <PRF_AutoCrafterSimple_HelpText></PRF_AutoCrafterSimple_HelpText>
  <PRF_AutoCrafter_HelpText></PRF_AutoCrafter_HelpText>
  <PRF_TheArtMachine_HelpText></PRF_TheArtMachine_HelpText>
  <PRF_TheArtMaster_HelpText></PRF_TheArtMaster_HelpText>
  <PRF_OverclockedAutoAssembler_HelpText></PRF_OverclockedAutoAssembler_HelpText>


  <!--================================ Drone stuff ==============================-->
  <PRF_MiniHelper_HelpText></PRF_MiniHelper_HelpText>
  <PRF_MiniDroneColumn_HelpText></PRF_MiniDroneColumn_HelpText>

  <!--   <xxx_HelpText></xxx_HelpText>   -->

</LanguageData>