<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Defs>
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef Abstract="true" Name="UpdateFeatureBase">
		<modNameReadable>Real Ruins</modNameReadable>
		<modIdentifier>RealRuins</modIdentifier>
		<linkUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1552146295</linkUrl>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
	
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>RealRuins_1_2_0</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>1.2.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>
&lt;i&gt;Hint 1: You can leave ruins event moving your pawns to a green area on map's edge.
Hint 2: You can use right mouse button to pick up any stuff while looting abandoned base. You can also load your caravan animals the same way.&lt;/i&gt;
|&lt;b&gt;Major changes&lt;/b&gt;
|1) In this version you can't instantly reform caravan between raids during the abandoned base event.
That's what you need the hints above for. On my opinion, during this encounter you should manually explore the ruins, find any valuable stuff, pick it up and leave before another hostile party arrives. From now on you won't be able to leave automatically after defeating initial defenders, picking goods lazily from the list. From now on, pick up all valuables and move to the map's edge.
Ok, you can actually revert to the old way in mod settings, but I won't recommend.
|2) Now contents of graves and cryptosleep pods are captured and spawned.
So if you open a cryptosleep pod and find a fatally infected colonist, you can be sure: it's the same colonist as in blueprint source game. And he still has been waiting for a healing serum since long time ago. The mod saves name, appearance, stats, health condition, traits and apparel, and so on (but not an entire pawn, it's still too much info). Also this feature works with corpses laying around and in general, with any containers and their contents.
&lt;i&gt;But please note that this will work only for newly captured blueprints, so you probably won't notice anything at first, until the server gets enough new blueprints. And you should probably clear your cache after a week and force loading some data to increase probability of getting additional content.&lt;/i&gt;
|&lt;b&gt;Minor changes&lt;/b&gt;
- Replaced most of collapsed rocks with various walls
- Dates of all events (including those in art objects) are now consistent across one ruins piece and are always earlier than current date
- During most encounters hostile units won't spawn near map's edge, so you can enter relatively safely
- Fires and torches are not spawned in ruins
- Separate settings for minimum and maximum ruins piece radius
- Added ability to reset mod settings to defaults
- Now you're not able to claim active turrets during abandoned base encounter
- Weapon shelves and other storages are spawned with the lowest storage priority possible, so your pawn won't run across the map to store your weapons
- Doors and locks compatibility checked
- Fixed bug with ruins placed on water
- Now mod tends to load more recent maps
- Rebalanced deterioration (now objects most likely won't lose more than 300-500 hit points, so no more "23 of 350000 hit-points" beta-poly walls)
- Fixed crash on exit
- Speed up loading (for me the game takes the same 70 seconds to load as before, but probably it will help for those who report 40 minutes loading)
		</content>                                 
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>RealRuins_1_2_1</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>1.2.1</assemblyVersion>
		<content>
Quick fixes of some annoying ruins event bugs.
		</content>                                 
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>RealRuins_1_8_0</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>1.8.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>
|&lt;b&gt;Important: &lt;/b&gt; this version has significantly reworked internal mechanics, and I'm not completely sure it will work absolutely the same as the previos version. So if you notice ruins generation become worse for you, or if you encounter compatibility or saving problems, please report to steam discussion thread.
|&lt;b&gt;Major changes and new features&lt;/b&gt;
|1) "Pristine ruins" event now has additional info: current wealth and raiders presence. So you can wait nearby before entering to get smaller initial enemy party. Also initial raiders party is toned down and made much more diverse. Now there are several groups of different factions, most likely fighting with each other, so you will face serious danger only if you decide to stay in ruins.
|2) Event threat level is tied to game difficulty. For peaceful difficulty level you won't get raids on ruins events
|3) Now you can instantly reform caravan if you wait some time (0.5 to 3 days) after defeating the last raid in current ruins location. So if you don't want to pick up things manually, just setup a temporary outpost and wait a couple of days.
|4) Your colonists may get a mood boost when visiting ruins. Boost amount is based on ruins wealth. If ruins wealth is too low you'll get a small mood penalty.
|5) Now you have an option to disable ruins on your starting location.
|&lt;b&gt;Minor changes and bugfixes&lt;/b&gt;
- Moved blueprints loading to a separate thread, this fixed short freezes on startup
- Fixed issue with 100% gear on corpses
- Rebalanced ruins density depending on settlement proximity
- Blueprint id is selected preliminaly for ruins events, so you can't savescum to get different ruins on each entry
- Unfinished items spawn normally
		</content>                                 
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>RealRuins_2_0_0</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>2.0.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>
|&lt;b&gt;Planetary Ruins!&lt;/b&gt;
Now you can visit all bases of all players who played their games on a planet with the same coverage, map size and seed. Some bases will be spawned as ruins (and you can explore them) and some will be spawned as factions' properties, so you can attack them with the same conseqences as for attacking a regular faction base.
To load planetary ruins you need to go to Options -&gt; Mod Settings -&gt; Real Ruins - Planetary Ruins and hit the load button.
If you're about to start a new game, you can check how many places on the map you can get for a particular seed, map size and planet coverage by visiting https://woolstrand.art	
Please note that this feature is still in beta and it's highly recommended to make a backup save game before trying. However, this feature won't influence your gameplay in any way until you manually load planetary ruins.

|&lt;b&gt;Caravan reforming changes&lt;/b&gt;
Ok, finally I managed to make caravan reforming in a way it supposed to be. Now you can reform caravan via standard caravan menu, but after that pawns will load caravan in the same way they load it on your home map. They will bring all items to a caravan packing spot and then leave via map edge. And a lot of things may happen while they're doing it!

|&lt;b&gt;Other changes&lt;/b&gt;
There are also a bit of stability changes, less bugs and error messages when importing some kind of maps, no more minified things issues and some more small changes I even can't recall now.
		</content>                                 
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>RealRuins_2_0_1</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>2.0.1</assemblyVersion>
		<content>
|&lt;b&gt;Caravan forming selector!&lt;/b&gt;
So, now you can select one of three ways of reforming caravan after ruins event. "Automatic" is a regular reform like you have on your home map. "Instant" is instant reform like in previous version. "Manual" is also one of two previous types where you need to collect all items manually and leave via map edge.
		</content>                                 
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>RealRuins_2_0_2</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>2.0.2</assemblyVersion>
		<content>
|&lt;b&gt;Caravan forming issue resolved&lt;/b&gt;
1. Fixed issue with automatic items unloading upon arriving on event or POI locations.
2. Now both Automatic and Manual caravan forming options work in the same way. They both allow manual items picking and they both allow homemap-style caravan forming (even when there are enemies, so watch your pawns!). Instant caravan reforming option is still available and it works the same way as before, instantly reforming caravan if there are no enemies nearby.
		</content>                                 
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>RealRuins_2_1_0</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>2.1</assemblyVersion>
		<content>
|&lt;b&gt;Version 1.1 compatibility&lt;/b&gt;
Looks like the mod works again with 1.1 game version.
		</content>                                 
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
</Defs>