<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><LanguageData>

    <Milk.label>milk</Milk.label>
    <Milk.description>Milk from an animal.</Milk.description>

    <InsectJelly.label>insect jelly</InsectJelly.label>
    <InsectJelly.description>Jelly stored and used as food by oversized insects. It is smooth, rich, and brings joy to those who consume it. Because of its unique biological properties, it can nourish almost any creature and never rots.</InsectJelly.description>

    <EggChickenUnfertilized.label>chicken egg (unfert.)</EggChickenUnfertilized.label>
    <EggChickenUnfertilized.description>Unfertilized chicken egg. It can be eaten raw, but it's much, much better cooked.</EggChickenUnfertilized.description>

    <EggChickenFertilized.label>chicken egg (fert.)</EggChickenFertilized.label>
    <EggChickenFertilized.description>Fertilized chicken egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a chick. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</EggChickenFertilized.description>

    <EggCobraFertilized.label>cobra egg (fert.)</EggCobraFertilized.label>
    <EggCobraFertilized.description>Fertilized cobra egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a baby cobra. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</EggCobraFertilized.description>

    <EggIguanaFertilized.label>iguana egg (fert.)</EggIguanaFertilized.label>
    <EggIguanaFertilized.description>Fertilized iguana egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a baby iguana. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</EggIguanaFertilized.description>

    <EggTortoiseFertilized.label>tortoise egg (fert.)</EggTortoiseFertilized.label>
    <EggTortoiseFertilized.description>Fertilized tortoise egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a baby tortoise. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</EggTortoiseFertilized.description>

    <EggCassowaryFertilized.label>cassowary egg (fert.)</EggCassowaryFertilized.label>
    <EggCassowaryFertilized.description>Fertilized cassowary egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a baby cassowary. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</EggCassowaryFertilized.description>

    <EggEmuFertilized.label>emu egg (fert.)</EggEmuFertilized.label>
    <EggEmuFertilized.description>Fertilized emu egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a baby emu. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</EggEmuFertilized.description>

    <EggOstrichFertilized.label>ostrich egg (fert.)</EggOstrichFertilized.label>
    <EggOstrichFertilized.description>Fertilized ostrich egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a baby ostrich. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</EggOstrichFertilized.description>

    <EggTurkeyFertilized.label>turkey egg (fert.)</EggTurkeyFertilized.label>
    <EggTurkeyFertilized.description>Fertilized turkey egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a baby turkey. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</EggTurkeyFertilized.description>

</LanguageData>