<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><LanguageData>

    <PlantPotato.label>potato plant</PlantPotato.label>
    <PlantPotato.description>A simple, highly nutritious tuber. Grows well even in somewhat poor soil. Harvests quickly. A strong, versatile crop.</PlantPotato.description>

    <PlantCorn.label>corn plant</PlantCorn.label>
    <PlantCorn.description>A large grain plant which produces ears of delicious yellow seeds. Takes a relatively long time to grow, but yields lots of food, takes a long time to spoil, and can be happily eaten raw. Needs fertile soil to grow well.</PlantCorn.description>

    <PlantRice.label>rice plant</PlantRice.label>
    <PlantRice.description>A low grain plant that thrives in rich soil and yields food fast, but is not nice to eat uncooked.</PlantRice.description>

    <PlantStrawberry.label>strawberry plant</PlantStrawberry.label>
    <PlantStrawberry.description>A fragile but tasty fruit. Delicious even when raw.</PlantStrawberry.description>

    <PlantHaygrass.label>haygrass</PlantHaygrass.label>
    <PlantHaygrass.description>A mixture of nutrient-rich grasses which yield large amounts of hay. Hay is edible for animals, but not humans.</PlantHaygrass.description>

    <PlantCotton.label>cotton plant</PlantCotton.label>
    <PlantCotton.description>Yields cotton, a fine plant fiber used to make cloth.</PlantCotton.description>

    <PlantDevilstrand.label>devilstrand</PlantDevilstrand.label>
    <PlantDevilstrand.description>This fragile mushroom was genetically engineered to produce a silk net of the highest grade. Long rumored to have mystical properties, it owes its name to the greed it inspires in people.</PlantDevilstrand.description>

    <PlantHealroot.label>healroot</PlantHealroot.label>
    <PlantHealroot.description>A slow-growing plant which yields herbal medicine when harvested.\n\nHealroot was selectively bred for centuries by settlers. It is sometimes also called "healer's hand" by tribespeople - a nickname it owes to its five major medicinal virtues.</PlantHealroot.description>

    <PlantHops.label>hop plant</PlantHops.label>
    <PlantHops.description>A flowering plant that yields hops, an essential ingredient in beer.</PlantHops.description>

    <PlantPsychoid.label>psychoid plant</PlantPsychoid.label>
    <PlantPsychoid.description>A leafy plant. Its leaves can be refined into various forms of the psychoid drug.</PlantPsychoid.description>

    <PlantSmokeleaf.label>smokeleaf plant</PlantSmokeleaf.label>
    <PlantSmokeleaf.description>A leafy plant cultivated for its psychological effects. Smokeleaf leaves can be prepared into joints at the crafting spot.</PlantSmokeleaf.description>

</LanguageData>