<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>MJ - MiniMap (A16)</name>
	<author>Mauro Junior</author>
	<targetVersion>0.16.1393</targetVersion>
	<description>
Version: 1.6 (Full) [Completo]

Future: Suggestions ?

Requires: None

[English]

First of all, I would like to thank Fluffy for suggesting that I use CCL for this minimap, and this allowed me to advance a lot in a short time. Again, my many thanks Fluffy.

The minimap has undergone numerous changes (for the better):

1 - The areas that can be viewed are:
Colonist
Non-Colonist
Animals
Real Estate Management
Electrical network
Mining
Mountains
Land
Camera

2 - You can drag the map and resize the Map (After activating the option, click with the LMB and drag inside the Map.)

3 - Allow to visualize the areas created in the game

4 - Click on the MiniMap and move the camera in the world

In the image above, you have a MiniMap preview in a game.

NOTE: When you click on a Menu option, A (enabled) or D (disabled) is displayed. Just click to switch between options.
NOTE: Clicks are always with RMB (Right Mouse Button) and LMB (Left Mouse Button) to select item menu.

[Brazilian]

Primeiramente, gostaria de agradecer ao Fluffy, pois me sugeriu utilizar o CCL para este minimap e isso permitiu avançar muito em pouco tempo. Novamente, meu muito obrigado Fluffy.

O minimapa sofreu inúmeras mudanças (para melhor):

1 - As áreas que podem ser visualizadas são:
Colonista
Não Colonista
Animais
Construções
Rede Elétrica
Mineração
Montanhas
Terreno
Camera

2 - Pode-se arrastar o mapa e redimensionar o mapa (Após ativar a opção, clique com o LMB e arraste dentro do Mapa.)

3 - Permiti visualizar as áreas criadas no jogo

4 - Clicar no MiniMapa e mover a câmera no mundo

Na imagem acima, tem uma prévia do MiniMapa em um jogo.

NOTA: Quando clicar em uma opção do Menu, aparece A (ativado) ou D (desativado). Basta clicar para mudar entre as opções.
NOTA: Os cliques sempre são com o RMB (Botão Direito do Mouse) e LMB (Botão Esquerdo do Mouse) para selecionar um item do menu.

[Russian]

Прежде всего, я хотел бы поблагодарить Fluffy за то, что я предложил использовать CCL для этой мини-карты, и это позволило мне значительно продвинуться вперед за короткое время. Еще раз большое спасибо Fluffy.

Миникарта претерпела многочисленные изменения (к лучшему):

1 - Области, которые можно просмотреть:
Колонисты
Враги
Животные
Постройки
Электрические сети
Область раскопки
Горы
Тип почвы
Область видимости

2 - Вы можете перетащить карту и изменить размер карты (после активации этого параметра щелкните ЛКМ и перетащите его внутрь Карты).

3 - Позволяет визуализировать области, созданные в игре

4 - Нажмите на мини-карту и переместите камеру в мир

На изображении выше у вас есть предварительный просмотр MiniMap в игре.

ПРИМЕЧАНИЕ. Когда вы нажимаете кнопку «Меню», отображается A (включено) или D (отключено). Просто нажмите, чтобы переключаться между параметрами.
ПРИМЕЧАНИЕ. Для выбора элементов меню всегда используются щелчки ПКМ (правая кнопка мыши) и ЛКМ (левая кнопка мыши).
		
	</description>
</ModMetaData>
