<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>Arachnophobia SK</name>
	<author>Jecrell</author>
	<supportedVersions>
		<li>1.2</li>
	</supportedVersions>
	<packageId>skyarkhangel.arachnophobia</packageId>
	<modDependencies>
		<li>
			<packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
			<displayName>Harmony</displayName>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
			<downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
		</li>
	</modDependencies>
	<loadAfter>
		<li>brrainz.harmony</li>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld</li>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Royalty</li>
		<li>CETeam.CombatExtended</li>
	</loadAfter>
	<incompatibleWith>
		<li>Mlie.RimofMadnessArachnophobia</li>
	</incompatibleWith>
	<description>1.20.0.3 (10-30-2018) Updated to Rimworld 1.2 by skyarkhangel

  Adds spiders to RimWorld.

  * Features *
  ------------
  Adds Spiders
  - Eight-legged critters able to weave webs out of incredibly useful silk.
  Adds Giant Spiders
  - Giant genetically-engineered intelligent nephilids the size of a canine.
  Adds Flying Spider Queens
  - A failed genetic experiment gone wrong, flying spider queens are capable of creating giant spider eggs and flying short distances.
  Adds Webs.
  - Webs stun smaller animals for spiders to catch.
  - Webs can be harvested for spider silk.
  Adds Cocoons.
  - Spiders spin dead or downed prey into cocoons.
  - Cocoons will be carried by spiders to other cocoons to help make a spider home.
  - Cocoons can have their insides melted, making delicious juice for spiders.
  Adds Spider Silk
  - Webs and cocoons will occasionally drop spider silk that can be used in creating clothing.

Thank you to my Patrons for supporting me in my efforts. Without you, none of this would be possible.

These are the most excellent rim dwellers who support me: 
Maaxar, Shibby Says, TheJagermeister, Cory Bonifay, Kiya Nicoll, Matt Harris, Paul Fenwick, Grendalloffen, Martin K. Bonde, Bentley Alsup, Eric Idema, MasterScootie, GoSu, Josh McCabe, spook, Clifford Campbell, J, CrankyPeanut, E_T, Finwej, Jan Koutsky, Audrin Navarro, Михаил Юрченко, John Kanady, Luis Figueroa, Midgeman, Nate Haug, Nemuri Hime, Richard Paul, SilentWeirdo, Calum, Calhoun Cattell, Keith Thoma, Tim Stillson, Dick Jones, Patrick, Nathan Getman, Populous25, Sharp Spook, Steven James, Marcus Sireanu, Mark, Emily Shaw, Drachken, Zalson, Baron Xot, Nicholas Bateman, Christopher, Justin Andres, Luis Salvatierra, TinyFloatingTurtle, George Chong Chuang Ming, John Boehr, Oliver White, roxxploxx, Robin Hager, Brachiaraidos, That Guy, Toc Anastar, Karol Rybak, Allic, Austin Harbert, Yewty, Evan Hwang, Ryan Brock, Jonathan Holzinger, MC, Alexander, Kevin Reagan, Alex Mederer, Toss Antilles, Chelsea Archambeau, Aron Glasser, Dan Winn, Fredric Sundberg, Sarah Banks, ted stevens

========================
Changelog
========================
1.20.0.3 (10-30-2018)
========================
Spiders have extra damage. All spiders now use special neurotoxin that does not cause carcinomas or dementia but causes fast conscious loss that is easily recoverable after a few days. Spiders also tend victims wounds due to wrapping them in silk.

1.20.0.2 (10-30-2018)
========================
Rebalanced Giant Spiders. Massive damage addition. Stingers added for extra toxicity. Spider silk is now slightly stronger than Devilstrand, but burns more easily. Friendly spider webs do not trigger on guests anymore. Spiders now have 8 eyes.

1.20.0.1 (10-18-2018)
========================
Did not include Manifest.xml in the initial RimWorld 1.0 release.

1.20.0.0 (10-18-2018)
========================
Initial release for Arachnophobia for RimWorld 1.0.

1.19.0.4 (10-16-2018)
========================
Removes abstracts for ResourceBase and BaseFilth

	</description>
</ModMetaData>