<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>A Dog Said...</name>
	<author>spoonshortage</author>
	<url>https://ludeon.com/forums/index.php?topic=24578.0</url>
	<targetVersion>0.17.1557</targetVersion>
	<description>
Adds prosthetics/bionics and surgeries for animals

Following parts are added to the game:

A Dog Said Research Tab: Simple Animal Prosthetics, Animal Bionics, Animal Healing

* animal brain stimulator. Fits all animals.
* bionic animal eyes. Fits all animals. 
* bionic animal heart. Fits all animals.
* bionic animal lung. Fits all animals.
* bionic animal kidney. Fits all animals.
* bionic animal liver. Fits all animals.
* bionic animal stomach. Fits all animals.
* simple/bionic animal ears. Fits all animals except those without ears (birds,insects,snakes).
* simple/bionic animal jaw. Fits all animals. 
* simple/bionic animal spine. Fits all animals.
* simple/bionic animal arms. Fits monkey and megatherium.
* peglegs. Can be crafted with 1 wood. Fits all animals. Least efficiency.
* simple/bionic animal legs. Fits all animals.
* simple prosthetic tail. Fits all animals with tails.
* simple prosthetic nose. Fits all animals with nose (not birds,insects)

All parts can be obtained from traders, except peglegs.
All parts can be crafted at the animal prosthetics bench, after research of electricity and simple animal prosthetics
Crafting requires a skill of 5-12, depending on part.

Simple parts are slightly lower in efficiency than natural parts. Bionic parts are higher.


All parts need medicine skill and 1 medicine to be installed. 
Simple parts need a skill from 4-6. Bionic parts need a skill form 8-10.

Animal Healing of old wounds requires research, min med skill of 10 and 3 normal medicine. (make sure animals are set to receive it)

DMG on bionic parts is non variable from animal to animal. A fully bionic Yorkie will do the same damage as a fully bionic Thrumbo.
So make sure to not replace parts unneccissarily on higher damage animals.
</description>
</ModMetaData>
