<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Defs>

  <ScenarioDef>
    <defName>Nanotrasen</defName>
    <label>Nanotrasen</label>
    <description>NanoTrasen (NT) is one of the great megacorporations of the modern day. It deals in research of the most advanced sciences, such as genetics, blue space, and - recently - the uses of phoron, as well as mass consumer manufacturing on a truly galactic scale. They also have a sizeable asset protection and security branch with which they secure both investments and occasionally new acquisitions - a distressing rival to some minor star systems, and a powerful administrative branch sitting atop it all, directing their company's actions. NanoTrasen is characterized by its aggression and questionable ethics, which, combined with the high emphasis they put on new, untested and dangerous technology, means their installations are often considered unsafe and hazardous.\n\nYou have been genetically engineered in a lab and perfected to serve as a reconaissance unit. Your directive is to explore, discover and research new technolgies on distant planets and report your findings back to Nanotrasen. How you do this is left at your own discretion.</description>
    <scenario>
      <summary>You play as an all-purpose scouting unit, deployed as a member of the Nanotrasen megacorp.</summary>
      <playerFaction>
        <def>PlayerFaction</def>
        <factionDef>PlayerNanotrasen</factionDef>
      </playerFaction>
      <parts>

        <!-- Game start dialog -->
        <li Class="ScenPart_GameStartDialog">
          <def>GameStartDialog</def>
          <text>Your reasons for being here are a mystery to anyone but yourself. Maybe it was something you did to someone. Maybe you pushed your luck too hard. Whatever the cause, you must have left in a great hurry, considering you didn't bring any supplies with you. You receive a transmission on your radio, a familiar voice speaks to you:\n\n"I managed to sneak you out of there, but you need to leave this world ASAP. I wish i could do more for you, but i need to get back before they realize i'm missing or they'll know it was me who helped you escape. Best of luck." \n\nYou'll need a spaceship to get off the planet, but right now you better set up a camp in order to survive.</text>
          <closeSound>GameStartSting</closeSound>
        </li>
		
        <!-- Config pages -->
        <li Class="ScenPart_ConfigPage_ConfigureStartingPawns">
          <def>ConfigPage_ConfigureStartingPawns</def>
          <pawnCount>1</pawnCount>
		  <pawnChoiceCount>1</pawnChoiceCount>
        </li>

        <!-- Player starting stuff spawn method-->
        <li Class="ScenPart_PlayerPawnsArriveMethod">
          <def>PlayerPawnsArriveMethod</def>
          <method>DropPods</method>
        </li>
		
        <li Class="ScenPart_ScatterThingsAnywhere">
          <def>ScatterThingsAnywhere</def>
          <visible>false</visible>
          <thingDef>Totem</thingDef>
          <stuff>WoodLog</stuff>
          <count>20</count>
        </li>
        <li Class="ScenPart_ScatterThingsAnywhere">
          <def>ScatterThingsAnywhere</def>
          <visible>false</visible>
          <thingDef>Cairn</thingDef>
		  <stuff>BlocksGranite</stuff>
          <count>28</count>
        </li>
		<li Class="ScenPart_ScatterThingsAnywhere">
		  <def>ScatterThingsAnywhere</def>
		  <visible>false</visible>
		  <thingDef>ShipChunk</thingDef>
		  <count>10</count>
		</li>
		<li Class="ScenPart_ScatterThingsAnywhere">
		  <def>ScatterThingsAnywhere</def>
		  <visible>false</visible>
		  <thingDef>ShipMechChunk</thingDef>
		  <count>6</count>
		</li>
		<li Class="ScenPart_ScatterThingsAnywhere">
		  <def>ScatterThingsAnywhere</def>
		  <visible>false</visible>
		  <thingDef>ShipWreck</thingDef>
		  <count>1</count>
		</li>
      </parts>
    </scenario>
  </ScenarioDef>
    	

  
</Defs>
