<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Defs>
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef Abstract="true" Name="UpdateFeatureBase">
		<modNameReadable>Real Ruins</modNameReadable>
		<modIdentifier>RealRuins</modIdentifier>
		<linkUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1552146295</linkUrl>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
	
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>RealRuins_1_2_0</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>1.2.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>
&lt;i&gt;Hint 1: You can leave ruins event moving your pawns to a green area on map's edge.
Hint 2: You can use right mouse button to pick up any stuff while looting abandoned base. You can also load your caravan animals the same way.&lt;/i&gt;
|&lt;b&gt;Major changes&lt;/b&gt;
|1) In this version you can't instantly reform caravan between raids during the abandoned base event.
That's what you need the hints above for. On my opinion, during this encounter you should manually explore the ruins, find any valuable stuff, pick it up and leave before another hostile party arrives. From now on you won't be able to leave automatically after defeating initial defenders, picking goods lazily from the list. From now on, pick up all valuables and move to the map's edge.
Ok, you can actually revert to the old way in mod settings, but I won't recommend.
|2) Now contents of graves and cryptosleep pods are captured and spawned.
So if you open a cryptosleep pod and find a fatally infected colonist, you can be sure: it's the same colonist as in blueprint source game. And he still has been waiting for a healing serum since long time ago. The mod saves name, appearance, stats, health condition, traits and apparel, and so on (but not an entire pawn, it's still too much info). Also this feature works with corpses laying around and in general, with any containers and their contents.
&lt;i&gt;But please note that this will work only for newly captured blueprints, so you probably won't notice anything at first, until the server gets enough new blueprints. And you should probably clear your cache after a week and force loading some data to increase probability of getting additional content.&lt;/i&gt;
|&lt;b&gt;Minor changes&lt;/b&gt;
- Replaced most of collapsed rocks with various walls
- Dates of all events (including those in art objects) are now consistent across one ruins piece and are always earlier than current date
- During most encounters hostile units won't spawn near map's edge, so you can enter relatively safely
- Fires and torches are not spawned in ruins
- Separate settings for minimum and maximum ruins piece radius
- Added ability to reset mod settings to defaults
- Now you're not able to claim active turrets during abandoned base encounter
- Weapon shelves and other storages are spawned with the lowest storage priority possible, so your pawn won't run across the map to store your weapons
- Doors and locks compatibility checked
- Fixed bug with ruins placed on water
- Now mod tends to load more recent maps
- Rebalanced deterioration (now objects most likely won't lose more than 300-500 hit points, so no more "23 of 350000 hit-points" beta-poly walls)
- Fixed crash on exit
- Speed up loading (for me the game takes the same 70 seconds to load as before, but probably it will help for those who report 40 minutes loading)
		</content>                                 
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>RealRuins_1_2_1</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>1.2.1</assemblyVersion>
		<content>
Quick fixes of some annoying ruins event bugs.
		</content>                                 
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

</Defs>