<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<LanguageData>

<BeefMeat.label>Говядина</BeefMeat.label>
<BeefMeat.description>Beef is a category of meat that comes from bovine-like animals. Domestic Cows, Muffalo and Alphamuffalo produce Beef when butchered. Beef is a tender, lean meat with a decent fat content. It makes for good roasts and steaks.</BeefMeat.description>

<DogMeat.label>Собачье мясо</DogMeat.label>
<DogMeat.description>Dog Meat is a fatty, protein rich meat from breeds of canines. Labradror Retrievers, Yorkshire Terriers, Rimdogs, Rimwolves, Furxes, Samoyed, Border Collies, German Shepherds, Huskies and Wargs are canines.</DogMeat.description>

<HumanMeat.label>Человеческая плоть</HumanMeat.label>
<HumanMeat.description>This is the soft flesh of a Human that was butchered. You would have to be a Psychopath to want to butcher humans without remorse. A Cannibal would find this flesh a delicate treat to eat.</HumanMeat.description>

<NarnMeat.label>Плоть Нарна</NarnMeat.label>
<NarnMeat.description>This is the soft flesh of a Narn that was butchered. You would have to be a Psychopath to want to butcher humans without remorse. A Cannibal would find this flesh an exquisite treat to eat.</NarnMeat.description>

<NorbalMeat.label>Норбальская плоть</NorbalMeat.label>
<NorbalMeat.description>This is the soft flesh of a Norbal that was butchered. You would have to be a Psychopath to want to butcher humans without remorse. A Cannibal would find this flesh a superb treat to eat.</NorbalMeat.description>

<NovaMeat.label>Плоть Новы</NovaMeat.label>
<NovaMeat.description>This is the soft flesh of a Nova that was butchered. You would have to be a Psychopath to want to butcher humans without remorse. A Cannibal would find this flesh a splendid treat to eat.</NovaMeat.description>

<InsectoidMeat.label>Мясо инсектоидов</InsectoidMeat.label>
<InsectoidMeat.description>This is greasy, oily and squishy meat of insectoid-type creatures. It doesn't look too appealing. This meat comes from butchered Antis, Crashbug, Feralisk, Flea, Fly, Gnawler, Megascarab, Mosquito, Scorpion, Spindlecrib, Tarantula and Terramorph.</InsectoidMeat.description>

<PorkMeat.label>Свинина</PorkMeat.label>
<PorkMeat.description>Pork is the meat category from pig-like animals. It is fatty, rich in protein and high in cholesterol. Pork chops, roasts and bacon are common meal items. Domestic Pigs, Wild Boars and Quadhogs produce Pork when butchered.</PorkMeat.description>

<BirdMeat.label>Курятина</BirdMeat.label>
<BirdMeat.description>This is the tender, raw flesh of a bird. Chickens produce poultry when butchered. It is said that everything tastes like Chicken, but many meat-loving consumers would disagree.</BirdMeat.description>

<ReptileMeat.label>Мясо рептилии</ReptileMeat.label>
<ReptileMeat.description>This is the tough muscle meat belonging to a reptilian creature. Cobra, Iguana, Lacosdile and Tortoise produce Reptile Meat when butchered.</ReptileMeat.description>

<RodentMeat.label>Мясо грызуна</RodentMeat.label>
<RodentMeat.description>This is the raw meat of a rodent-like animal. Alphabeavers, Chinchillas, Capybaras, Hares, Hedgehogs, Squirrels</RodentMeat.description>

<VenisonMeat.label>Оленина</VenisonMeat.label>
<VenisonMeat.description>Venison is a category of very lean meats from game animals. Alpaca, Deer, Dromedary and Elk produce Venison when butchered. This meat is great when cooked into Jerky.</VenisonMeat.description>

<ElephantMeat.label>Мясо слона</ElephantMeat.label>
<ElephantMeat.description>This is the soft, raw flesh of a Elephant.</ElephantMeat.description>

<FeatheredRaptorMeat.label>Мясо пернатого раптора</FeatheredRaptorMeat.label>
<FeatheredRaptorMeat.description>This is the soft, rare, exotic flesh of a Feathered Raptor.</FeatheredRaptorMeat.description>

<FeenixMeat.label>Мясо феникса</FeenixMeat.label>
<FeenixMeat.description>This is the soft, raw flesh of a Feenix.</FeenixMeat.description>

<FenrirMeat.label>Мясо Фенрира</FenrirMeat.label>
<FenrirMeat.description>This is the soft, raw flesh of a Fenrir.</FenrirMeat.description>

<IcicatMeat.label>Мясо ледяного кота</IcicatMeat.label>
<IcicatMeat.description>This is the soft, raw flesh of an Icicat.</IcicatMeat.description>

<LionMeat.label>Мясо льва</LionMeat.label>
<LionMeat.description>This is the soft, raw flesh of a Lion.</LionMeat.description>

<MonkeyMeat.label>Мясо обезьяны</MonkeyMeat.label>
<MonkeyMeat.description>This is the soft, raw flesh of a Monkey.</MonkeyMeat.description>

<RhinocerosMeat.label>Мясо носорога</RhinocerosMeat.label>
<RhinocerosMeat.description>This is the soft, raw flesh of a Rhinoceros.</RhinocerosMeat.description>

<MuttonMeat.label>Баранина</MuttonMeat.label>
<MuttonMeat.description>This is the soft, raw flesh of a Rimram.</MuttonMeat.description>

<SnorkMeat.label>Мясо снорка</SnorkMeat.label>
<SnorkMeat.description>This is the soft, blubbery raw flesh of a Snork.</SnorkMeat.description>

<ThrumboMeat.label>Мясо трумбо</ThrumboMeat.label>
<ThrumboMeat.description>This is the soft, raw flesh of a Thrumbo.</ThrumboMeat.description>

</LanguageData>