<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<LanguageData>

	<SkynetAgentLabel>Skynet Agent</SkynetAgentLabel>
	<SkynetAgentDesc> has been exposed as a Skynet agent!</SkynetAgentDesc>
	<TerminatorName>Terminator</TerminatorName>
	<StatusLab>Status: </StatusLab>
	<StatusReactor>Reactor: </StatusReactor>
	<StatusBattery>Charge: </StatusBattery>
	<RegenerationEnabled>Active recovery.</RegenerationEnabled>
	<ReactorInDanger>Reactor in danger.</ReactorInDanger>
	<ReactorDestroying>Reactor destruction.</ReactorDestroying>
	<fulllevel>No Damage</fulllevel>
	<damagedlevel>Detected damage.</damagedlevel>
	<dangerlevel>Danger level of damage.</dangerlevel>
	<Critlevel>Сritical level of damage.</Critlevel>
	<overheatDanger>Overheating.</overheatDanger>
	<LeakingRate>Coolant loss</LeakingRate>
	<coolantLossDanger>Coolant loss.</coolantLossDanger>
	<AgentChasedTitle>Joining terminator to our group</AgentChasedTitle>
	<AgentChasedInitial>I am the {0}, machine of the future. We've been fighting a long time. I was recruited by you and sent here to protect you. Soon it will be the first Skynet attack. Machines more than us. But the power of the human spirit can not be measured. \n\nThe most important thing we can do right now is stay alive. In here and in here. All right? Just stay alive. You have no idea how important you are, and how important you will become. The machines are advancing even faster than I told you they would. I've seen it with my own eyes. They're inventing new Terminators, new ways of killing us. Skynet is planning something big. But the Resistance is planning something bigger. Skynet's a machine, and like all machines it has an off switch. If you're listening to this, you are the Resistance. \nI request permission to join your colony. \n\nDescription: {2}</AgentChasedInitial>
	<AgentChasedInitial_Accept>Agree</AgentChasedInitial_Accept>
	<AgentChasedRejected>I told you everything I know. Skynet is ruthless and unpredictable. They will use the best part of you against yourself. And they will have methods I can't imagine or predict that I can't help you with. And when you're unsure, well, just always follow your heart. Good luck and goodbye...</AgentChasedRejected>
	<AgentChasedInitial_Reject>Disagree</AgentChasedInitial_Reject>
	<transformationLabel>Transform</transformationLabel>
	<transformationDesc>This terminator type may acquire form the nearest dead or alive humanoids. Not able to take the form of other humanoids, such as Asari.</transformationDesc>
	<AgentKilled>My time is coming to an end. It was known to us. We sent another machine to protect you, you need to hold out for some time without my help. I told you everything I know. Skynet is ruthless and unpredictable. They will use the best part of you against yourself. And they will have methods I can't imagine or predict that I can't help you with. And when you're unsure, well, just always follow your heart. Good luck. I'll be back...</AgentKilled>
	<MachinelikeHibernate>Hibernate {0}</MachinelikeHibernate>
	<MachinelikeHibernateFail>{0} can't hibernate. Is not capable.</MachinelikeHibernateFail>
	<MachinelikeHibernateFailNoPower>{0} can't hibernate at {1} due to no power.</MachinelikeHibernateFailNoPower>
	<MachinelikeHibernateFailReserveOrReach>{0} can't reserve or reach {1}.</MachinelikeHibernateFailReserveOrReach>
	
</LanguageData>
