<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Defs>

  <TipSetDef>
    <defName>ZF_MineralsTips</defName>
    <tips>
      <li>Granite is the hardest common stone, but is also the hardest to mine.</li>
      <li>Slate sometimes yields natraully rectangular blocks that can be used for building without stonecutting.</li>
      <li>Marble is a beautiful and relatively hard stone, but does not yield many chunks.</li>
      <li>Sandstone is a beautiful and somewhat soft stone that yields lots of stone chunks.</li>
      <li>Limestone is a somewhat hard stone that yields lots of stone chunks.</li>
      <li>Basalt is a hard stone, but is not very attrative. Basalt terrain is often covered in lava flows.</li>
      <li>Claystone and mudstone are very soft and easily mined, but dont yield chunks that can be cut into blocks.</li>
      <li>Some stone types results in landscapes with more natural cover in a gunfight than others.</li>
      <li>Cut gems are a valuable and lightweight currency.</li>
      <li>Some of the most valuable minerals like diamonds and rubies are embedded into stone floors and are easy to overlook.</li>
      <li>Glowstone and coldstone crystals spawn and grow under certian natural conditions. Perhaps you can replicate these conditions...</li>
      <li>Salt forms from evaporating sea water in warm and dry climates.</li>
      <li>Sulfur forms near gysers and volcanic activity.</li>
      <li>Rare giant crystals and large fossils can be extracted and reinstalled in your base as a decoration or put in your laboratory for a small research boost.</li>
      <li>The most valuable minerals can typically only be found away from settlements or in extreme biomes.</li>
      <li>Some rocks like dunite and pegmatite are only found as chunks in other rocks and can be used to make blocks to make very attractive or durable buildings.</li>
      <li>The amount of resources gained by mining depends on mining skill and the size of the thing being mined.</li>
      <li>Some resources can only be identified extracted by more experienced miners.</li>
    </tips>
  </TipSetDef>
  
</Defs>
