<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
    <name>ZB333ZB's Patches</name>
    <author>ZB333ZB</author>
    <supportedVersions>
        <li>1.4</li>
    </supportedVersions>
    <packageId>ZB333ZB.patches</packageId>
    <loadAfter>
        <li>brrainz.harmony</li>
        <li>haplo.miscellaneous.robots</li>
        <li>kentington.saveourship2</li>
        <li>linkolas.linkabledoors</li>
        <li>jecrell.doorsexpanded</li>
        <li>avius.locks</li>
        <li>skyarkhangel.HSK</li>
        <li>Dubwise.DubsBadHygiene</li>
        <li>Dubwise.Rimefeller</li>
        <li>multilangcolorfultraits.pirateby</li>
        <li>LWM.DeepStorage</li>
        <li>falconne.BWM</li>
    </loadAfter>
    <description><![CDATA[<color=#d3c87a><size=24>[RU]</size></color>

<color=#d37a86><size=20>Сборник патчей</size></color>

<color=#7ab2d3>ApplyToAllDoors</color>: в настройках дверного замка добавляет кнопку, которая позволяет применить настройки из текущего таба для всех дверей колонии

<color=#7AB2D3>AutoRebuildTerrainOnSeismicActivity</color>: разрушаемый terrain при Seismic Activity теперь ставиться на автопостройку. Для эффекта должна быть активна галка Автопостройка и terrain находиться в домашней зоне

<color=#7AB2D3>EnhancedDefSelector</color>: заменяет лаганый список доступных def в виде floatmenu в редакторе сценария на фиксированное окно со встроенным списком

<color=#7AB2D3>StorageSelector</color>: в Bill Config Dialogue поддержка DeepStorage storages на равне со stockpiles. Заменяет ванильные кнопки "Взять из" и "Отнести на" на кастомные. Добавляет попап окно со встроенным поиском для выбора из доступных storages/stockpiles. Tooltip над каждым storage/stockpile в списке позволяет узнать их метрики. StorageSelector видет все stockpiles/storages независимо от их фильтров на предметы. В случае несоответствия фильтров target storage и bill's продукции пешка кладет продукцию на пол. Присутствуют сообщения, уведомляющие игрока о подобных случаях.

Интегрирован <color=#7AB2D3>What's Missing</color> мод от Revolus (Steam Workshop: h͟t͟t͟p͟s͟:͟/͟/͟s͟t͟e͟a͟m͟c͟o͟m͟m͟u͟n͟i͟t͟y͟.͟c͟o͟m͟/͟s͟h͟a͟r͟e͟d͟f͟i͟l͟e͟s͟/͟f͟i͟l͟e͟d͟e͟t͟a͟i͟l͟s͟/͟?͟i͟d͟=͟2͟0͟7͟3͟0͟8͟2͟7͟4͟7͟):
<color=#a7bda7>
"Highlighted requirements and tooltips for recipe descriptions.

When a recipe has many ingredients, it's quite annoing to lookup what's missing. This mod tells you everything you need to know the first glance. Or at least it tells you a lot."</color>

Интеграция была необходима для обеспечения корректного отображения UI в Bill Config Dialog, так как оба мода модифицируют один и тот же интерфейс.

<color=#7AB2D3>ToggleDBHGridsPatch</color>: добавляет WidgetRow иконку для отображения сеток воды из Dubs Bad Hygiene. Отображение глубокой воды требует изучения соответствующей технологии

<color=#7AB2D3>ToggleRimefellerGridsPatch</color>: добавляет WidgetRow иконку для отображения сеток нефти из Rimefeller. Отображение каждой из сеток требует изучения соответствующей технологии

<color=#d3c87a><size=24>[EN]</size></color>

<color=#d37a86><size=20>A collection of patches</size></color>

<color=#7ab2d3>ApplyToAllDoors</color>: adds a button in door lock settings that allows applying settings from the current tab to all colony doors

<color=#7AB2D3>AutoRebuildTerrainOnSeismicActivity</color>: destroyed terrain during Seismic Activity is now set for auto-rebuild. For this to work, Auto-rebuild must be enabled and terrain must be in home zone

<color=#7AB2D3>EnhancedDefSelector</color>: replaces the laggy float menu list of available defs in the scenario editor with a fixed window with built-in list

<color=#7AB2D3>StorageSelector</color>: adds DeepStorage support in Bill Config Dialogue on par with stockpiles. Replaces vanilla "Take from" and "Deliver to" buttons with custom ones. Adds a popup window with built-in search for selecting from available storages/stockpiles. Tooltip over each storage/stockpile in the list shows their metrics. StorageSelector sees all stockpiles/storages regardless of their item filters. In case of mismatch between target storage filters and bill's products, pawn drops products on the floor. Messages are present to notify player about such cases.

Integrated <color=#7AB2D3>What's Missing</color> mod by Revolus (Steam Workshop: h͟t͟t͟p͟s͟:͟/͟/͟s͟t͟e͟a͟m͟c͟o͟m͟m͟u͟n͟i͟t͟y͟.͟c͟o͟m͟/͟s͟h͟a͟r͟e͟d͟f͟i͟l͟e͟s͟/͟f͟i͟l͟e͟d͟e͟t͟a͟i͟l͟s͟/͟?͟i͟d͟=͟2͟0͟7͟3͟0͟8͟2͟7͟4͟7͟):
<color=#a7bda7>
"Highlighted requirements and tooltips for recipe descriptions.

When a recipe has many ingredients, it's quite annoing to lookup what's missing. This mod tells you everything you need to know the first glance. Or at least it tells you a lot."</color>

Integration was necessary to ensure correct UI rendering in Bill Config Dialog, as both mods modify the same interface.

<color=#7AB2D3>ToggleDBHGridsPatch</color>: adds a WidgetRow icon to display water grids from Dubs Bad Hygiene. Deep water grid display requires researching the corresponding technology

<color=#7AB2D3>ToggleRimefellerGridsPatch</color>: adds a WidgetRow icon to display oil grids from Rimefeller. Display of each grid requires researching the corresponding technology]]></description>
</ModMetaData>
