<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Defs>
	
	<!--===================== Concepts taught through the learning readout, when opportunities arise ===================-->

	<ConceptDef>
		<defName>ReformCaravan</defName>
		<label>Reforming caravans</label>
		<priority>50</priority>
		<needsOpportunity>True</needsOpportunity>
		<helpText>After an encounter, you can easily re-form a caravan by using the RE-FORM CARAVAN command in the World view.</helpText>
		<highlightTags>
			<li>MainTab-World-Closed</li>
			<li>ReformCaravan</li>
		</highlightTags>
	</ConceptDef>

	<ConceptDef>
    <defName>Rescuing</defName>
    <label>Rescuing</label>
    <priority>50</priority>
    <needsOpportunity>True</needsOpportunity>
    <helpText>To rescue a wounded person, select a healthy colonist and then right-click on the wounded one.\n\nIf you rescue a non-colonist, they won't necessarily join your colony. They may simply walk away after healing. If you want to guarantee that they join, capture them and recruit them.</helpText>
  </ConceptDef>

  <ConceptDef>
    <defName>Capturing</defName>
    <label>Capturing</label>
    <priority>50</priority>
    <needsOpportunity>True</needsOpportunity>
    <helpText>When an enemy is downed on the ground but not dead, you can CAPTURE them.\n\nTo capture, select a colonist, right-click on the incapacitated enemy, and select Capture.\n\nYou'll need an extra bed marked for prisoner use.</helpText>
  </ConceptDef>

  <ConceptDef>
    <defName>ShieldBelts</defName>
    <label>Shield belts</label>
    <priority>50</priority>
    <needsOpportunity>True</needsOpportunity>
    <helpText>Shield belts stop ranged attacks from coming in or out. They have no effect on melee attacks.\n\nTo fight against shield belts, either concentrate a lot of gunfire on the target, or fight hand-to-hand.</helpText>
  </ConceptDef>
  
  <ConceptDef>
    <defName>InteractingWithTraders</defName>
    <label>Interacting with traders</label>
    <priority>50</priority>
    <needsOpportunity>True</needsOpportunity>
    <helpText>You can talk to people with ? over their heads.\n\nSelect a colonist and right-click on the character with ? attached to his head.</helpText>
  </ConceptDef>

  <ConceptDef>
    <defName>Drafting</defName>
    <label>Drafting for combat</label>
    <priority>50</priority>
    <needsOpportunity>True</needsOpportunity>
    <highlightTags>
      <li>Draft</li>
    </highlightTags>
    <helpText>To control colonists directly for combat, Draft them by selecting them and hitting the DRAFT button.\n\nA drafted colonist will do only what you tell them, and can only take combat actions. Those with weapons will use them when possible.\n\nDon't leave colonists Drafted forever - they'll starve and become unhappy.</helpText>
  </ConceptDef>
    
  <ConceptDef>
    <defName>BuildOrbitalTradeBeacon</defName>
    <label>Build orbital trade beacon</label>
    <priority>50</priority>
    <needsOpportunity>True</needsOpportunity>
    <helpText>To send items or silver to orbital traders, you must build an ORBITAL TRADE BEACON and place a stockpile of items near it.</helpText>
    <highlightTags>
      <li>MainTab-Architect-Closed</li>
      <li>DesignationCategoryButton-Misc-Closed</li>
      <li>Designator-Build-OrbitalTradeBeacon</li>
    </highlightTags>
  </ConceptDef>
  
  <ConceptDef>
    <defName>AnimalsDontAttackDoors</defName>
    <label>Animals don't attack doors</label>
    <priority>50</priority>
    <needsOpportunity>True</needsOpportunity>
    <helpText>Manhunting animals generally won't attack doors or inactive turrets.\n\nYou can escape them by getting inside or behind a wall. But they'll wait for you.</helpText>
  </ConceptDef>

	<ConceptDef>
    <defName>BillsTab</defName>
    <label>Bills tab</label>
    <needsOpportunity>true</needsOpportunity>
    <opportunityDecays>false</opportunityDecays>
    <priority>50</priority>
    <highlightTags>
      <li>ITab-Bills-Closed</li>
    </highlightTags>
    <helpText>To make colonists work at a table, select the table and open the Bills tab. Here, you can say what meals to cook, what things to craft, what creatures to butcher.</helpText>
  </ConceptDef>

  <ConceptDef>
    <defName>OpeningComms</defName>
    <label>Using the comms console</label>
    <priority>50</priority>
    <needsOpportunity>True</needsOpportunity>
    <helpText>To communicate, select a colonist and right-click on the comms console.</helpText>
  </ConceptDef>

  <ConceptDef>
    <defName>DrugAddiction</defName>
    <label>Drug addiction</label>
    <needsOpportunity>true</needsOpportunity>
    <priority>50</priority>
    <highlightTags>
      <li>ITab-Needs-Closed</li>
    </highlightTags>
    <helpText>You can inspect your colonists' desire to take a drug in their Needs tab.\n\nAs long as their need level is at zero, their addiction changes to a "withdrawal" state which can have various negative side effects.\n\nHowever, after long enough in withdrawal, their addiction will end and the drug need will disappear.</helpText>
  </ConceptDef>

  <ConceptDef>
    <defName>DrugPolicies</defName>
    <label>Drug policies</label>
    <priority>50</priority>
    <helpText>You can assign colonists to take specific drugs on a specific schedule. For example, you can make them take infection-blocking drugs regularly, or drink a beer a day to stay happy.\n\nOpen the ASSIGN tab and press the 'Manage drug policies' button. Create a new drug policy. Then, you can assign this policy to colonists.\n\nColonists can still take drugs not in their policy. You can tell them what to do, but they also follow their own desires!</helpText>
    <needsOpportunity>true</needsOpportunity>
    <highlightTags>
      <li>MainTab-Assign-Closed</li>
      <li>ManageDrugPolicies</li>
    </highlightTags>
  </ConceptDef>

  <ConceptDef>
    <defName>TVForSickPeople</defName>
    <label>TV for sick people</label>
    <priority>50</priority>
    <needsOpportunity>true</needsOpportunity>
    <helpText>Sick people can watch TV while laying in bed.</helpText>
  </ConceptDef>

  <ConceptDef>
    <defName>PrisonerTab</defName>
    <label>Prisoner tab</label>
    <priority>50</priority>
    <needsOpportunity>True</needsOpportunity>
    <highlightTags>
      <li>ITab-Prisoner-Closed</li>
    </highlightTags>
    <helpText>Look in a prisoner's 'Prisoner' tab to set how they'll be treated.\n\nYou can set whether they'll be recruited, ignored or executed, whether they eat, and what kind of medical care they get.\n\nColonists with the Warden work type will interact with the prisoner.</helpText>
  </ConceptDef>

  <ConceptDef>
    <defName>SetGrowingZonePlant</defName>
    <label>Set what plant to grow</label>
    <priority>50</priority>
    <needsOpportunity>true</needsOpportunity>
    <opportunityDecays>false</opportunityDecays>
    <helpText>You can set what to plant in a growing zone. You can even grow trees!\n\nJust select the growing zone, open the Growing tab, and click the 'plant' button.</helpText>
    <highlightTags>
      <li>GrowingZoneSetPlant</li>
    </highlightTags>
  </ConceptDef>

  <ConceptDef>
    <defName>DrugBurning</defName>
    <label>Drug burning</label>
    <priority>50</priority>
    <helpText>Drugs can be useful, but can also lead to harmful addictions.\n\nIf you want to avoid drugs in your colony, you have the option of burning them at a campfire.</helpText>
    <needsOpportunity>true</needsOpportunity>
    <highlightTags>
      <li>DesignationCategoryButton-Temperature-Closed</li>
      <li>Designator-Build-Campfire</li>
      <li>ITab-Bills-Closed</li>
    </highlightTags>
  </ConceptDef>

	<ConceptDef>
		<defName>DoorOpenSpeed</defName>
		<label>Door opening speeds</label>
		<priority>50</priority>
		<helpText>Doors open at different speeds depending on what they're made of.\n\nWarning: Stone doors open very slowly. Anyone passing through will be significantly slowed down.</helpText>
		<needsOpportunity>true</needsOpportunity>
	</ConceptDef>

  <ConceptDef>
    <defName>QueueOrders</defName>
    <label>Order queueing</label>
    <priority>50</priority>
    <helpText>When giving commands to pawns, you can queue up multiple orders by holding "shift". This also works when giving jobs to undrafted pawns.</helpText>
    <needsOpportunity>true</needsOpportunity>
  </ConceptDef>

</Defs>
