<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<ModMetaData>
  <packageId>CrashM.ColorCodedMoodBar.11</packageId>
  <name>CM Color Coded Mood Bar [1.1+]</name>
  <author>CrashM</author>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.1</li>
    <li>1.2</li>
    <li>1.3</li>
    <li>1.4</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <description>Color code each pawn's mood bar within the colonist bar based on their current mood.\n\nRed: extreme mental break threshold\nOrange: major mental break threshold\nYellow: minor mental break threshold\nGray: neutral mood\nLight Blue: content\nGreen: happy\n\nAlso includes:\n\nBreak Box, an outline to highlight when the colonist is in a break mood, useful for "larger" colonists (default on). This can be drawn beneath or on top of the colonist to further highlight the colonist (default beneath).\nSchedule Box, an outline to show the colonists current schedule (default off).\nIllness Icon, an icon that is displayed when the colonist has an illness that requires immunity (default on).\nBleeding Icon, an icon that is displayed when the colonist is bleeding with 3 different sizes based on bleed rate, Large lt 8 hours until death, Medium lt 24 hours, Small gt 24 hours (default on).\nThermal Icons, icons for when colonists are suffereing hypotherma/heatstroke (minor and above).\n\nUpdates:\n\nPorqueNoLosDos:\n24-09-2017: Removed unnecessary error log messages.\n18-11-2017: Updated for RimWord version 0.18.1722, and added content and happy mood colors.\n04-05-2019: Updated for RimWorld version 1.0.2231.\n\nCrashM:\n24-02-2020: Updated for RimWorld version 1.1 (1.1 only, won't work on 1.0), and made it better reflect break thresholds.\n27-02-2020: Added outline box for break risks as previously extreme had such a small bar it was usually not visible.\n29-02-2020: Added Mod Settings to allow changing the color of each threshold and disable the mental break outline box if needed.\n01-03-2020: Fixed memory leak.\n04-04-2020: Added option to put the break box on top of the colonist (default off) so it is more visible for the larger colonists.\n15-06-2020: Added optional neutral break box (default off).\n28-07-2020: Added Optional Schedule Box to show colonists current schedule.\n04-09-2020: Added optional illness icon for illnesses that require immunity.\n05-09-2020: Added optional bleeding icon with 3 sizes based on bleed rate.\n15-09-2020: Performance updates and caching. I have improved performance by an average of 25% over the previous version (test has 20 colonists, same settings), I also removed the schedule box for when colonists are on the Anything schedule as this also helps performance. There is also a new Refresh Rate setting where you can decide how often the cache is refreshed (150ms seems more than enough for 20 colonists, 0 disables the cache).\n23-09-2020: More performance improvements. Please note, the performance improvement has made the cache mandatory, if this causes problems please let me know.\n27-09-2020: Bug Fix (error when enabling schedule box when in game), Added optional ability to hide portraits (helps performance).\n27-09-2020: Bug Fix.\n01-10-2020: Extended the allowed caching to 2s, and made the selection highlighting uncached.\n24-10-2020: More performance improvements (removed some reflection).\n25-10-2020: Bug Fix + Another performance improvement that make it faster than vanilla.\n25-10-2020: Bug Fix + Minor performance improvments + the bleeding icon now flashes when lt 3 hours + the illness icon will flash when severity gt immunity and severity gt 80% + the illness icon will turn yellow when immunity gt severity + the illness icon will turn green when immunity gt %5 more than severity.\n20-12-2020: Bug fix + An optional (disabled by default) alternative label that is faster but may have bugs + Thermal warning icons (colors customisable in the settings).\n27-03-2021: Added proper tooltips to the settings.\n06-04-2021: Additional Performance Improvment when enabling the Alternative Label in the settings.\n09-04-2021: Bug Fix\n23-04-2021: Added an option to force a portrait update when colonists drafted status changes (as requested by Deco)\n05-07-2021: 1.3 Compatibility\n07-07-2021: Fixed Problem with RW1.2 loading the 1.3 dll.\n23-07-2021: Ideology Update\n24-07-2021: Fixed Settings\n28-07-2021: 1.3.3074.1: Added a Version Number to help prevent issues with old versions being used. It will be included in the initialisation message in the games log and the mod settings.\n15-08-2021: 1.3.3087.1: Fixed compatibility issue with QEE by Mario55770\n18-08-2021: 1.3.3094.1: Added Compatability with Colony Groups, please note this is a work in progress so some things might be weird or broken.\n20-08-2021: 1.3.3096.1: Bug Fix\n25-08-2021: 1.3.3102.1: Fixed thermal icon still showing after death.\n16-09-2021: 1.3.3117.1: Additional compatibility with Colony Groups (fixed issues with pawn/box sizes).\n18-09-2021: 1.3.3117.2: Added optional Gender icon.\n30-09-2021: 1.3.3136.1: Added optional Cryptosleep Icon.\n18-07-2022: 1.3.3389.1: Added Compatibility for Pawn Badges and Job In Bar when used in combination with Colony Groups.\n06-10-2022: 1.4.3509.1: Update for Rimworld 1.4.</description>
  <modDependencies>
    <li>
      <packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
      <displayName>Harmony</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
      <downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
    </li>
  </modDependencies>
  <loadAfter>
	<li>DerekBickley.LTOColonyGroupsFinal</li>
	<li>SaucyPigeon.PawnBadge</li>
	<li>Dark.JobInBar</li>
  </loadAfter>
</ModMetaData>