<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>Rumours And Deception</name>
  <author>SeveralPuffins</author>
  <targetVersion>0.18.0000</targetVersion>
  <description>Have you ever wondered why your colonists don't talk about each other? Did no-one wonder about sending that shifty cannibal Alex to bury the dead? How come Ray likes the abrasive psycho that beat up her friend, just because she's never been insulted directly? And why is no-one ever apologetic about anything they've done?

If you want more social complexity, or just plain gossip and intrigue in your stories, then look no further! Rumours and Deception adds several new colonist social interactions, traits and thoughts that largely focus on people talking about people. 

New interactions:
- Chat about other colonists: Alice likes Bob. Bob hates Carol. Bob can now tell Alice this!
- Spread rumour: Colonists will tell nasty, unsubstantiated tales to each other, particularly about colonists that neither of them like.
- Share secret: A colonist can trust another enough to reveal something deep and personal, bringing them closer together.
- Reveal secret: There's no guarantee that all trust is well placed! Colonists that have been told a secret can go and gossip about it to their friends!
- Apologise: Colonists can try to make up with others that they've insulted or hurt.
- Make peace: Colonists may try and apologise on behalf of a third party.
- Culture clash: Not all insults are intended! One may insult another due to having a poor understanding of their background culture (for example, Tribal vs GlitterWorld culture clashes).


New traits:
- Compulsive liar: This colonist just can't help it- every conversation is an opportunity to make up some new, snide story about one of the others.
- Gushing: This colonist just cannot judge who to trust with their darkest secrets, exposing themselves to potential embarrassment.
- Gossip: This colonist talks about other people all the time. This extends to secrets, with which they can't be trusted.
- Manipulative: This colonist will use any social trick they know to make other people see things THEIR way. They are great negotiators, but can be divisive and isolating within a colony.
- Trustworthy: This colonist keeps secrets. They rarely spread rumours, and if they do they feel terrible about it.
- Peacemaker: This colonist can't stand to see their friends fighting. They will try to resolve other people's differences, and will get a mood boost if successful.

New events:
- Defection: A socially isolated colonist will suffer mood penalties and very regular mental breaks. If they remain friendless, they may, occasionally, walk off the map and join an ally (currently suspended while HugsLib updates).
- Brawl:    Even if cliques don't leave, they may still start fights!

[Russian]
 
Мод добавляет больше социальных аспектов в вашу колонию. Новые взаимодействия между колонистами — слухи, обман, истории, интриги и тд. Также добавлены новые черты характера.

    Разговор между колонистами о других колонистах
    Распускание слухов
    Секреты
    Извинения за свои действия
    Извинения от лица другого колониста
    Разные верования (почва для конфликтов)

Новые события:

    Дефекция (Defection) — социальная изоляция колониста. Колонист может уйти или присоединится к другой колонии (союзной или врагов)
    Splinter — объединения колонистов по общим интересам. Есть вероятность, что колонисты решат сделать свою колонию и создать новую фракцию
    Массовые драки
    
Новые взаимодействия:
- Чат о других колонистах: Алисе нравится Боб. Боб ненавидит Кэрол. Теперь Боб может рассказать Алисе!
- Распространяйте слухи: колонисты расскажут о неприятных, необоснованных рассказах друг другу, особенно о колонистах, которых никто из них не любит.
- Поделитесь секретом: колонист может доверять другому, чтобы открыть что-то глубокое и личное, сближая их.
- Выяснить секрет: нет никакой гарантии, что все доверие будет хорошо размещено! Колонисты, которые были рассказаны в секрете, могут пойти и сплетничать об этом своим друзьям!
- Извиняйтесь: колонисты могут попытаться смириться с другими, оскорбляющими или обиженными.
- Помиритесь: колонисты могут попытаться извиниться от имени третьей стороны.
- Культурное столкновение: не все оскорбления предназначены! Можно оскорбить другого из-за плохого понимания их фоновой культуры (например, столкновения с Tribal vs GlitterWorld).


Новые черты:
- Навязчивый лжец: этот колонист просто не может с этим поделать - каждый разговор - это возможность составить новую, непристойную историю об одном из других.
- Болтун: Этот колонист просто не может судить, кому доверять свои самые темные секреты, подвергая себя потенциальному смущению.
- Сплетник: Этот колонист все время говорит о других людях. Это распространяется на секреты, с которыми им нельзя доверять.
- Манипулятор: этот колонист будет использовать любой трюк, который они знают, чтобы другие люди видели вещи ИХ. Они великие переговорщики, но могут делиться и изолироваться внутри колонии.
- Надежный: этот колонист хранит секреты. Они редко распространяют слухи, и если они чувствуют себя ужасно.
Миротворец: Этот колонист не может видеть, как их друзья сражаются. Они будут пытаться решать чужие разногласия и в случае успеха повысят настроение.

  </description>

</ModMetaData>
