<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Defs>
	<!-- Use either "\n" or XML whitespace return to make linebreaks; both method works -->

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef Abstract="true" Name="CommonSense_UpdateFeatureBase">
		<modNameReadable>Common Sense</modNameReadable>
		<modIdentifier>net.avilmask.rimworld.mod.CommonSense</modIdentifier>
		<linkUrl>https://github.com/catgirlfighter/RimWorld_CommonSense</linkUrl>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
	
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="CommonSense_UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>CS_1_0_0</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>1.0.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>Check, check. *Ahem* Greetings, %username%! Many of you use HugsLib, and it allows to make a change log visible in-game. So here it comes, for yours and slightly mine convenience. If you don't have HugsLib, you'll not even notice any difference, so don't worry about it.</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
	
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="CommonSense_UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>CS_1_0_13</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>1.0.13</assemblyVersion>
		<content>- Added an option to pick up ALL ingredients before hauling them to the crafting place. As usual, you can disable it from mod settings;
- fixed a possible issue with recreational drugs in inventory when "fulfilling outdoors" is triggered;
If you see pawns acting funny, don't mind to report your observations. "Hauling in between" and "hauling ALL before going to the crafting place" are two options that completely redo, how working on a bill works.</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
	
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="CommonSense_UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>CS_1_0_14</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>1.0.14</assemblyVersion>
		<content>- added an option to prefer faster spoiling ingredients for cooking. I can't really tell, how it impacts performance. If you think it causes a lag, you may disable it.</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="CommonSense_UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>CS_1_0_15</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>1.0.15</assemblyVersion>
		<content>- made "full recipe descriptions" for apparel simpler;
- added order optimization when a pawn is hauling ingredients for a recipe;
- optimized some things considering ingredients that was left in inventory if hauling was interrupted, but it's hardly noticeable.</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="CommonSense_UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>CS_1_0_16</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>1.0.16</assemblyVersion>
		<content>- fixed an error on trying to cut stone chunks. Sorry about that;
- added an option to unload an item from an inventory (to the closest stockpile, instead of dropping on the ground). Doesn't work with RPG Style (ATM), so probably most of you not gonna see that option anyway.</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
	
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="CommonSense_UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>CS_1_1_0</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>1.1.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>- added an option to unload equipped items;
- made an option for manual unloading optional;
- added compatibility patch for RPG Style Inventory;
- added an option for pawns to put items back in inventory when they get interrupted (ex. when you draft them during consumption of a meal in the middle of nowhere);
- added an option do prevent pawns from taking more sweets than they can eat;

This is probably the final changes to the mod. For now I've fulfilled all I wanted. I'll make some refactoring and optimization, but I'm out of further ideas for new features :)</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
	
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="CommonSense_UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>CS_1_1_1</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>1.1.1</assemblyVersion>
		<content>- added category to item's info;
- added prioritization of spoiling herbal medicine and corpses;
- added prioritization of spoiling food (to eat before it turns bad);
- removed unintentional duplicate in settings;</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
	
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="CommonSense_UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>CS_1_1_2</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>1.1.2</assemblyVersion>
		<content>- changed pawn priorities for sleeping schedule. Now they'll prioritize topping off joy need if they happen to wake up early;
- added an option to prevent colonists from taking joy activities if they're already topped of(after reaching 95%, they'll not start it again until it's down to 80%);</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="CommonSense_UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>CS_1_1_3</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>1.1.3</assemblyVersion>
		<content>- fixed a problem, when material of an item could change with "all components hauled together" on, because order of picking up could change due to path optimization (basically, whatever was closer to the pawn, it automatically become a main ingredient);</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
	
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="CommonSense_UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>CS_1_1_4</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>1.1.4</assemblyVersion>
		<content>- when recreating, colonists will prefer taking spare meals if they don't have one;
- fixed a problem, due to which colonists would prefer herbal medicine over any other when doing surgery;
- added a special patch for "dubs bad hygiene" that tweaks assignment priorities (pawns now will prefer to top off all needs during recreation and when not sleeping during sleeping assignment).</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="CommonSense_UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>CS_1_1_5</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>1.1.5</assemblyVersion>
		<content>- added some more checks for "random ingredients", to possibly remove any issues with unusual recipes;
- rearranged checks for opportunistic cleaning jobs to remove possibilities of pawns ignoring assignments in incapability;</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="CommonSense_UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>CS_1_1_6</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>1.1.6</assemblyVersion>
		<content>- when pawns unload inventory, their task actually get canceled midway if you unmark items or drop them;
- if you unmark items to unload, and pawn doesn't have enough space in inventory, that item is dropped on the ground;</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="CommonSense_UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>CS_1_1_12</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>1.1.12</assemblyVersion>
		<content>I'm sorry that fixes are kinda slow, but ATM I'm out of rimworld loop.
- made so doctors don't prioritize faster spoiling medicine for surgeries anymore;
- made so pawns, that require medical attention, don't do opportunistic cleaning errands;
- made so doctors don't clean after tending if their next job is also tending on a pawn that's in the same room or if it's an emergency (bleeding time &lt; 6 hours). Keep in mind that it DOESN'T change, how doctors chose their patients.
</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="CommonSense_UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>CS_1_1_22</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>1.1.22</assemblyVersion>
		<content>Updated for RimWorld 1.1! Now, that doesn't mean it works at least as good as before, because some things may be broken silently, without me knowing about it, so it may take a bit more time to fine tune everything.</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
</Defs>