<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<LanguageData>

	<LetterLabelNewElection>Election being held in {0}</LetterLabelNewElection>
	<LetterNewElection>A mayoral election is being held in {0}. Some colonists there have announced their candidacy.</LetterNewElection>
	<LetterLabelElectionHeld>Election underway in {0}</LetterLabelElectionHeld>
	<LetterElectionHeld>The election in {0} is now underway. The colony has selected a polling place from the available gathering spots, and colonists will go there to vote.</LetterElectionHeld>
	<LetterLabelElectionCandidate>Candidate: {0_labelShort}</LetterLabelElectionCandidate>
	<LetterElectionCandidate>{0_labelShort} is running for mayor of {1}. This is {0_possessive} platform:\n{2}</LetterElectionCandidate>
	<LetterLabelTieSettled>Election tie settled in favor of {0_labelShort}</LetterLabelTieSettled>
	<LetterTieSettled>The mayoral election resulted in a tie, and after a battle royale bickering match, {0} was the only one willing to continue arguing about it. The other candidates have withdrawn, leaving {0_objective} the victor.</LetterTieSettled>
	<LetterLabelElectionWon>Election won by {0_labelShort}</LetterLabelElectionWon>
	<LetterElectionWon>{0_labelShort} won the mayoral election at {1}. {0_pronoun} received {2} votes.\n\nAs a reminder, this was {0_possessive} platform:\n{3}\n\n{0_pronoun} will now receive visits from {0_possessive} constituents in {0_possessive} room if {0_pronoun} has one. If they have complaints, they will likely feel better after talking to {0_objective} if {0_pronoun} is good at talking to people and understanding their feelings. Having a beautiful room to meet them in won't hurt either.\n\nKeep a close eye on {0_objective}; {0_pronoun} has no one to complain to and bearing the burdens of an entire colony can be hard, especially if things are going badly.</LetterElectionWon>
	<LetterLabelFuneralPlanned>Funeral planned for {0}</LetterLabelFuneralPlanned>
	<LetterFuneralPlanned>{0_labelShort} has planned a funeral for {1_labelShort}. The service will be held on the {2}, at {3}h.</LetterFuneralPlanned>
	<LetterLabelFuneralStarted>Funeral service being held for {0}</LetterLabelFuneralStarted>
	<LetterFuneralStarted>{0_labelShort}'s funeral is underway. Your colonists may or may not attend depending on their relationship with {0}.</LetterFuneralStarted>
	<LetterLabelFuneralEnded>Funeral ended</LetterLabelFuneralEnded>
	<LetterFuneralEnded>The funeral for {0_labelShort} is over now.\n\nThe following people attended:\n{1}</LetterFuneralEnded>
	<LetterLabelPTSD>Stress trauma</LetterLabelPTSD>
	<LetterPTSD>{0_labelShort} has developed post-traumatic anxiety as a result of {0_possessive} mental break. Anxiety is a permanent condition, but can be treated to slowly reduce its severity to a manageable level and allow {0_possessive} to function normally. Any further mental breaks will worsen {0_possessive} anxiety.\n\nGlitterworld doctors are rumored to have cured mental illnesses like anxiety in their patients. If you get your hands on some ultratech medicine, an extremely skilled doctor may be able to use it to cure {0_labelShort}'s anxiety.</LetterPTSD>
	<LetterLabelDatePlanned>Date</LetterLabelDatePlanned>
	<LetterDatePlanned>{0_labelShort} has planned a date with {1_labelShort} for the {2} at hour {3}.\n\nDates may be cancelled for several reasons, most notably if either colonist is assigned to Work, or they are drafted, or otherwise incapacitated by injury or urgent colony business.\n\nIf the date is cancelled, both colonists will be unhappy. Colonists can also miss dates if they sleep through them. This will make the other colonist upset at them, but not cause a negative thought.</LetterDatePlanned>
	
	<!-- Replaced vanilla letters -->
	<LetterRejectedProposalPsychology>Depending on their personality, their mood and relationship will be affected.</LetterRejectedProposalPsychology>

</LanguageData>