<Defs>
  <ConceptDef>
    <defName>Concept_SimpleSidearmsBasic</defName>
    <label>SS: Sidearms</label>
    <priority>50</priority>
    <highlightTags>
      <li>SidearmList</li>
    </highlightTags>
    <helpText>Simple Sidearms\n\nIn order to equip weapons as sidearms, rightclick them and select the Equip as sidearm option.\n\nBy default, colonists will use whichever weapon type they are best skilled with or passionate about. Ranged weapon users will also switch to a melee weapon when engaged in close combat. This behaviour can be altered in the mod settings.</helpText>
  </ConceptDef>
  
  <ConceptDef>
    <defName>Concept_SidearmsDropping</defName>
    <label>SS: Dropping sidearms</label>
    <needsOpportunity>True</needsOpportunity>
    <priority>50</priority>
    <highlightTags>
      <li>SidearmInInventory</li>
    </highlightTags>
    <helpText>Sidearms with a gray background are currently in a colonists inventory and eligible for use. Right click to drop.</helpText>
  </ConceptDef>  
  
<ConceptDef>
    <defName>Concept_SidearmsMissing</defName>
    <label>SS: Missing sidearms</label>
    <needsOpportunity>True</needsOpportunity>
    <priority>50</priority>
    <highlightTags>
      <li>SidearmMissing</li>
    </highlightTags>
    <helpText>Sidearms with a dark purple background are currently missing from a colonists loadout. They will attempt to replace them at earliest opportunity, assuming any can be found. Right click to forget about the sidearm.</helpText>
  </ConceptDef>
  
  <ConceptDef>
    <defName>Concept_SimpleSidearmsPreference</defName>
    <label>SS: Weapon preference</label>
    <needsOpportunity>True</needsOpportunity>
    <priority>50</priority>
    <highlightTags>
      <li>SidearmPreferenceButton</li>
    </highlightTags>
    <helpText>Colonists can have sidearm use configured on an individual basis. The options are: \nUse ranged weapons\nUse weapons colonist is passionate about or skilled with \nUse melee weapons</helpText>
  </ConceptDef>
  
  <ConceptDef>
    <defName>Concept_SimpleSidearmsAdvancedRanged</defName>
    <label>SS: Advanced controls (ranged)</label>
    <needsOpportunity>True</needsOpportunity>
    <priority>50</priority>
    <highlightTags>
      <li>SidearmInInventoryRanged</li>
    </highlightTags>
    <helpText>Left click a carried ranged weapon to set it as the default ranged weapon. If the colonist weapon preference is set to ranged (or skill on a colonist more skilled with ranged weapons), this weapon will be what the colonist equips when not in active combat. It will also be used while hunting. \n\nClick a default ranged weapon again to force its use regardless of range/DPS. \n\nRight click to remove forced use/default status.</helpText>
  </ConceptDef>

  <ConceptDef>
    <defName>Concept_SimpleSidearmsAdvancedMelee</defName>
    <label>SS: Advanced controls (melee)</label>
    <needsOpportunity>True</needsOpportunity>
    <priority>50</priority>
    <highlightTags>
      <li>SidearmInInventoryMelee</li>
    </highlightTags>
    <helpText>Left click a carried melee weapon to set it as the preferred ranged weapon. The colonist will always use this weapon when weapon preference is set to melee (or skill on a colonist more skilled with melee weapons) and when forced into close combat. \n\nClick a preferred melee weapon again to force its use at all times. \n\nRight click to remove forced use/preference.</helpText>
  </ConceptDef>
  
  
  <ConceptDef>
    <defName>Concept_SimpleSidearmsAdvancedDrafted</defName>
    <label>SS: Advanced controls (drafted)</label>
    <needsOpportunity>True</needsOpportunity>
    <priority>50</priority>
    <highlightTags>
      <li>SidearmInInventory</li>
      <li>Draft</li>
    </highlightTags>
    <helpText>Left click a carried weapon while drafted to force its use until end of combat. \n\nNote that most changes to sidearm loadout require the pawn to not be drafted.</helpText>
  </ConceptDef>
  
  
  <ConceptDef>
    <defName>Concept_SimpleSidearmsLosingWeapons</defName>
    <label>SS: Losing weapons</label>
    <needsOpportunity>True</needsOpportunity>
    <priority>1</priority>
    <helpText>Depending on the settings, Simple Sidearms can cause colonists to drop their weapons in a variety of situations (default is attacks in melee). Don't worry - your colonists will retrieve their weapons after the fight. \n\nThis is a customizable feature - take a look in the mod settings dialog to learn more.</helpText>
  </ConceptDef>
  
  <ConceptDef>
    <defName>Concept_CEOverride</defName>
    <label>SS: CE patch</label>
    <needsOpportunity>True</needsOpportunity>
    <priority>1</priority>
    <helpText>Combat Extended is loaded. SimpleSidearms inventory management functionality is disabled.</helpText>
  </ConceptDef>
 
 </Defs>  