<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>A Dog Said...</name>
	<author>spoonshortage and kaptain_kavern</author>
	<url>https://ludeon.com/forums/index.php?topic=24578.0</url>
	<targetVersion>0.16.1393</targetVersion>
	<description>

[English]

Adds basic animal surgeries and bionics to Rimworld 
This mod is fully compatible with Expanded Prosthetics and Organ Engineering (EPOE)

Following parts are added to the game:

* animal brain stimulator. Fits all animals.
* bionic animal eyes. Fits all animals. 
* simple/bionic animal ears. Fits all animals.
* simple/bionic animal jaw. Fits all animals. 
* simple/bionic animal spine. Fits all animals.
* simple prosthetic animal arms. Fits monkey and megatherium.
* bionic animal arms. Fits monkey and megatherium.
* bionic animal heart. Fits all animals.
* bionic animal lung. Fits all animals.
* bionic animal kidney. Fits all animals.
* bionic animal liver. Fits all animals.
* bionic animal stomach. Fits all animals.
* peglegs. Can be crafted with 1 wood. Fits all animals. Least efficiency.
* simple prosthetic animal legs. Fits all animals.
* bionic animal legs. Fits all animals.
* prosthetic tail. fits all animals with tails.

All parts can be obtained from traders, except pegleg.
All parts can be crafted at the animal prosthetics bench. Crafting requires a skill of 5-12, depending on part.

Simple parts are slightly lower in efficiency than natural parts. Bionic parts are higher.

Simple/ bionic legs, arms and jaws do melee damage now, depending on type.

All parts need medicine skill now to be installed. Simple parts need a skill from 4-6. Bionic parts need a skill form 8-10.

Updated, overhauled and expanded from Latta's A13

[Russian]

Добавляет базовые операции по вживлению бионических протезов на животных в Rimworld
Этот мод полностью совместим с Expanded Prosthetics и Organ Engineering (EPOE)

В игру добавлены следующие части:

* Стимулятор мозга животных. Подходит для всех животных.
* Бионические глаза. Подходит для всех животных.
* Простые / бионические уши. Подходит для всех животных.
* Простая / бионическая челюсть. Подходит для всех животных.
* Простой / бионический позвоночник. Подходит для всех животных.
* Простой протез руки. Подходит для обезьян и мегатерий.
* Бионические руки. Подходит для обезьян и мегатерий.
* Бионическое сердце. Подходит для всех животных.
* Бионическое лёгкое. Подходит для всех животных.
* Бионическая  почка. Подходит для всех животных.
* Бионическая печень. Подходит для всех животных.
* Бионический желудок. Подходит для всех животных.
* Деревянная нога. Может быть создано из 1 дерева. Подходит для всех животных. Наименьшая эффективность.
* Простые костыли животных. Подходит ко всем животным.
* Бионические костыли животных. Подходит для всех животных.
* Протезный хвост. Подходит для всех животных с хвостами.

Все части могут быть куплены у торговцев, кроме простых костылей.
Все части могут быть изготовлены на скамья для протезирования животных. Ремесло требует навыка 5-12, в зависимости от сложности.

Простые детали немного ниже по эффективности, чем натуральные детали. Бионические части выше.

Простые / бионические ноги, руки и челюсти теперь наносят урон в ближнем бою, в зависимости от типа.

Все операции теперь требуют навыка медицины. Простые части требуют навыка от 4-6. Для бионических частей требуется навык 8-10.

Мод обновлён, переработан и расширен из A13 Latta

</description>
</ModMetaData>
