<Defs>
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef Abstract="true" Name="UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>UpdateFeature</defName>
		<modNameReadable>Psychology</modNameReadable>
		<modIdentifier>Psychology</modIdentifier>
		<linkUrl>https://ludeon.com/forums/index.php?topic=17218</linkUrl>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
	
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase">
		<assemblyVersion>18.9.1</assemblyVersion>
		<content>Welcome to B19! | The internal workings of Psychology have been changed, so that anything that should receive a Psyche tab ought to now have one automatically. No more save file editing. Remember you can turn on dev mode to edit a pawn's psyche and sexuality from the Psyche tab, if the one that's generated for them isn't to your liking. | Two new traits have been added: Sedentary and Chatty. The likelihood of Psychology traits appearing has also been upped to bring them more in line with vanilla trait probabilities. | If you were ever curious which conversation topics corresponded to which parts of a person's personality, they are now listed in the Psyche tab. | The way that prisoner recruiting works is pretty dumb, huh? It'd be neat if someone were to make it more realistic and involved. Stay tuned.</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
	
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase">
		<assemblyVersion>18.9.6</assemblyVersion>
		<content>Psychology now has built-in performance benchmarking. | If you're interested in helping reduce this mod's performance footprint on your game, thereby potentially increasing your FPS (particularly in mid-to-late game colonies), then you can go to the mod settings and toggle "Enable performance reporting." | Afterwards, simply play as normal, and check your developer console for the performance reports you will receive. The longer your colony has been running without quitting to the menu or out of the game, the more helpful these reports will be. | Note that enabling performance reporting will have a detrimental effect on your FPS. This option is only for people interested in helping optimize Psychology.</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
</Defs>