<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  
  <!-- EN: psylink -->
  <PsychicAmplifier.label>пси-связь</PsychicAmplifier.label>
  <!-- EN: An organic connection to a larger psychic field. This allows a person to psychically induce a distant archotech superintelligence to influence reality in ways that seem impossible.\n\nHigher levels of psylink permit the use of more powers. Regardless of psylink level, a person can only use specific powers that they have learned.\n\nPsylink comes from a variety of sources. Single-use psylink neuroformer devices can create a psylink. Tribal peoples also know how to develop it through ritual linking with the legendary anima tree.\n\nAs a physical phenomenon in the brain, psylink is poorly-understood by scientists, not least because it seems to actively conceal itself if studied too closely. One thing most agree on is that it somehow connects people to archotechs and harnesses their power, possibly through some sort of negotiation or sympathy mechanism. -->
  <PsychicAmplifier.description>Органическая связь с широким пси-полем, позволяющая её обладателю побуждать сверхразум далёкого архотека воздействовать на окружающую действительность труднообъяснимыми способами.\n\nЧем выше уровень пси-связи, тем больше разных способностей можно применять. Вне зависимости от уровня, человек может применять лишь изученные им пси-способности.\n\nПси-связь можно установить разными способами. Для её искусственного формирования используют специальный одноразовый нейроформер. Во многих племенах научились развивать её при помощи ритуального связывания с легендарным древом души.\n\nКак физическое явление пси-связь плохо поддаётся научному объяснению. Одной из причин является то, что она будто бы активно скрывает себя при попытках изучения. Учёные сходятся во мнении, что пси-связь каким-то образом соединяет людей с архотеками и позволяет использовать их силу, вероятно, посредством своего рода переговоров или симпатического механизма.</PsychicAmplifier.description>
  <!-- EN: Allows a person to psychically-induce an archotech to influence reality in ways that seem impossible. Higher levels of psylink permit the use of more powers. -->
  <PsychicAmplifier.descriptionShort>Позволяет человеку психически побуждать архотека труднообъяснимыми способами воздействовать на окружающий мир. Чем выше уровень связи, тем больше видов воздействия доступно.</PsychicAmplifier.descriptionShort>
  <PsychicAmplifier.labelNoun>пси-связь</PsychicAmplifier.labelNoun>
  
</LanguageData>