<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<packageId>martinbaste.ideo.xenoprecept</packageId>
	<name>XenoDiversity Precept</name>
	<author>Martin Basterrechea</author>
	<supportedVersions>
		<li>1.3</li>
	</supportedVersions>
	<modDependencies>
	</modDependencies>

	<incompatibleWith>
	</incompatibleWith>
	<loadAfter>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld</li>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Royalty</li>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Ideology</li>
		<li>erdelf.HumanoidAlienRaces</li>
		<li>skyarkhangel.HSK</li>
	</loadAfter>

	<description>
Ideology DLC requires!

Do you want to create a colony that embraces having members from different species? Or do you prefer a colony of racist aliens that reject anyone from a different species?
XenoDiversity Precept mod adds a precept that can be selected for your ideologies. This precept allows you to control how colonists react to other Human-like species, their xenophobia or xenophilia. All humans are considered the same species, only pawns from other species (aliens, etc. for example from Humanoid Alien Races) are considered.
The xenophobia precept is linked to the Human Primacy and Supremacist memes, and the xenophilia precept is linked to the Individualist meme. I might remove this requirement.

Features:

- Positive moodlet if the colony has uniform species (for xenophobes) and negative if there is species diversity. The reverse happens with xenophilia.

- For xenophobes, negative moodlet if leader is from a different species.

- Negative social standing to people of different species if xenophobe.

Should be compatible with any mod, tested with Humanoid Alien Races.
Icon edited from original made by Freepik from www.flaticon.com
Feedback and bug reports are very welcome.


Требуется DLC Идеология.

Данная модификация добавляет заповеди (precepts), оказывающие реакцию ваших колонистов на наличие прочих рас (по умолчанию, ксенофилия для индивидуализма (Individualist) и ксенофобия для супримасизма (Supremacist) и превосходства человечества (Human Primacy)).
	</description>
</ModMetaData>