<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<DefPackage-ConceptDef>

	<ConceptDef>
		<defName>CameraDolly</defName>
		<priority>95</priority>
		<helpTexts>
			<li>Move the camera by clicking and dragging the MIDDLE MOUSE BUTTON or with the WASD keys.</li>
		</helpTexts>
	</ConceptDef>

	<ConceptDef>
		<defName>Rescuing</defName>
		<priority>55</priority>
		<needsOpportunity>True</needsOpportunity>
		<helpTexts>
			<li>To rescue a wounded colonist, select a healthy colonist and the right-click on the wounded one.</li>
		</helpTexts>
	</ConceptDef>

	<ConceptDef>
		<defName>Capturing</defName>
		<priority>55</priority>
		<needsOpportunity>True</needsOpportunity>
		<helpTexts>
			<li>An enemy has been incapacitated. You can capture them!</li>
			<li>To capture, select a colonist, right-click on the incapacitated enemy, and select Capture.\n\nYou'll need an extra bed marked for prisoner use.</li>
		</helpTexts>
	</ConceptDef>
  
	<ConceptDef>
		<defName>InteractingWithTraders</defName>
		<priority>50</priority>
		<needsOpportunity>True</needsOpportunity>
		<helpTexts>
			<li>You can talk to people with ? over their heads.\n\nSelect a colonist and right-click on the character with ? attached to his head.</li>
		</helpTexts>
	</ConceptDef>

	<ConceptDef>
		<defName>Drafting</defName>
		<priority>45</priority>
		<needsOpportunity>True</needsOpportunity>
    <highlightTag>ToggleDrafted</highlightTag>
    <helpTexts>
			<li>To control colonists directly for combat, Draft them by selecting them and hitting the DRAFT button.</li>
			<li>A drafted colonist will do only what you tell them, and can only take combat actions. Those with weapons will use them when possible.\n\nDon't leave colonists Drafted forever - they'll starve and become unhappy.</li>
		</helpTexts>
	</ConceptDef>

  <ConceptDef>
    <defName>AnimalsDontAttackDoors</defName>
    <priority>40</priority>
    <needsOpportunity>True</needsOpportunity>
    <noteTeaches>true</noteTeaches>
    <helpTexts>
      <li>Manhunting animals generally won't attack doors or inactive turrets.\n\nYou can escape them by getting inside or behind a wall. But they'll wait for you.</li>
    </helpTexts>
  </ConceptDef>
  
  <ConceptDef>
    <defName>BillsTab</defName>
    <needsOpportunity>true</needsOpportunity>
    <opportunityDecays>false</opportunityDecays>
    <priority>40</priority>
    <highlightTag>TabBills</highlightTag>
    <helpTexts>
      <li>To make colonists work at a table, select the table and open the Bills tab. Here, you can say what meals to cook, what things to craft, what creatures to butcher.</li>
    </helpTexts>
  </ConceptDef>

	<ConceptDef>
		<defName>TVForSickPeople</defName>
		<priority>35</priority>
		<needsOpportunity>true</needsOpportunity>
    <noteTeaches>true</noteTeaches>
    <helpTexts>
			<li>To entertain sick people in bed, set up a TV they can watch.</li>
		</helpTexts>
	</ConceptDef>
  
  <ConceptDef>
    <defName>AnimalTraining</defName>
    <priority>30</priority>
    <highlightTag>TabTraining</highlightTag>
    <helpTexts>
      <li>You can assign a tame animal to be trained in specific skills on its TRAINING tab.\n\nAnimals can't be trained continuously; they need time between training sessions.</li>
    </helpTexts>
  </ConceptDef>
  
  <ConceptDef>
    <defName>StorageTabCategories</defName>
    <priority>20</priority>
    <needsOpportunity>True</needsOpportunity>
    <helpTexts>
      <li>In the storage tab of a stockpile, you can expand categories to allow or deny specific items. Click the triangles to the left of category names.</li>
    </helpTexts>
  </ConceptDef>

  <ConceptDef>
    <defName>Mining</defName>
    <priority>12</priority>
    <highlightTag>DesignatorMine</highlightTag>
    <helpTexts>
      <li>You can designate where to mine by opening the ARCHITECT menu and selecting the ORDERS tab.\n\nSome mineable blocks yield STEEL, GOLD, PLASTEEL, and other useful materials.</li>
    </helpTexts>
  </ConceptDef>

  <ConceptDef>
    <defName>HostilityResponse</defName>
    <priority>8</priority>
    <highlightTag>HostilityResponse</highlightTag>
    <helpTexts>
      <li>You can configure how colonists should automatically respond to threats like predatory animals.\n\nChoose from FLEE, ATTACK, and IGNORE modes in the ASSIGN menu.</li>
    </helpTexts>
  </ConceptDef>
  
  <ConceptDef>
    <defName>OpeningComms</defName>
    <priority>5</priority>
    <needsOpportunity>True</needsOpportunity>
    <helpTexts>
      <li>To communicate, select a colonist and right-click on the comms console.</li>
    </helpTexts>
  </ConceptDef>

  <ConceptDef>
    <defName>Deterioration</defName>
    <priority>4</priority>
    <noteTeaches>true</noteTeaches>
    <helpTexts>
      <li>Items left outdoors will slowly deteriorate.\n\nIf you want to store items long-term, keep them under a roof.</li>
    </helpTexts>
  </ConceptDef>

  <ConceptDef>
    <defName>InspectRoomStats</defName>
    <priority>3</priority>
    <highlightTag>InspectRoomStats</highlightTag>
    <helpTexts>
      <li>You can inspect the impressiveness, wealth, and beauty of individual rooms using the ROOM STATS INSPECT toggle in the bottom right.</li>
    </helpTexts>
  </ConceptDef>
  
  <ConceptDef>
    <defName>ClickingMessages</defName>
    <priority>3</priority>
    <highlightTag>Messages</highlightTag>
    <helpTexts>
      <li>You can click on the notifications in the top-left of the screen to instantly center the camera on their subject.</li>
    </helpTexts>
  </ConceptDef>
  
</DefPackage-ConceptDef>