<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<LanguageData>

	<PAC.PawnsAreCapable>Pawns Are Capable!</PAC.PawnsAreCapable>
	
	<PAC.debuffLevel>Severity of Mood Debuffs for Hated Work Types</PAC.debuffLevel>
	<PAC.DebuffLow>Low debuffs (typically -10, -20 and -30, depending upon length of work assignment).</PAC.DebuffLow>
	<PAC.DebuffNormal>Normal debuffs (typically -20, -35 and -50, depending upon length of work assignment).</PAC.DebuffNormal>
	<PAC.DebuffHigh>High debuffs (typically -30, -50 and -70, depending upon length of work assignment.)</PAC.DebuffHigh>

  <PAC.AllowNewHate>New Work Type Hatreds Can Appear</PAC.AllowNewHate>
  <PAC.AllowNewHateTip>Pawns who hate a particular type of work but are assigned to it anyway have a (very slight) chance to decide that the work's not so bad, after all, and spontaneously lose the hatred. If this option is checked, the reverse can happen, as well, and pawns will have a (very slight) chance to begin hating a type of work they've previously done without complaint. Note, however, that a pawn will never spontaneously begin hating a particular type of work if he or she has any passion for the relevant skill(s).</PAC.AllowNewHateTip>
  
	<PAC.AllThumbsAssignedCrafting.Label>All Thumbs assigned to crafting</PAC.AllThumbsAssignedCrafting.Label>
	<PAC.AllThumbsAssignedCrafting.Explanation>One of your colonists has the All Thumbs personality trait, but is assigned to crafting, tailoring, or smithing. This will make them very unhappy.</PAC.AllThumbsAssignedCrafting.Explanation>

	<PAC.AnimalLoverAssignedHunting.Label>Animal Lover assigned to hunting</PAC.AnimalLoverAssignedHunting.Label>
	<PAC.AnimalLoverAssignedHunting.Explanation>One of your colonists has the Animal Lover personality trait, but is assigned to hunting. This will make them very unhappy.</PAC.AnimalLoverAssignedHunting.Explanation>

	<PAC.AntiSocialAssignedWardening.Label>Anti-Social assigned to wardening</PAC.AntiSocialAssignedWardening.Label>
	<PAC.AntiSocialAssignedWardening.Explanation>One of your colonists has the Anti-Social personality trait, but is assigned to wardening. This will make them very unhappy.</PAC.AntiSocialAssignedWardening.Explanation>

	<PAC.BrownThumbAssignedGrowing.Label>Brown Thumb assigned to growing</PAC.BrownThumbAssignedGrowing.Label>
	<PAC.BrownThumbAssignedGrowing.Explanation>One of your colonists has the Brown Thumb personality trait, but is assigned to growing. This will make them very unhappy.</PAC.BrownThumbAssignedGrowing.Explanation>

	<PAC.BurnsWaterAssignedCooking.Label>Burns Water assigned to cooking</PAC.BurnsWaterAssignedCooking.Label>
	<PAC.BurnsWaterAssignedCooking.Explanation>One of your colonists has the Burns Water personality trait, but is assigned to cooking. This will make them very unhappy.</PAC.BurnsWaterAssignedCooking.Explanation>

	<PAC.ClaustrophobicAssignedMining.Label>Claustrophobic assigned to mining</PAC.ClaustrophobicAssignedMining.Label>
	<PAC.ClaustrophobicAssignedMining.Explanation>One of your colonists has the Claustrophobic personality trait, but is assigned to mining. This will make them very unhappy.</PAC.ClaustrophobicAssignedMining.Explanation>

	<PAC.DislikesAnimalsAssignedHandling.Label>Dislikes Animals assigned to handling</PAC.DislikesAnimalsAssignedHandling.Label>
	<PAC.DislikesAnimalsAssignedHandling.Explanation>One of your colonists has the Dislikes Animals personality trait, but is assigned to handling. This will make them very unhappy.</PAC.DislikesAnimalsAssignedHandling.Explanation>

	<PAC.DunceAssignedResearch.Label>Dunce assigned to research</PAC.DunceAssignedResearch.Label>
	<PAC.DunceAssignedResearch.Explanation>One of your colonists has the Dunce personality trait, but is assigned to research. This will make them very unhappy.</PAC.DunceAssignedResearch.Explanation>

	<PAC.HatesHospitalsAssignedDoctor.Label>Hates Hospitals assigned to doctoring</PAC.HatesHospitalsAssignedDoctor.Label>
	<PAC.HatesHospitalsAssignedDoctor.Explanation>One of your colonists has the Hates Hospitals personality trait, but is assigned to doctoring. This will make them very unhappy.</PAC.HatesHospitalsAssignedDoctor.Explanation>
			
	<PAC.IneptAssignedSkilledLabor.Label>Inept assigned to skilled labor</PAC.IneptAssignedSkilledLabor.Label>
	<PAC.IneptAssignedSkilledLabor.Explanation>One of your colonists has the Inept personality trait, but is assigned to skilled labor. This will make them very unhappy.</PAC.IneptAssignedSkilledLabor.Explanation>
	
	<PAC.NonViolentHasWeapon.Label>Pacifist has weapon</PAC.NonViolentHasWeapon.Label>
	<PAC.NonViolentHasWeapon.Explanation>One of your colonists has the Pacifist personality trait, but is carrying a weapon. This will make them very unhappy.</PAC.NonViolentHasWeapon.Explanation>

	<PAC.PhilistineAssignedArt.Label>Philistine assigned to art</PAC.PhilistineAssignedArt.Label>
	<PAC.PhilistineAssignedArt.Explanation>One of your colonists has the Philistine personality trait, but is assigned to art. This will make them very unhappy.</PAC.PhilistineAssignedArt.Explanation>
	
	<PAC.PyromaniacAssignedFirefighting.Label>Pyromaniac assigned to firefighting</PAC.PyromaniacAssignedFirefighting.Label>
	<PAC.PyromaniacAssignedFirefighting.Explanation>One of your colonists has the Pyromaniac personality trait, but is assigned to firefighting. This will make them very unhappy.</PAC.PyromaniacAssignedFirefighting.Explanation>
	
	<PAC.PyrophobicAssignedFirefighting.Label>Pyrophobic assigned to firefighting</PAC.PyrophobicAssignedFirefighting.Label>
	<PAC.PyrophobicAssignedFirefighting.Explanation>One of your colonists has the Pyrophobic personality trait, but is assigned to firefighting. This will make them very unhappy.</PAC.PyrophobicAssignedFirefighting.Explanation>
	
	<PAC.SlackerAssignedHauling.Label>Slacker assigned to hauling</PAC.SlackerAssignedHauling.Label>
	<PAC.SlackerAssignedHauling.Explanation>One of your colonists has the Slacker personality trait, but is assigned to hauling. This will make them very unhappy.</PAC.SlackerAssignedHauling.Explanation>
	
	<PAC.SlobAssignedCleaning.Label>Slob assigned to cleaning</PAC.SlobAssignedCleaning.Label>
	<PAC.SlobAssignedCleaning.Explanation>One of your colonists has the Slob personality trait, but is assigned to cleaning. This will make them very unhappy.</PAC.SlobAssignedCleaning.Explanation>
	
	<PAC.SnobAssignedManualLabor.Label>Snob assigned to manual labor</PAC.SnobAssignedManualLabor.Label>
	<PAC.SnobAssignedManualLabor.Explanation>One of your colonists has the Snob personality trait, but is assigned to manual labor. This will make them very unhappy.</PAC.SnobAssignedManualLabor.Explanation>
	
	<PAC.UselessAssignedWork.Label>Useless assigned to work</PAC.UselessAssignedWork.Label>
	<PAC.UselessAssignedWork.Explanation>One of your colonists has the Useless personality trait, but is assigned to skilled labor or dumb labor. This will make them very unhappy.</PAC.UselessAssignedWork.Explanation>
	
	<PAC.NotSoBad.Label>That's Not So Bad After All!</PAC.NotSoBad.Label>
	
	<PAC.NotSoBad.AllThumbs> has discovered that crafting isn't quite so bad, after all.</PAC.NotSoBad.AllThumbs>
	<PAC.NotSoBad.AnimalLover> has decided that hunting isn't necessarily a bad thing, as long as the animals being hunted aren't cute.</PAC.NotSoBad.AnimalLover>
	<PAC.NotSoBad.AntiSocial> has decided that dealing with people is sort of okay, at least if there aren't any crowds around.</PAC.NotSoBad.AntiSocial>
	<PAC.NotSoBad.BrownThumb> has discovered that growing things isn't quite so bad, after all.</PAC.NotSoBad.BrownThumb>
	<PAC.NotSoBad.BurnsWater> has discovered that cooking isn't quite so bad, as long as the recipes are simple.</PAC.NotSoBad.BurnsWater>
	<PAC.NotSoBad.Claustrophobic> has learned that mining isn't so horrible and is no longer in fear of being buried alive in a tunnel collapse.</PAC.NotSoBad.Claustrophobic>
	<PAC.NotSoBad.DislikesAnimals> has realized that animals aren't really so bad, after all. But thrumbos are still pretty intimidating.</PAC.NotSoBad.DislikesAnimals>
	<PAC.NotSoBad.Dunce> has discovered researching isn't so bad, as long as the subject is interesting.</PAC.NotSoBad.Dunce>
	<PAC.NotSoBad.HatesHospitals> has decided that caring for sick people isn't so bad, after all.</PAC.NotSoBad.HatesHospitals>
	<PAC.NotSoBad.Inept></PAC.NotSoBad.Inept>
	<PAC.NotSoBad.NonViolent> has concluded that carrying a weapon, at least while on a dangerous rimworld, is maybe not such a bad idea, after all.</PAC.NotSoBad.NonViolent>
	<PAC.NotSoBad.Philistine> has developed a knack for art, even if it is just drawing fancy stick figures.</PAC.NotSoBad.Philistine>
	<PAC.NotSoBad.Slacker> has decided that hauling isn't quite so bad after all. At the very least, it's good exercise.</PAC.NotSoBad.Slacker>
	<PAC.NotSoBad.Slob> has decided that a bit of cleaning every now and then really isn't deadly. But neat freaks are still fair targets for mockery.</PAC.NotSoBad.Slob>
	<PAC.NotSoBad.Snob> has decided that putting up with having to do a bit of manual labor now and then is a fair trade off for the aid of others in surviving on a rimworld.</PAC.NotSoBad.Snob>

  <PAC.NewHatred.Label>New Hated Work Type!</PAC.NewHatred.Label>
  <PAC.NewHatred.AllThumbs> has had quite enough of being assigned to crafting, and will no longer tolerate it without complaining!</PAC.NewHatred.AllThumbs>
  <PAC.NewHatred.AntiSocial> has had quite enough of being assigned to wardening, and will no longer tolerate it without complaining!</PAC.NewHatred.AntiSocial>
  <PAC.NewHatred.BrownThumb> has had quite enough of plantwork, and will no longer tolerate it without complaining!</PAC.NewHatred.BrownThumb>
  <PAC.NewHatred.BurnsWater> has had quite enough of cooking, and will no longer tolerate being assigned to it without complaining!</PAC.NewHatred.BurnsWater>
  <PAC.NewHatred.Claustrophobic> has had quite enough of being assigned to mining, and will no longer tolerate it without complaining!</PAC.NewHatred.Claustrophobic>
  <PAC.NewHatred.DislikesAnimals> has had quite enough of dealing with animals, and will no longer tolerate it without complaining!</PAC.NewHatred.DislikesAnimals>
  <PAC.NewHatred.Dunce> has had quite enough of being assigned to research, and will no longer tolerate it without complaining!</PAC.NewHatred.Dunce>
  <PAC.NewHatred.HatesHospitals> has had quite enough of doctoring, and will no longer tolerate being assigned to it without complaining!</PAC.NewHatred.HatesHospitals>
  <PAC.NewHatred.Philistine> has had quite enough of art, and will no longer tolerate being assigned to it without complaining!</PAC.NewHatred.Philistine>
  <PAC.NewHatred.Slacker> has had quite enough of being assigned to hauling, and will no longer tolerate it without complaining!</PAC.NewHatred.Slacker>
  <PAC.NewHatred.Slob> has had quite enough of being assigned to cleaning, and will no longer tolerate it without complaining!</PAC.NewHatred.Slob>
  
</LanguageData>
