<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>The enemy of my enemy is my friend</name>
	<author>arpomo6</author>
	<supportedVersions>
		<li>1.4</li>
	</supportedVersions>
	<packageId>arpomo6.hmpc.teomeimf</packageId>
	<description>
(ENG)
&lt;color=red&gt;Experimental mod, can greatly increase the difficulty of the game.&lt;/color&gt;
The modification unites all factions hostile by default with each other, making them allies or neutrals in relation to each other. If hostile raids from different factions happen at the same time, they will jointly attack the player. Norbals and mechanoids will join forces, terminators and tribes will stand up to protect this world, and even darkness will stand up to protect them from the oppression of the player.

Notes: The mod only works with HSK factions, as well as some factions and races from the patches-1-3 section (e.g. Revia Race, Nyaron), factions can still become hostile to each other due to the influence of game mechanics. Mod may not work on existing colonies, it is recommended to create a new one.

(RUS)
&lt;color=red&gt;Экспериментальный мод, может значительно усложнить игру.&lt;/color&gt;
Модификация объединяет все враждебные по умолчанию фракции между собой, делая их союзниками или нейтралами по отношению друг к другу. Если враждебные рейды разных фракций окажутся в одно время на вашей карте, они будут совместно нападать на вас. Норбалы и механоиды объединят свои силы, терминаторы и племена встанут на защиту этого мира и даже тьма встанет на их защиту от гнета игрокова.

Примечания: модификация работает только с фракциями ХСК, а также некоторыми фракциями и расами из раздела patches-1-3 (например, Revia Race, Nyaron), фракции все ещё могут стать враждебными друг другу из-за влияния игровых механик. Мод может не работать на существующих колониях, рекомендуется создать новую.
	</description>
	<modDependencies>
	</modDependencies>
	<loadBefore>
		<li>GhostRolly.Rim73</li>
		<li>experimental.optimizations</li>
		<li>notooshabby.rocketman</li>
		<li>Krkr.RocketMan</li>
	</loadBefore>
	<loadAfter>
		<li>brrainz.harmony</li>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld</li>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Royalty</li>
		<li>UnlimitedHugs.HugsLib</li>
		<li>CETeam.CombatExtended</li>
		<li>skyarkhangel.HSK</li>
		<li>killface.facialstuff</li>
		<li>chjees.androids</li>
		<li>multilangcolorfultraits.pirateby</li>
		<li>Solaris.RatkinRaceMod</li>
		<li>skyarkhangel.skynet</li>
		<li>skyarkhangel.asarirace</li>
		<li>skyarkhangel.darkestnight</li>
		<li>arpomo6.hmc.project</li>
		<li>Farmradish.Nyaron</li>
		<li>FS.ReviaRace</li>
	</loadAfter>
</ModMetaData>
