<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<LanguageData>
	<HelpTextAddOn>More CleanUp..



Animal Family sweep-up:
	Sometimes there are too many members(dead or of other factions) in an animal family,and this function can remove them.Better use after cleaning World Pawns.



Remove Filth (Home Area): Yes, literally.

Remove Snow (Home Area): The same, but snow this time.

Remove Corpses in current map:
	All the dead pawns in graves, cryo caskets or anything like that will be ignored.

Remove BattleLog Entries:
	Entries will be created during combat and shown under Log tab of a pawn. This cleanup will remove them while social interaction logs are not affected.

Remove Unpinned Messages:
	Letters and messages (top left floating notifications) will be saved and can be tracked under History - Message tab. This cleanup will remove them, but an entry will be kept if you've clicked and pinned it before.</HelpTextAddOn>
	<HelpTextFix>First Aid..



Show Debug Log:
	Bring up Debug Log window. Designed for those who refuse to enable Dev mode or get it disabled permanently.

Regenerate AvoidGrids:
	Regenerate AvoidGrids and attempt to fix some enemy raid AI issues. 

Faction Relationships: Attempt to fix the DebugLog Error:"Faction xxx has null relation with xxx. Return Dummy relation." 
This tool could not fix the Error caused by the following mods:
	1.Misc. FactionBase:Error while generating maps,if a mechanoid is spawned.
	2.PPSMedicalCare (not for sure):Error during saving and loading,and that might become increasingly serious.



Faction Leaders: Attempt to fix Comms Console issues by generating leaders for bugged factions. A faction leader won't be replaced if a faction currently has one.</HelpTextFix>
	<HelpTextSysGC>Reclaim Memory



Call System.GC.Collect() and recycle some used memory (will not intefere other programs).
Minor boost for game performance (and it returns to normal soon).

Shift+click: Manually execute some auto-cleanup commands. Find details in RuntimeGC's mod setting page.</HelpTextSysGC>

	

</LanguageData>
