<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <RRP_Grassland.label>grassland</RRP_Grassland.label>
  <RRP_Grassland.description>Grasslands, as the name suggests, are areas where the vegetation is dominated by grasses and shrubs. The soil is fertile, but there is little protection from the elements.</RRP_Grassland.description>

  <RRP_Savanna.label>savanna</RRP_Savanna.label>
  <RRP_Savanna.description>Savannas are mixed woodland/grassland ecosystems typically found between rainforests and deserts. Though savannas are more forested than grasslands, their trees are still spaced widely enough that sufficient light reaches the ground to support an unbroken layer of grasses. Despite the abundance of plants, the soil is mostly dry, and a wide variety of animals roam the area searching for food and water.</RRP_Savanna.description>

  <RRP_Steppes.label>steppes</RRP_Steppes.label>
  <RRP_Steppes.description>Steppes are high-altitude grassland regions. A steppe may be semi-desert or covered with grass or shrubs or both, depending on the season and latitude.</RRP_Steppes.description>

  <RRP_TemperateDesert.label>temperate desert</RRP_TemperateDesert.label>
  <RRP_TemperateDesert.description>Temperate deserts are cooler but often even drier than subtropical deserts. Vegetation is sparse, and the ground is typically more rocky than sandy.</RRP_TemperateDesert.description>

  <RRP_Permafrost.label>permafrost</RRP_Permafrost.label>
  <RRP_Permafrost.description>Permafrost exists on the border between tundra and ice sheets. The ground is permanently frozen, and much of it is covered in ice, but the ice is at most a few meters, rather than kilometers, thick. There is little vegetation beyond scrub brush, and few animals.</RRP_Permafrost.description>

  <RRP_Oasis.label>oasis</RRP_Oasis.label>
  <RRP_Oasis.description>Oases are vibrant, isolated bits of life and color. In even the harshest of deserts, after all, groundwater occasionally manages to make it to the surface, and where it does, life blooms. Plants grow around small ponds, and animals gather in search of water and shade.</RRP_Oasis.description>


</LanguageData>