<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><LanguageData>

    <Nudist.degreeDatas.0.label>nudist</Nudist.degreeDatas.0.label>
    <Nudist.degreeDatas.0.description>NAME enjoys the feeling of freedom that comes from being nude. HECAP can handle clothing, but will be happier without it.</Nudist.degreeDatas.0.description>

    <Bloodlust.degreeDatas.0.label>bloodlust</Bloodlust.degreeDatas.0.label>
    <Bloodlust.degreeDatas.0.description>NAME gets a rush from hurting people, and never minds the sight of blood or death. HECAP is twice as likely to start a social fight.</Bloodlust.degreeDatas.0.description>

    <Psychopath.degreeDatas.0.label>psychopath</Psychopath.degreeDatas.0.label>
    <Psychopath.degreeDatas.0.description>NAME has no empathy. The suffering of others doesn't bother HIM at all. HECAP doesn't mind if others are butchered, left unburied, imprisoned, or sold to slavery - unless it affects HIM. HECAP also feels no mood boost from socializing.</Psychopath.degreeDatas.0.description>

    <Cannibal.degreeDatas.0.label>cannibal</Cannibal.degreeDatas.0.label>
    <Cannibal.degreeDatas.0.description>NAME was taught that eating human meat is wrong and horrible. But one time, long ago, HE tried it... and HE liked it.</Cannibal.degreeDatas.0.description>

    <Abrasive.degreeDatas.0.label>abrasive</Abrasive.degreeDatas.0.label>
    <Abrasive.degreeDatas.0.description>NAME always says exactly what's on HIS mind, especially if it's bugging HIM. That tends to rub people the wrong way.</Abrasive.degreeDatas.0.description>

    <TooSmart.degreeDatas.0.label>too smart</TooSmart.degreeDatas.0.label>
    <TooSmart.degreeDatas.0.description>NAME is too smart for HIS own good. HECAP learns everything much faster than everyone, but can be quite eccentric.</TooSmart.degreeDatas.0.description>

    <Brawler.degreeDatas.0.label>brawler</Brawler.degreeDatas.0.label>
    <Brawler.degreeDatas.0.description>NAME likes to fight up close and personal. HISCAP accuracy is greatly increased in melee combat, but HE'll be very unhappy if asked to carry a ranged weapon.</Brawler.degreeDatas.0.description>

    <Masochist.degreeDatas.0.label>masochist</Masochist.degreeDatas.0.label>
    <Masochist.degreeDatas.0.description>For NAME, there's something exciting about getting hurt. HECAP doesn't know why, HE's just wired differently.</Masochist.degreeDatas.0.description>

    <Prosthophile.degreeDatas.0.label>prosthophile</Prosthophile.degreeDatas.0.label>
    <Prosthophile.degreeDatas.0.description>NAME feels limited in HIS feeble human body. HECAP often dreams of going bionic.</Prosthophile.degreeDatas.0.description>

    <Prosthophobe.degreeDatas.0.label>prosthophobe</Prosthophobe.degreeDatas.0.label>
    <Prosthophobe.degreeDatas.0.description>NAME believes the human body is limited for a reason. To HIM, bionic body parts are unethical.</Prosthophobe.degreeDatas.0.description>

    <GreenThumb.degreeDatas.0.label>green thumb</GreenThumb.degreeDatas.0.label>
    <GreenThumb.degreeDatas.0.description>NAME has a passion for gardening. HECAP gets a mood bonus for every plant HE sows.</GreenThumb.degreeDatas.0.description>

    <NightOwl.degreeDatas.0.label>night owl</NightOwl.degreeDatas.0.label>
    <NightOwl.degreeDatas.0.description>NAME likes to be up during the night, and sleep during the day.\n\nHECAP gets a mood bonus if awake at night (23h-6h) and mood loss if awake during the day (11h-18h).</NightOwl.degreeDatas.0.description>

    <Greedy.degreeDatas.0.label>greedy</Greedy.degreeDatas.0.label>
    <Greedy.degreeDatas.0.description>NAME needs a really impressive bedroom. HECAP gets a mood loss if HE doesn't get what HE wants.</Greedy.degreeDatas.0.description>

    <Jealous.degreeDatas.0.label>jealous</Jealous.degreeDatas.0.label>
    <Jealous.degreeDatas.0.description>For NAME, it's degrading to have a less impressive bedroom than someone else. HECAP gets a mood loss if any colonist has a more impressive bedroom.</Jealous.degreeDatas.0.description>

    <Ascetic.degreeDatas.0.label>ascetic</Ascetic.degreeDatas.0.label>
    <Ascetic.degreeDatas.0.description>NAME prefers to live in asceticism. HECAP will be put in a poor mood if HE has a bedroom that's too impressive. HECAP also dislikes fancy food and prefers to eat raw - and raw food won't both HIM a bit.</Ascetic.degreeDatas.0.description>

    <Gay.degreeDatas.0.label>gay</Gay.degreeDatas.0.label>
    <Gay.degreeDatas.0.description>NAME is romantically attracted to people of HIS own gender.</Gay.degreeDatas.0.description>

    <DislikesMen.degreeDatas.0.label>dislikes men</DislikesMen.degreeDatas.0.label>
    <DislikesMen.degreeDatas.0.description>NAME really dislikes and distrusts men.</DislikesMen.degreeDatas.0.description>

    <DislikesWomen.degreeDatas.0.label>dislikes women</DislikesWomen.degreeDatas.0.label>
    <DislikesWomen.degreeDatas.0.description>NAME really dislikes and distrusts women.</DislikesWomen.degreeDatas.0.description>

    <AnnoyingVoice.degreeDatas.0.label>annoying voice</AnnoyingVoice.degreeDatas.0.label>
    <AnnoyingVoice.degreeDatas.0.description>NAME's voice has a particularly grating, nasal quality to it, and HE tends to talk in barked, garbled phrases. This predisposes others to dislike HIM.</AnnoyingVoice.degreeDatas.0.description>

    <CreepyBreathing.degreeDatas.0.label>creepy breathing</CreepyBreathing.degreeDatas.0.label>
    <CreepyBreathing.degreeDatas.0.description>NAME breathes heavily all the time, and sweats constantly. People find it creepy.</CreepyBreathing.degreeDatas.0.description>

    <Pyromaniac.degreeDatas.0.label>pyromaniac</Pyromaniac.degreeDatas.0.label>
    <Pyromaniac.degreeDatas.0.description>NAME loves fire. HECAP will occasionaly start fires and will never extinguish them.</Pyromaniac.degreeDatas.0.description>

</LanguageData>