<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
<name>JT's Field Surgery</name>
<author>JT</author>
<targetVersion>0.18.0</targetVersion>
<description>(B18 Version 4)

Expands your options for emergency surgery, whether in the field or in the hospital.

&lt;b&gt;&lt;color=#009000&gt;Unanaesthetised Amputations:&lt;/color&gt;&lt;/b&gt;

Creates a &lt;color=#C0C000&gt;dismember&lt;/color&gt; operation to amputate without the use of anaesthetic, for use in extreme emergencies (e.g., advanced infection with no medicine) or as a particularly nasty way of counting coup against your "guilty" prisoners. Chance of death is high, and failure rate in non-ideal conditions is high.

The removed limb or organ will be only a worthless chunk of meat, being unsalvageable as a result of the procedure, and will ALWAYS be removed. In the event of a failure, even a "minor" failure, it will be forcibly ripped/chopped out/off, leaving a gaping wound and in all probability killing them anyway. Be absolutely certain to administer medical treatment immediately after the procedure, in the event of a non-fatal amputation, to avoid further infection!

To dispel ambiguity:
* &lt;color=#C0C000&gt;Dismember&lt;/color&gt; means "chop off without anaesthetic".
* &lt;color=#C0C000&gt;Amputate&lt;/color&gt; means "chop off with anaesthetic".
* &lt;color=#C0C000&gt;Harvest&lt;/color&gt; means "remove carefully for re-use".
* &lt;color=#C0C000&gt;Remove&lt;/color&gt; means "detach prosthetic".

&lt;b&gt;&lt;color=#009000&gt;Elective Dismemberment:&lt;/color&gt;&lt;/b&gt;

You can now &lt;color=#C0C000&gt;hold SHIFT to dismember healthy limbs&lt;/color&gt; from colonists or "not guilty" prisoners. Psychopathic or cannibalistic doctors won't mind one bit (and secretly long to be able to), but other doctors will be a bit upset that they did unnecessary surgery tantamount to torture.  Your other colonists will also be mortified if they have normal moral predilections.

&lt;b&gt;&lt;color=#009000&gt;Blood Donations and Packs:&lt;/color&gt;&lt;/b&gt;

A blood economy is included which allows one to &lt;color=#C0C000&gt;draw blood&lt;/color&gt; to be stored as &lt;color=#C0C000&gt;blood packs&lt;/color&gt;. Note that a person who donates blood will have the same amount of blood loss as the pack would restore, slightly under one-third of the fatal limit.  From an ordinarily healthy individual, this of course isn't particularly devastating, although it will make them a little woozy until they recuperate.

You may then &lt;color=#C0C000&gt;transfuse blood&lt;/color&gt;, which will attach an intravenal drip to reduce a pawn's blood loss gradually.  The pawn can walk around while the transfusion is underway, suffering only minor movement penalties due to the transfusion equipment, unless of course they are incapacitated.  The blood pack will automatically be detached and discarded (deleted) once there is no blood loss, so proactively initiating transfusions before combat won't work (in this house, we respect the laws of haemovigilance!).  Note that the condition of the blood pack reflects how much blood can actually be transfused.

There is no minimum skill level to performing the blood transfusion operation, but poorly-skilled attendants will &lt;color=#C0C000&gt;randomly spill&lt;/color&gt; some of the blood, limiting the useful effect.  At zero skill, the amount spilled is usually less than half, but can be up to 5/6ths of the blood pack!  Note that the amount of usable blood in a blood pack also depends on its condition.  A blood pack in poor condition may only be worth a few percentage points of blood loss severity before it must be discarded.

Be careful to store blood carefully: it has a short shelf life, and can be refrigerated to prolong life but &lt;color=#C0C000&gt;cannot be frozen&lt;/color&gt; without degrading quickly.  Especially destructive is freeze-thaw action!  A blood pack which is frozen will not last more than a couple of days, and can be destroyed in mere minutes if it suffers from multiple freeze-thaws, but a room temperature pack will last up to 7 days and a blood pack at 1 &#176;C can last over 60 days.  (Note that many mods that claim to be "refrigerators" are in fact freezers (e.g., RimFridge cools things to -10 &#176;C!) and will destroy your blood packs.  Until these mods are updated to allow configuration of their temperatures, they are probably unwise to use for blood packs versus a walk-in cold room.)

&lt;color=#C0C000&gt;Plasma packs&lt;/color&gt; can also be used to correct the negative side effects of blood loss; when a plasma pack is administered it will add a modifier which counteracts most the penalties of blood loss exactly.  However, the body will still be missing blood: if the person is injured again, or continues to bleed, they may die of blood loss anyway.  The principal advantages of plasma packs are that they counteract *most* of the bad side effects, can be frozen naturally, and last longer.

Glycerolisation of blood packs at a drug lab by adding neutroamine to produce &lt;color=#C0C000&gt;freezable blood packs&lt;/color&gt; will allow them to be frozen forever, eliminating all of their disadvantages and rendering them superior to plasma packs -- but at cost.

Generally, &lt;color=#C0C000&gt;traders will stock&lt;/color&gt; freezable blood packs and plasma packs along with all other routine medications.

&lt;b&gt;&lt;color=#009000&gt;Medications&lt;/color&gt;&lt;/b&gt;

Special medications permit the treatment of certain conditions that are ordinarily difficult to treat without outside assistance.

&lt;color=#C0C000&gt;Wormicide&lt;/color&gt; provides the ability to treat gutworms.  It is essentially ingestible poison, but you're bigger than they are.  As long as you moderate your doses, you'll be fine.

&lt;color=#C0C000&gt;Ananogel&lt;/color&gt; seeks out and eliminates nanites within the skeletomuscular and nervous system pathways.  It eliminates both the good and the bad effects of sensory and fibrous mechanites, and the good effects -- but not the bad -- of luciferium.

&lt;color=#C0C000&gt;Anti-malarials&lt;/color&gt; are artemesins and quinines capable of treating malaria.  Although nauseating, they can be mixed into tasty &lt;color=#C0C000&gt;tonic water&lt;/color&gt; or tastier &lt;color=#C0C000&gt;jinnantonyx&lt;/color&gt;, which can be rolled into your daily social regimen to give the benefits of immunity with the benefits of having fun.  Though only slightly less nausea.

&lt;color=#C0C000&gt;Endotide&lt;/color&gt; is a powerful psychoid analgesic for treating chronic pain.  Like most psychite-derived medications, it is somewhat addictive.  By "somewhat", I mean "quite".

&lt;b&gt;&lt;color=#009000&gt;Future:&lt;/color&gt;&lt;/b&gt;

* TODO: Similar to blood, prevent live organs from being frozen without resulting in degradation.  (Pro tip: Passive coolers will never drop below freezing.)  This significantly limits the game-breaking nature of a meat wagon economy, as you will not only need to have a source for the organs available at the time you require them, but also will need to have a buyer available or coming soon.  Organs will not remain viable for more than a few days.  (Note that I had intended for general freeze-degradation to be an entirely separate mod.  Which I will eventually get around to.  Eventually.)

* TODO: Enable incision wounds for vanilla surgeries.  Allow Shift-adding of elective amputations (with medicine) and harvesting of all organs and limbs (with medicine), with all vanilla harvesting operations otherwise always disabled.  Thereafter only medically necessary or at least generally legitimate procedures will show up without holding Shift, cutting down on clutter in emergencies.

* TODO: Mod Settings page to disable features you don't like (organ degradation and freeze-thaw, etc.), with no external configuration necessary.  (Note that I'm a huge fan of external configuration in general and I usually HATE being forced to go through in-game settings menus.  The mod's licence supports you making any changes you like.)

* TODO: Combat tourniquets which will cinch off a limb, causing continuous but slow asphyxiation damage to the limb in question but automatically halting all blood flow.  Automatic application of CATs to pawns with life-threatening bleeding as part of the give emergency treatment job driver, prior to recovery.

* TODO: Prosthetics can no longer be installed on healthy limbs; the limb must be absent or significantly damaged before the installation process can begin, as no doctor worth his licence would ever consider purely elective body modification of a patient.  Of course, since this is a rim world where half of the population hasn't even heard of licensing, back-alley meatwagons can still ply their trade by chopping off the undesired limbs first.

* TODO: Automatic bills to transfuse blood packs to patients with blood loss when they are in a bed and blood is available, to save annoying amounts of clicking.  A transfusion threshold (e.g., if blood loss severity is severe) would serve well here.

* TODO: Automatic job driver for transfusion of plasma or saline to injured pawns in the field, once they've been stabilised, prior to being brought back and given proper blood.

* TODO: Continuous blood loss even from tended wounds dependent on the tend quality, especially from internal organs, requiring frequent blood transfusions for badly wounded pawns.  External locations are easy to bandage and the tend quality percentage will be square-rooted to determine the amount staunched (so if your tend quality is 50%, then the square root of 0.5 is 0.75: 75% of the flow has been stopped, so blood will still leak at 25% of its former speed).  Internal locations are hard to bandage and the tend quality percentage will be taken directly (so if your tend quality is 15%, you've staunched only 15% of flow).  Presumably even 0% tending would reduce blood loss by a flat factor (say, 25%), with prorated levels of bleeding on higher tend qualities.  Be forewarned that the mortality rate for traumatic bleeding injury in medieval cultures was close to 100%: a thigh wound was expected to be fatal unless proven otherwise.  Because internal organs are so important and tending will not reduce their fatality rate as much as tending external flesh, it becomes meaningful to obtain transplant organs to treat ANY injury, rather than just to replace things for sake of organ trade.

* TODO: Asking NPCs and other visitors to provide voluntary blood donations, with or without compensation depending on their social relationship with your colonists and/or the pawn doing the asking.  Asking non-faction relatives of pawns with malignant organs to donate similar organs.

* TODO: Ironically, this mod is probably the only circumstance where Tynan's ridiculous surgery failures actually make sense, because if you're attempting to chop someone's hand off without anaesthetic, they're going to be thrashing around unless suitably restrained, especially if you're torturing the poor sot.  However, I'd like to finally do away with Tynan's ridiculous surgery failures for any other vanilla organ extraction or amputation.  Even in the worst case scenarios with the worst quacks that ever ducked, there is an inherent proximity of body parts necessary for a botched failure.  For instance, one may accidentally perform a surgery on the wrong body part (e.g., if there's a malignant lung, they will remove another part instead), or one may make too large and too rapid of a hacking cut and therefore also seriously damage either the parent limb or another of its child limbs (e.g., you may accidentally cut a little too close to the hip when amputating a thigh, or you may accidentally deeply incise the other leg when lopping off a leg with a meat cleaver).  However, one does not "accidentally" stab someone in the face when cutting off their big toe (so random parts are complete nonsense), and it is inherently ridiculous to chop off an arm when aiming at a completely separate section of the body (so a simple "is part also a child of my parent part" is insufficient).  I'd also do away completely with any other damage type than "cut" as a surgical result.

* TODO: I would really like to be able to extract organs from freshly-slain people for transplant -- no sense letting a needed heart go to waste just because the fellow kicked off before you could get there.  (The morality surrounding extracting a beating heart versus a recently-deceased heart is *more* frightening in the vanilla game, and it's evident that it was implemented solely in the interest of an amorphous concept of game balance... which would already be handily plugged with the freeze-degradation of organs and therefore a maximum limitation on the organs' lifespan no matter what.)  Most likely this would involve setting up their bodies on a special autopsy table, with their organs having degraded proportionally to time since death.  Realistically, soft tissue would be degraded by 100% within 6 hours of death (liver), muscle by 100% within 12 hours of death (heart, most limbs), and hard tissue by 100% within 30 hours (kidney), but these could easily be converted into tenths of a day for more reasonable playability, and for compatibility with other organ mods (0.6 days for soft tissue, 1.2 days for muscle, 3.0 days for hard tissue), a multiplier of 2.4.  Since health diffs are already visible on foreign pawns, there'd be no advantage to performing an autopsy for its intended purpose to diagnose cause of death, but it might be nice to include a "suspected cause of death" for glitz anyway.
</description>

</ModMetaData>
