<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<LanguageData>

<WTM_RequireRestart>You must restart the game for changes to take effect.</WTM_RequireRestart>

<WTM_FlagVanilla>Flag vanilla: </WTM_FlagVanilla>
<WTM_FlagVanilla_Desc>If enabled, vanilla objects will also be labeled using the custom name '{0}'.</WTM_FlagVanilla_Desc>
<WTM_VanillaName>Vanilla name: </WTM_VanillaName>

<WTM_VisualOptions>Visual options</WTM_VisualOptions>

<WTM_Format>Mod label format:</WTM_Format>
<WTM_Format_Desc>This allows you to customize how the mod name will be displayed. In this label {0} will be replaced with the mod name.\nSo, for example, typing ({0}) would result in mod names being displayed: (ModName), and typing xX{0}Xx would result in: xXModNameXx.</WTM_Format_Desc>
<WTM_Format_MissingTag>Invalid! You must include "{0}" in the format.</WTM_Format_MissingTag>
<WTM_Format_FormatError>Invalid! Tag format is invalid.</WTM_Format_FormatError>

<WTM_Italics>Italics: </WTM_Italics>
<WTM_Italics_Desc>If true, the mod name will be drawn in italics.</WTM_Italics_Desc>

<WTM_Bold>Bold: </WTM_Bold>
<WTM_Bold_Desc>If true, the mod name will be drawn bold.</WTM_Bold_Desc>

<WTM_CustomSize>Custom font size: {0}</WTM_CustomSize>
<WTM_CustomSize_Desc>Optional custom font size. Value of 0 means that the default Rimworld font size will be used.</WTM_CustomSize_Desc>

<WTM_SelectFontColor>Font color:</WTM_SelectFontColor>
<WTM_SelectFontColor_Desc>Change the font color. Can also change font transparency.</WTM_SelectFontColor_Desc>

<WTM_BlankLines>Blank lines: {0}</WTM_BlankLines>
<WTM_BlankLines_Desc>The number of blank lines to insert before the mod name. This can make it easier to see where the description ends and the mod name starts.</WTM_BlankLines_Desc>

<WTM_ExampleDescription>This is an example definition for an item.\nThis is a new line of the description, which might tell you about the item. Bla bla bla!</WTM_ExampleDescription>

<WTM_Show>Show</WTM_Show>
<WTM_Hide>Hide</WTM_Hide>
<WTM_AdvancedSettings>advanced settings</WTM_AdvancedSettings>

<WTM_AddNew>Add new</WTM_AddNew>
<WTM_RemoveBlank>Remove blank entries</WTM_RemoveBlank>

<WTM_ExcludedMods>Excluded mods</WTM_ExcludedMods>
<WTM_ExcludedMods_Desc>Here you can specify mods that will not be labeled. You must type the ID of the mod, not it's name.</WTM_ExcludedMods_Desc>

<WTM_ExcludedDefTypes>Excluded mods</WTM_ExcludedDefTypes>
<WTM_ModFound>Mod: {0}</WTM_ModFound>
<WTM_ModNotFound>Installed mod not found. Must type ID, not name!</WTM_ModNotFound>

<WTM_DetectPatched>Detect patched defs</WTM_DetectPatched>
<WTM_DetectPatched_Desc>If enabled, all active mod's patches are scanned to detect patched defs. This can catch some errors where patched items are not tagged correctly.
However, scanning all patches can be quite slow, especially with large mod packs.
You can check the debug log to see how long scanning patches took, and if you would rather the game load faster than have each and every item tagged, you should disable this option.</WTM_DetectPatched_Desc>

<WTM_UltraDeepMode>Deep patch scan</WTM_UltraDeepMode>
<WTM_UltraDeepMode_Desc>By default this mod will scan patches to look added items, however it will only scan the 'top level' of patches to speed up loading.
Enabling this option will make the entirety of all patches be scanned, which can be much slower but might catch some patched defs that would otherwise be missed.
Recommended to leave it disabled, as it is unlikely to have any effect but will always slow down loading.</WTM_UltraDeepMode_Desc>

<WTM_CECompat>Combat Extended compatibility</WTM_CECompat>
<WTM_CECompat_Desc>When enabled, the ammo stats will be added to the description of all combat extended ammunitions, making it easier to check ammo stats at a glance.</WTM_CECompat_Desc>
<WTM_AmmoStats>Ammo stats:</WTM_AmmoStats>

<WTM_LoadingMsg>(ノಠ益ಠ)ノ彡┻━┻ WHAT'S THAT MOD?!?</WTM_LoadingMsg>
<WTM_LoadingMsgZoo>WHAT'S THAT ANIMAL!? ლ(ಠ益ಠლ)</WTM_LoadingMsgZoo>
<WTM_ZooLabel>Zoo Mode</WTM_ZooLabel>
<WTM_ZooDesc>Created for Mr. Samuel Streamer's Jorassic Park series and community challenge.
Displays a 'zoo score' based on what tamed animals your colony has. Requires EdB Prepare Carefully to be installed.</WTM_ZooDesc>

<WTM_ZooMultiLabel>Multithreaded Zoo Counter</WTM_ZooMultiLabel>
<WTM_ZooMultiDesc>If enabled, the zoo score calculation will run on a background thread, greatly reducing framerate lag spikes. However, it may cause errors.
If the score does not work as expected, warnings appear in the debug log, or the score stops updating, disable this option.</WTM_ZooMultiDesc>

</LanguageData>