<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Defs>
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef Abstract="true" Name="UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>UpdateFeature</defName>
		<modNameReadable>Allow Tool</modNameReadable>
		<modIdentifier>AllowTool</modIdentifier>
		<linkUrl>https://ludeon.com/forums/index.php?topic=17218</linkUrl>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
	
	<!-- Note: these are probably not worth translating. This is a lot of text, and the player will only see this once -->
		
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>AllowTool_2_3_0</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>2.3.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>In-game options have been added for hiding unused tools (see Options &gt; Mod Settings).|The &lt;b&gt;Mass Select&lt;/b&gt; tool has become a lot more useful. When holding the Control key (Option on Mac), it will select only things of the same type as are already selected. This is great for selecting power conduits under walls, walls made only out of a certain material, all animals of a certain species, and many other things.</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
	
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>AllowTool_2_4_0</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>2.4.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>The Mass Select tool is now able to select all items or pawns of the same type across the whole map (Hold Alt and click).</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
	
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>AllowTool_3_0_0</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>3.0.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>&lt;b&gt;Massive update!&lt;/b&gt;|&lt;b&gt;New tools:&lt;/b&gt;|img:News/selectSimilar|caption:"Select similar" (formerly Mass select) allows to easily find and select only things similar to those already selected. Great for deconstruction and finding things around the map.|img:News/haulUrgently|caption:"Haul urgently" allows to have the marked items hauled before any other work is done. Holding Shift will have colonists interrupt current work and begin hauling immediately.|&lt;b&gt;Tool right-click menus:&lt;/b&gt;|img:News/contextMenuExample|caption:Tools with the small mouse icon now have a context menu that allows them to affect the whole map. To activate the context menu action for the tool you are holding, you can also press the "Context action" key ("Equals" by default).</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
	
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>AllowTool_3_2_0</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>3.2.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>&lt;b&gt;New tool:&lt;/b&gt;|img:News/finishOff|caption:"Finish off" allows to quickly and humanely clean up downed animals and raid survivors. Requires a colonist skilled in melee combat to carry out the order.</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
	
</Defs>