<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>Harsher Map Conditions</name>
	<author>MarvinKosh</author>
	<url>http://marvinkosh.omniloth.net</url>
	<targetVersion>Alpha 12</targetVersion>
	<description>This makes Cold Snap, Heat Wave and Volcanic Winter potentially more severe than before.

Cold Snap: Storyteller can now trigger as long as the seasonal temperature is 10C or below but not if it is already lower than -75C. The duration can be up to 4 months.
Heat Wave: Will no longer trigger if the seasonal temperature is over 32C. The duration can be up to 4 months.
Volcanic Winter: The duration can be as long as 20 months.
Flash Storm: Can opportunistically increase in frequency if the temperature is over 45C.

Version 1.0.0 introduces time-based multiplication of the temperature offsets. This is calibrated against the maximum duration set in the LongerSnapWaveAsh.xml file.

For Cold Snap and Volcanic Winter, this means that the extreme of cold will be reached fairly soon after the incident is triggered, and then taper off over time. The actual severity will depend on the random duration which is chosen, but should not exceed -50C for Cold Snap and -30C for Volcanic Winter.

For Heat Wave, this means the the extreme of heat will be reached gradually towards the end of the incident's duration, followed by a quick return to normal conditions. Again, the actual severity will depend on the random duration, but should not exceed +45C.

Solar Apocalypse: This event is extremely rare and will never occur in the ten years after crash landing. It will gradually render the surface of the planet uninhabitable due to extreme temperature. For sanity's sake, the default chance for this event is set to zero. You can modify this chance or trigger it from the debug menu. Your choice!

Version 1.0.3 adds checks to Cold Snap and Heat Wave so that they cannot fire while Solar Apocalypse is active. It also adds the possibility for more frequent Flash Storms if the outdoor temperature is over 45C.


[Version 1.0.3]
</description>
</ModMetaData>