<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Defs>
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef Abstract="true" Name="ATUpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>AllowToolUpdateFeature</defName>
		<modNameReadable>Allow Tool</modNameReadable>
		<modIdentifier>AllowTool</modIdentifier>
		<linkUrl>https://ludeon.com/forums/index.php?topic=17218</linkUrl>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
	
	<!-- Note: these are probably not worth translating. This is a lot of text, and the player will only see this once -->
		
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="ATUpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>AllowTool_2_3_0</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>2.3.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>In-game options have been added for hiding unused tools (see Options &gt; Mod Settings).|The &lt;b&gt;Mass Select&lt;/b&gt; tool has become a lot more useful. When holding the Control key (Option on Mac), it will select only things of the same type as are already selected. This is great for selecting power conduits under walls, walls made only out of a certain material, all animals of a certain species, and many other things.</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
	
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="ATUpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>AllowTool_2_4_0</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>2.4.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>The Mass Select tool is now able to select all items or pawns of the same type across the whole map (Hold Alt and click).</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
	
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="ATUpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>AllowTool_3_0_0</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>3.0.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>&lt;b&gt;Massive update!&lt;/b&gt;|&lt;b&gt;New tools:&lt;/b&gt;|img:images/selectSimilar|caption:"Select similar" (formerly Mass select) allows to easily find and select only things similar to those already selected. Great for deconstruction and finding things around the map.|img:images/haulUrgently|caption:"Haul urgently" allows to have the marked items hauled before any other work is done. Holding Shift will have colonists interrupt current work and begin hauling immediately.|&lt;b&gt;Tool right-click menus:&lt;/b&gt;|img:images/contextMenuExample|caption:Tools with the small mouse icon now have a context menu that allows them to affect the whole map. To activate the context menu action for the tool you are holding, you can also press the "Context action" key ("Equals" by default).</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
	
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="ATUpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>AllowTool_3_2_0</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>3.2.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>&lt;b&gt;New tool:&lt;/b&gt;|img:images/finishOff|caption:"Finish off" allows to quickly and humanely clean up downed animals and raid survivors. Requires a colonist skilled in melee combat to carry out the order.</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
	
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="ATUpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>AllowTool_3_4_0</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>3.4.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>&lt;b&gt;Cut blighted plants:&lt;/b&gt; marks all blighted plants on the map to be cut. Right-click the "Cut plants" tool to use.|&lt;b&gt;Cancel all of this type:&lt;/b&gt; cancels all designations found on the selected item across the whole map. Useful to undo accidentally issued commands that affect the whole map.</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
	
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="ATUpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>AllowTool_3_5_0</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>3.5.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>&lt;b&gt;New tools:&lt;/b&gt;|img:images/draftedHunt|caption:&lt;b&gt;Drafted hunt&lt;/b&gt; is a tool for manual hunting. When enabled, allows colonists to automatically target and finish off wild animals. Draft a colonist to use, right-click to change settings.|&lt;b&gt;Harvest/Chop fully grown&lt;/b&gt;: tools to mark only fully grown plants for harvesting and chopping, which improves resource yield. Right click the "Harvest" or "Chop" tools to use.</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>	
	
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="ATUpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>AllowTool_3_6_0</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>3.6.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>&lt;b&gt;Chop tool actions:&lt;/b&gt; added "Chop all wood" and "Chop all wood in home area" to the Chop tool's right-click menu.|&lt;b&gt;Pick Up And Haul compatibility:&lt;/b&gt; Haul Urgently will now use the custom (and more effective) hauling logic if the Pick Up And Haul mod is installed.</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
	
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="ATUpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>AllowTool_3_7_0</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>3.7.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>&lt;b&gt;New tools:&lt;/b&gt;|img:images/harvestGrown|caption:&lt;b&gt;Harvest fully grown:&lt;/b&gt; Harvesting fully grown things has been promoted to a separate tool, which can now be used in combination with "Select similar". Can selectively mark crops or trees only by holding Shift or Ctrl.|img:images/stripMine|caption:&lt;b&gt;Strip mine:&lt;/b&gt; all new tool to easily lay out mining orders in a grid to maximize the chance of finding ores.|&lt;b&gt;Other additions:&lt;/b&gt;|&lt;b&gt;Select similar in visible area:&lt;/b&gt; added to "Select similar" tool right-click menu.|&lt;b&gt;Customizable tool placement:&lt;/b&gt; other mods can now affect where in the menu the tools appear (most notably RIMMSqol).</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
	
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="ATUpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>AllowTool_3_10_0</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>3.10.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>
		&lt;b&gt;Improved "Allow" toggle:&lt;/b&gt; When something is selected, you can now Shift-click the Allow button to pick up the tool, and right-click it for map actions.|
		&lt;b&gt;New tool actions:&lt;/b&gt; "Allow/Forbid visible things" and "Select similar in home area" have been added to the right-click menus of their tools.|
		&lt;b&gt;Anima tree chopping:&lt;/b&gt; By popular demand, the "Cut", "Chop" and "Harvest fully grown" tools now ignore the Anima tree, unless ordered specifically.|
		&lt;b&gt;Performance improvements:&lt;/b&gt; Internals of the mod have been reworked to make it consume significantly fewer resources. Late-game colonies should see a noticeable improvement in frame rate.
		</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

</Defs>