<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<LanguageData>

  <NeedGenBioHopper>Need biogenerator hopper</NeedGenBioHopper>
  <NeedGenBioHopperDesc>You have a biogenerator with no hopper next to it.\n\nTo work, biogenerator must draw from an adjacent hopper filled with biomatter.\n\nBuild a hopper adjacent to the biogenerator.</NeedGenBioHopperDesc>

  <NeedFuelFeeder>Need fuel feeder</NeedFuelFeeder>
  <NeedFuelFeederDesc>You have a fuel power plant with no hopper next to it.\n\nTo work, fuel power plant must draw from an adjacent feeder filled with fuel or coal.\n\nBuild a feeder adjacent to the fuel power plant.</NeedFuelFeederDesc>

  <NeedGenHopper>Need steamgen hopper</NeedGenHopper>
  <NeedGenHopperDesc>You have a steam generator with no hopper next to it.\n\nTo work, steam generator must draw from an adjacent hopper filled with kindling or etanol fuel.\n\nBuild a hopper adjacent to the steam generator.</NeedGenHopperDesc>

  <NeedPlasmaGenFeeder>Need plasma reactor feeder</NeedPlasmaGenFeeder>
  <NeedPlasmaGenFeederDesc>You have a plasma geo reactor with no feeder next to it.\n\nTo work, plasma geo reactor must draw from an adjacent hopper filled with aluminium.\n\nBuild a hopper adjacent to the plasma geo reactor.</NeedPlasmaGenFeederDesc>

  <NeedNuclearFeeder>Need nuclear feeder</NeedNuclearFeeder>
  <NeedNuclearFeederDesc>You have a nuclear plant with no feeder next to it.\n\nTo work, nuclear power plant must draw from an adjacent feeder filled with either highly enriched uranium.\n\nBuild a feeder adjacent to the nuclear power plant.</NeedNuclearFeederDesc>

  <NeedCentrifugeFeeder>Need gas centrifuge feeder</NeedCentrifugeFeeder>
  <NeedCentrifugeFeederDesc>You have a gas centrifuge with no feeder next to it.\n\nTo work, a gas centrifuge must draw from an adjacent feeder filled with natural uranium.\n\nBuild a feeder adjacent to the a gas centrifuge.</NeedCentrifugeFeederDesc>

<NeedElectronicFeeder>Need electronic plant feeder</NeedElectronicFeeder> 
<NeedElectronicFeederDesc>You have a electronic plant with no feeder next to it.\n\nTo work, a electronic plant must draw from an adjacent feeder filled with electronic components.\n\nBuild a feeder adjacent to the electronic plant.</NeedElectronicFeederDesc> 

  <NeedCoalFeeder>Need coal feeder</NeedCoalFeeder>
  <NeedCoalFeederDesc>You have a coal power plant with no feeder next to it.\n\nTo work, a coal power plant must draw from an adjacent feeder filled with coal or peat.\n\nBuild a feeder adjacent to the a coal power plant.</NeedCoalFeederDesc>

  <AnotherGH>Too close to another geothermal heater.</AnotherGH>
  <NoGeothemalSource>No nearby geothermal source. Please find it.</NoGeothemalSource>
  <AnotherPG>Too close to another plasma generator</AnotherPG>

  <NoPlasmaGeothermalPlant>No nearby plasma geothermal reactor</NoPlasmaGeothermalPlant>

  <AnotherME>Too close to another mine extractor.</AnotherME>
  <AnotherPGR>Too close to another plasma reactor.</AnotherPGR>
  
  <AnotherFG>Too close to another drilling rig.</AnotherFG>
  <AnotherGG>Too close to another geothermal generator.</AnotherGG>
  
<OnMudOrWaterReportString>You can not collect here. Find the right place near with water or mud.</OnMudOrWaterReportString>

<DesignatorCollectSandLabel>Collect sand</DesignatorCollectSandLabel>
<DesignatorCollectSandDesc>Use to collect a sand.</DesignatorCollectSandDesc>
<DesignatorCollectSandReportString>You can not collect here. You need a sand.</DesignatorCollectSandReportString>

<DesignatorCollectPeatLabel>Collect peat</DesignatorCollectPeatLabel>
<DesignatorCollectPeatDesc>Use to collect a peat.</DesignatorCollectPeatDesc>
<DesignatorCollectPeatReportString>You can not collect here. You need a swamp to collect a peat.</DesignatorCollectPeatReportString>

<DesignatorCollectCrushedStoneLabel>Collect crushed stone</DesignatorCollectCrushedStoneLabel>
<DesignatorCollectCrushedStoneDesc>Use to collect a crushed stone.</DesignatorCollectCrushedStoneDesc>
<DesignatorCollectCrushedStoneReportString>You can not collect here. You need a gravel to collect a crushed stone.</DesignatorCollectCrushedStoneReportString>

<DesignatorCollectSnowLabel>Make snow block</DesignatorCollectSnowLabel>
<DesignatorCollectSnowDesc>Use to make snow block.</DesignatorCollectSnowDesc>
<DesignatorCollectSnowReportString>You can not collect here. You need ice terrain to collect a snow.</DesignatorCollectSnowReportString>

<DesignatorCollectSoftClayLabel>Collect clay</DesignatorCollectSoftClayLabel>
<DesignatorCollectSoftClayDesc>Designate areas of mud or shallow water to collect clay</DesignatorCollectSoftClayDesc>
<DesignatorCollectSoftClayReportString>Must designate mud or shallow water terrain</DesignatorCollectSoftClayReportString>

<NeedOilFeeder>Need oil refinery hopper</NeedOilFeeder>
<NeedOilFeederDesc>You have a oil refinery with no hopper next to it.\n\nTo work, oil refinery must draw from an adjacent hopper filled with crude oil.\n\nBuild a hopper adjacent to the oil refinery.</NeedOilFeederDesc>

<NeedHeaterHopper>Need heater hopper</NeedHeaterHopper>
<NeedHeaterHopperDesc>You have a stony heater with no hopper next to it.\n\nTo work, stony heater must draw from an adjacent hopper filled with coal or peat.\n\nBuild a hopper adjacent to the stony heater.</NeedHeaterHopperDesc>

<NearWithAnotherFissure>Too close to another fissure or mine extractor.</NearWithAnotherFissure>

  <NeedAntimatterReactorFeeder>Need antimatter reactor feeder</NeedAntimatterReactorFeeder>
  <NeedAntimatterReactorFeederDesc>You have a antimatter reactor with no feeder next to it.\n\nTo work, an antimatter reactor must draw from an adjacent feeder filled with antimatter.\n\nBuild a feeder adjacent to the an antimatter reactor.</NeedAntimatterReactorFeederDesc>

  <NeedHadronColliderFeeder>Need hadron collider feeder</NeedHadronColliderFeeder>
  <NeedHadronColliderFeederDesc>You have a hadron collider with no feeder next to it.\n\nTo work, a hadron collider must draw from an adjacent feeder filled with matter.\n\nBuild a feeder adjacent to the a hadron collider.</NeedHadronColliderFeederDesc>

  <Exhaustresource>Exhaust resource in:</Exhaustresource>
  <LetterLabelExaustedMine>Exhausted mine</LetterLabelExaustedMine>
  <ExhaustedMine>One of your mines exhausted. Disassemble it and build a new one.</ExhaustedMine>
  
  <LetterLabelExhaustedFissure>Exhausted oil fissure</LetterLabelExhaustedFissure>
  <ExhaustedFissure>One of your oil fissure exhausted. Disassemble oil extrator and drill a new one.</ExhaustedFissure>
  
</LanguageData>