<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<LanguageData>

  <CommandAddDangerZoneLabel>Create allow area</CommandAddDangerZoneLabel>
  <CommandAddDangerZoneDesc>Creates an area outside radiation danger radius.</CommandAddDangerZoneDesc>
  <DangerZoneLabel>Radiation danger area</DangerZoneLabel>

  <ContinueLabel>Continue</ContinueLabel>
  <QuickStartLabel>Quick Start</QuickStartLabel>
  
  <ImpassableDoor>The door can be placed if there is a support structure on both sides, and if nothing block pass through the door.</ImpassableDoor>
  
  <LookLabel>Ship crash found</LookLabel>
  <LookDiscA>We found the location of the ship wreck, perhaps spacer could have survived.</LookDiscA>
  <OnFissureReportString>Require fissure first!</OnFissureReportString>
  
  <RepTent>Repair the tent</RepTent>
  <TentneededRes>needed</TentneededRes>
  <DamagedTent>Damaged tent deployed. Some walls will be missing.</DamagedTent>
  <TentPlacementBlocked>Tent placement blocked by a item, pawn or a building. Please deploy on a suitable space.</TentPlacementBlocked>
  <NoResFoundOne>There is no</NoResFoundOne>
  <NoResFoundTwo>available to repair the tent</NoResFoundTwo>
  <NoResFoundTh>Need</NoResFoundTh>
  <TentPlacementBlockedTree>Tent placement blocked by a tree. Please deploy on a suitable space.</TentPlacementBlockedTree>
  <TentPlacementBlockedSimple>Tent placement blocked. Please deploy on a suitable space.</TentPlacementBlockedSimple>
  <CantPlaceTent>Cannot place a fully damaged tent.</CantPlaceTent>
  <DeployTentAt>Deploy tent at </DeployTentAt>
  
  <DeconstructConduitsLabel>Deconstruct Conduits</DeconstructConduitsLabel>
  
    <WarnAboutRestart>After changing the language, its highly recommended to restart the game. You can choose a different language, but before starting a new game or before load the savegame, please reboot. \ N \ nOtherwise, you can not avoid game errors during the game!</WarnAboutRestart>
	<AcceptTheConsequences>I accept the consequences</AcceptTheConsequences>

<RL_CannotChangeMod>Cannot change mode now, rod still discharging.</RL_CannotChangeMod>
<RL_ChangeMode>Change Mode</RL_ChangeMode>
<RL_PowerSavingMode>Power saving mode(Click to change modes): Does not consume power when idle, outputs a lot of power when struck, but only has a</RL_PowerSavingMode>
<RL_ChanceToAttract>chance to attract a lightning bolt and cools down</RL_ChanceToAttract>
<RL_Slower>slower</RL_Slower>
<RL_NormalMode>Normal mode(Click to change modes): Consumes a bit of power when idle, outputs enough power to sustain itself in a storm and has a 100% chance to attract a lightning bolt. Can attract lightning at a</RL_NormalMode>
<RL_ChanceOverwhelmed>chance when overwhelmed.</RL_ChanceOverwhelmed>
<RL_FastCooldown>Fast cooldown mode(Click to change modes): Cools down 4x faster than normal but consumes triple the amount of power. Has a 100% chance to attract a lightning bolt. Can attract lightning at a</RL_FastCooldown>
<RL_Cooldown>Cooldown</RL_Cooldown>
<RL_Standby>Standby.</RL_Standby>
<RL_Discharging>Discharging.</RL_Discharging>
<RL_Overwhelmed>Overwhelmed.</RL_Overwhelmed>
<RL_PowerConsumption>Power consumption</RL_PowerConsumption>

<OneTradingSpotMessage>Only one trading spot allowed per map.  Removing old spot.</OneTradingSpotMessage>

<HungryFlockTitle>Hungry critters</HungryFlockTitle>
<HungryFlockText>A pack of the hungry critters appeared nearby and they're out for blood! You can try hunting them, or hide, as you prefer. They'll leave the area in a few days.</HungryFlockText>

<DevourersCropsTitle>Devourers of crops</DevourersCropsTitle>
<DevourersCropsText>Some particularly hungry devourers of crops have made their way into your garden! They'll likely hang around and keep eating your crops (and other plants) until you deal with them.</DevourersCropsText>

<MoonFallMessageMeteorSwarm>A swarm of meteors -- possibly smaller pieces of your ship -- crosses the sky, burning up in the atmosphere.</MoonFallMessageMeteorSwarm>
<MoonFallMessageMeteorSwarmTribal>A swarm of meteors flame across the sky, but none crash to the ground near you.</MoonFallMessageMeteorSwarmTribal>

<SkyFallLetterLabelMeteorite>Large Ship Chunk</SkyFallLetterLabelMeteorite>
<SkyFallMeteorite>A lump of {0} just crashed to the ground. It was presumably once part of your ship, but the forces that ripped the ship apart, followed by the heat of uncontrolled reentry, have left nothing but a misshapen mass.</SkyFallMeteorite>

<MoonFallLetterLabelMeteoriteTribal>Meteorite</MoonFallLetterLabelMeteoriteTribal>
<MoonFallMeteoriteTribal>A large meteorite has struck ground in the area. It has left behind a lump of {0}.</MoonFallMeteoriteTribal>

<MoonFallLetterLabelFlashstorm>Flashstorm</MoonFallLetterLabelFlashstorm>
<MoonFallFlashstorm>Ionization in the atmosphere from the recent cascade of ship chunks and meteorites has caused a localized flashstorm. This can cause massive fires.</MoonFallFlashstorm>
<MoonFallFlashstormTribal>The gods are angry again, but instead of hurling rocks, they now hurl lightning. A flashstorm has begun. Beware of fires.</MoonFallFlashstormTribal>

<SkyFallRefugeePodCrash>You've detected an escape pod crashing hard nearby.\n\nThe occupant is an old acquaintance from your ship, who's agreed to join you.</SkyFallRefugeePodCrash>

</LanguageData>
