<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  
  <!-- EN: baseliner -->
  <Baseliner.label>первозданный</Baseliner.label>
  <!-- EN: A naturally-evolved human with no major significant genetic modifications. -->
  <Baseliner.description>Первозданный человек, практически не изменённый генной инженерией.</Baseliner.description>
  
  <!-- EN: dirtmole -->
  <Dirtmole.label>кроточеловек</Dirtmole.label>
  <!-- EN: With gray skin adapted to artificial light, they thrive in cramped and dark spaces where combat and travel happen over short distances. They are extremely capable at digging or mining tasks. In the open, however, they suffer from a sensitivity to light, slow speed and poor eyesight at distance.\n\nAfter the first tunnel colonies failed due to the stress of confinement, colonization agencies began genetically altering colonists to live without open space or sunlight. This xenotype is known colloquially as the dirtmoles. Today, dirtmoles have expanded out of their original tunnel homes and rule many confined spaces in the anthrosphere. They can be found in deep mines, cramped low-tech spacecraft, and teeming by the billions in the dark underlayers of countless urbworlds. -->
  <Dirtmole.description>Кротолюди прекрасно себя чувствуют в тесных и тёмных пространствах, их серая кожа адаптирована к отсутствию солнечного света. Они — прирождённые шахтёры. На открытой местности, однако, становятся очевидными все их слабые стороны: высокая светочувствительность, медлительность и плохое зрение.\n\nПосле того как первые шахтёрские колонии потерпели крах из-за невыносимых условий жизни в тоннелях, компании начали проводить генную модификацию колонистов, чтобы приспособить их к жизни в замкнутых помещениях и без солнечного света. В разговорной речи этот ксенотип чаще всего упоминается как кротолюди. На сегодняшний день кротолюди не ограничены родной планетой и населяют многие другие миры. Их часто можно встретить в глубоких шахтах или тесных внутренностях примитивных космических кораблей. Миллиардами они копошатся на подземных уровнях бесчисленных городских миров.</Dirtmole.description>
  <!-- EN: With gray skin adapted to artificial light, dirtmoles thrive in cramped and dark spaces where combat and travel happen over short distances. They are naturals at digging and navigating complex tunnel structures. In the open, they suffer from a sensitivity to light, slow speed and poor eyesight at distance. -->
  <Dirtmole.descriptionShort>Кротолюди прекрасно себя чувствуют в тесных и тёмных пространствах, их серая кожа адаптирована к отсутствию солнечного света. Они — прирождённые шахтёры. На открытой местности, однако, становятся очевидными все их слабые стороны: высокая светочувствительность, медлительность и плохое зрение.</Dirtmole.descriptionShort>
  
  <!-- EN: genie -->
  <Genie.label>инж</Genie.label>
  <!-- EN: Designed to be engineers, genies' delicate bones and natural aptitude with machines allow them to manipulate devices with remarkable precision. They are emotionally cold and can follow orders where others might panic. However, they are fragile, and their amplified nerve impulses make them easy to debilitate with relatively little pain. With so much of their brains dedicated to analyzing machines, they lack the neural hardware to analyze emotions, so they sometimes come off as socially inept. Their dead calm makes it even harder for them to relate to what they see as madly-hotheaded baseliner humans.\n\nGenies were engineered thousands of years ago by a long-disbanded space navy to hold engineering positions on large starships. Today, genies still serve as engineers in great cities and fleets, but many can also be found working as lawyers, pilots, and musicians. -->
  <Genie.description>Инжей выводили исключительно для технической работы, следствием этого стали их хрупкие кости и необычайная ловкость в работе с техникой любой сложности. Они хладнокровны и почти не поддаются панике, но их тела слабы, а болевой порог очень низок, что позволяет обезвреживать инжей почти без усилий. Инжи натренированны на постоянную работу с машинами и механизмами и испытывают дефицит эмоционального интеллекта, что очень сильно сказывается на их социальных навыках. Большинству из них обычные первозданные люди кажутся извергающимися вулканами страстей, с которыми очень тяжело взаимодействовать.\n\nИнжей создали тысячи лет назад для нужд давно забытого космического флота. Тогда они должны были занимать должности техников и инженеров на огромных космических кораблях. На этих должностях их и сегодня можно увидеть во многих городах и космических флотах, но иногда встречаются и инжи юристы, пилоты, и даже музыканты.</Genie.description>
  <!-- EN: Designed to be engineers, genies have natural aptitude with machines, and are emotionally cold and calm. They are also fragile and vulnerable to pain. Focused on machines, they often come off as socially inept. -->
  <Genie.descriptionShort>Инжей выводили для технической работы, следствием этого стала их необычайная ловкость в работе с техникой любой сложности и врождённое спокойствие. Их тела хрупки, а болевой порог очень низок. Привыкшие к обществу машин и механизмов, инжи страдают недостатком социальных навыков.</Genie.descriptionShort>
  
  <!-- EN: highmate -->
  <Highmate.label>ангел</Highmate.label>
  <!-- EN: Designed companions and concubines with a unique ability to psychically bond with a mate, highmates are empathic, beautiful, cheerful, and talented in social matters. They are also inept at manual tasks, physically weak, and mentally incapable of violence.\n\nOn a few wealthy worlds, highmate xenogerms are commercially available and some people become highmates as a sort of career. However, many societies find them abhorrent, either because they distract people from forming natural families, or because they are humans shaped to serve the pleasures of another. On such worlds they are either reserved as playthings of the powerful, or banned entirely. This particular line of highmate fits the fashions of classical Novaroma, but many other variants exist. -->
  <Highmate.description>Ангелов выводили как прирождённых компаньонов, наложниц и наложников. Эмпатичные, красивые, радостные, общительные и располагающие к себе, они также обладают уникальной способностью образовывать особую психическую связь при интимных контактах с другими людьми. Обратной стороной медали является их физическая слабость, неспособность к физическому труду и полное неприятие насилия в любой форме.\n\nВ некоторых богатых мирах ксеносемена ангелов находятся в открытой продаже, и некоторые люди добровольно имплантируют их себе, делая таким образом своеобразный «карьерный выбор». Тем не менее, во многих обществах такое глубоко порицается, чаще всего потому что потому что это отвлекает людей от создания настоящих семей и потому что ангелы были созданы для ублажения других людей. В таких случаях ангелы становятся лишь игрушками в руках власть имущих, либо же подвергаются полному запрету. Конкретно этот подвид ангелов соответствует классическим модным веяниям Новаромы, однако существуют и многие другие.</Highmate.description>
  <!-- EN: Designed companions and concubines with a unique ability to psychically bond with a mate, highmates are empathic, beautiful, cheerful, and talented in social matters. They are also inept at manual tasks, physically weak, and mentally incapable of violence. -->
  <Highmate.descriptionShort>Ангелов выводили как прирождённых компаньонов, наложниц и наложников. Эмпатичные, красивые, радостные, общительные и располагающие к себе, они также обладают уникальной способностью образовывать особую психическую связь при интимных контактах с другими людьми. Обратной стороной медали является их физическая слабость, неспособность к физическому труду и полное неприятие насилия в любой форме.</Highmate.descriptionShort>
  
  <!-- EN: hussar -->
  <Hussar.label>гусар</Hussar.label>
  <!-- EN: Hussars are engineered soldiers. They fight aggressively and with precision, heal fast, thrive in extreme temperatures, and freely ingest military drugs. They have a genetic dependence on go-juice, which also makes them less likely to rebel against their commanders.\n\nWhile hussars' emotions make them dangerous in combat, they can't relate to baseliner humans. They are famous for their blood-red eyes and "hussar stare", a dead expression that unsettles many people. Their lack of expression and burning aggressive nature has led to many violent misunderstandings.\n\nIn most societies where they live, hussars are kept separated from the rest of the population. Hussars are single-purpose tools - and they generally aren't bothered by the fact. -->
  <Hussar.description>Гусары — искусственно выведенные солдаты. Они агрессивно и эффективно сражаются, быстро восстанавливаются от ранений, прекрасно чувствуют себя в самых неблагоприятных температурных условиях и постоянно употребляют наркотики военного назначения. А заложенная в них генетическая зависимость от Go-сока, помимо прочего, понижает риск любых бунтов против их командиров.\n\nХоть взрывной характер гусар и является подспорьем в бою, на обычных первозданных людей они совсем не похожи. Их кроваво-красные глаза, безжизненное выражение лица и отрешённый «гусарский взгляд» на многих наводят ужас. Трудности с выражением эмоций и врождённая агрессивность гусар часто являются причиной недопониманий, переходящих в жестокие конфликты.\n\nВ большинстве миров их держат отдельно от всего остального населения. Гусары создавались исключительно для войны, но большинство из них этот факт мало волнует.</Hussar.description>
  <!-- EN: Hussars are engineered soldiers. They fight aggressively and with precision, heal fast, thrive in extreme temperatures, and freely ingest military drugs. They have a genetic dependence on go-juice. -->
  <Hussar.descriptionShort>Гусары — искусственно выведенные солдаты. Они агрессивно и эффективно сражаются, быстро восстанавливаются от ранений, прекрасно чувствуют себя в самых неблагоприятных температурных условиях и постоянно употребляют наркотики. В них заложена генетическая зависимость от Go-сока.</Hussar.descriptionShort>
  
  <!-- EN: impid -->
  <Impid.label>импид</Impid.label>
  <!-- EN: Made for desert life, impid cultures live on many rimworlds and dry deathworlds. Impids are extremely fast-moving, easily tolerate high temperatures, and can spew fire from their mouths. Though they are masters on the sand, impids struggle in other environments. They are terrible with farming. They fight well at range, but in close combat their physical weakness becomes apparent.\n\nOutlanders call them dustrunners because of their speed over open terrain and resistance to heat. Some tribes call them devils because of their horns and because they burn their enemies. Impid tribes' combat tactics usually center on rapid-approach incendiary attacks using both handheld fire weapons and their fire spew ability. -->
  <Impid.description>Выведенные для жизни в пустынях импиды населяют многие окраинные и засушливые мёртвые миры. Они очень быстрые, без проблем переносят высокие температуры и могут плеваться огнём. Импиды — повелители песков и дюн, но в других условиях испытывают трудности. Например, им неподвластно земледелие. Кроме того, импиды хороши только в дальнем бою, а в ближнем — их физическая слабость становится очевидной.\n\nНекоторые чужаки зовут их пустынными бегунами из-за способности последних быстро передвигаться по открытой местности и переносить высокие температуры. Другие же называют их чертями из-за рогов и способности изрыгать пламя. Боевая тактика импидов обычно сводится к быстрому сокращению дистанции и применению как огнестрельного зажигательного оружия, так и их врождённого.</Impid.description>
  <!-- EN: Made for desert life, impids are very fast, can spew fire from their mouths, and easily tolerate high temperatures. They fight well at range, but in close combat they do little damage. They are terrible with farming, and have weak immune systems. -->
  <Impid.descriptionShort>Выведенные для жизни в пустынях импиды очень быстрые, без проблем переносят высокие температуры и могут плеваться огнём. Импиды хороши в дальнем бою, но в ближнем бою они малоэффективны. Им неподвластно земледелие, и у них слабый иммунитет.</Impid.descriptionShort>
  
  <!-- EN: neanderthal -->
  <Neanderthal.label>неандерталец</Neanderthal.label>
  <!-- EN: Neanderthals are stocky, powerfully-built humanoids. Their most salient characteristic is that they are difficult to hurt: They are very resistant to injury, and their strong immune systems protect them from infection. However, without ever having evolved in a complex civilization, they are less adept than baseliner humans at intellectual and social tasks, and their impulsiveness can make them dangerously aggressive.\n\nHomo neanderthalensis was originally an archaic population of hominids that emerged over 200,000 years ago during the Pleistocene epoch. After they were replaced by and merged with humans 30,000 years ago, they were absent for tens of thousands of years until scientists resurrected them from ancient DNA. Neanderthals now survive in sub-societies on some settled planets. On the rimworlds, neanderthal tribes carve out the same existence as their Earth ancestors did so long ago. -->
  <Neanderthal.description>Коренастые и мускулистые гуманоиды. Наиболее заметным качеством неандертальцев является их поразительная стойкость: они очень устойчивы к ранениям и обладают сильным иммунитетом. С другой стороны, их цивилизация всегда оставалась примитивной, вследствие чего неандертальцы отстают от первозданных людей в интеллектуальном и эмоциональном развитии, а их импульсивность часто приводит к конфликтам и агрессии.\n\nНеандертальцы — подвид человека, возникший во время плейстоцена примерно двести тысяч лет назад. Около тридцати тысяч лет назад часть из них вымерла, другая же ассимилировались с Человеком разумным, после чего неандертальцы исчезли на десятки тысяч лет, пока учёные не возродили их с помощью древних образцов ДНК. В настоящее время на некоторых освоенных планетах неандертальцев можно встретить в виде отдельных общин. В окраинных же мирах их племена живут так же, как в незапамятные времена жили их предки на Земле.</Neanderthal.description>
  <!-- EN: Neanderthals are stocky, powerfully-built humanoids. They are hardy and difficult to injure, and their strong immune systems protect them from infection. However, their minds are less adept at intellectual and social tasks, and their impulsiveness can make them dangerously aggressive. -->
  <Neanderthal.descriptionShort>Коренастые и мускулистые гуманоиды. Наиболее заметным качеством неандертальцев является их поразительная стойкость: они очень устойчивы к ранениям и обладают сильным иммунитетом. С другой стороны, неандертальцы отстают от первозданных людей в интеллектуальном и эмоциональном развитии, а их импульсивность часто приводит к конфликтам и агрессии.</Neanderthal.descriptionShort>
  
  <!-- EN: pigskin -->
  <Pigskin.label>свиночеловек</Pigskin.label>
  <!-- EN: Pigskins are human-pig hybrids which are capable of two-legged movement, tool use, and speech, but which also retain many pig-like qualities. They are hardy and can eat almost anything without getting sick, but their trotter-shaped hands leave them at a disadvantage when attempting to precisely manipulate tools and objects. They don't see well at a distance, so pigskin gangs usually focus on close-range weapons. They also have a strong taste for explosives.\n\nPigskins were made for their organs. Uncomfortable with the idea of harvesting organs from baseliner humans, a long-gone government merged human DNA into pigs to make the animals produce more easily-transplantable hearts and lungs. They succeeded, but the resulting creatures became more humanlike than anyone anticipated. -->
  <Pigskin.description>Гибриды человека и свиньи, прямоходящие, обладают речью, способны использовать инструменты, при этом сохраняют много черт от свиней. Например, они могут есть почти что угодно, а их похожие на копыта руки не дают нормально держать предметы и пользоваться инструментами. У свинолюдей плохое зрение, поэтому их банды обычно выбирают оружие ближнего боя. Особое предпочтение они отдают взрывчатке.\n\nСвинолюдей выращивали на органы. Далеко в прошлом одно давно исчезнувшее правительство решило, что изъятие органов у первозданных людей — неэтично, а потому решило создать новый вид свиней, совместив ДНК человека и свиньи. Планировалось, что органы этих животных будут легче приживаться в телах новых хозяев, а сама процедура трансплантации будет проходить проще. Но в итоге эти «животные» оказались похожи на человека больше, чем кто-либо мог ожидать.</Pigskin.description>
  <!-- EN: Pigskins are human-pig hybrids. They are hardy and can eat almost anything without getting sick, but their trotter-shaped hands are bad at fine manipulation. They don't see well at a distance, so they usually focus on close-range weapons. They have a strong taste for explosives. -->
  <Pigskin.descriptionShort>Гибриды человека и свиньи. Они могут есть почти что угодно, а их похожие на копыта руки не дают нормально держать предметы и пользоваться инструментами. У свинолюдей плохое зрение, поэтому их банды обычно выбирают оружие ближнего боя. Особое предпочтение они отдают взрывчатке.</Pigskin.descriptionShort>
  
  <!-- EN: sanguophage -->
  <Sanguophage.label>гемофаг</Sanguophage.label>
  <!-- EN: Sanguophages are a type of archotech-enhanced xenohuman. Powered by archites, their abilities go far beyond normal genetic enhancements. They are mentally adept and preternaturally beautiful. In combat, they can launch deadly spines and heal injured friends. They don't age or die naturally and never suffer from disease or poison. A sanguophage can make a new sanguophage by reimplanting their own xenogerm into a person.\n\nSanguophages must regularly consume hemogen derived from human blood, and they must periodically deathrest for long periods. They're easily destroyed by fire, and slowed down by UV light.\n\nThe first sanguophage appeared thousands of years ago when the lord-explorer Varan-Dur sought to control a hyperintelligent archotech and found himself transformed by it instead. Every sanguophage is descended from him. Since then, sanguophages have often been hunted because of their destabilizing power and their need for blood. Since they can pass for baseliners, many live in hiding among typical humans.\n\nTheir numbers are unknown. Some think they are legends or rare irrelevancies. Some believe sanguophages secretly direct entire human civilizations. The stories speak of eternal lords ruling billions from slate-black space stations, or directing blood sacrifices at conferences in the underlayers of the deepest urbworlds. -->
  <Sanguophage.description>Гемофаги — ксенотип людей, улучшенных архотеками. Архиты наделяют их способностями, которые невозможно получить обычными генетическими модификациями. Они умны и невероятно красивы. В бою они способны стрелять смертоносными шипами и лечить раненых союзников. Гемофаги не стареют, им не страшны болезни и яды. Они могут вживлять своё ксеносемя в других людей, превращая тех в гемофагов.\n\nГемофагам необходимо регулярно употреблять гемоген, получаемый из человеческой крови, и входить в продолжительный торпор. Их злейший враг — огонь, а на солнечном свету они становятся медлительными.\n\nПервый гемофаг появился тысячи лет назад, когда исследователь лорд Варан-Дур захотел взять под свой контроль сверхразумного архотека, но вместо этого был им изменён. Все гемофаги происходят от него одного. С тех пор гемофагов часто преследуют из-за их сверхчеловеческих способностей и нужды в крови. Так как они могут выдавать себя за обычных первозданных людей, многие гемофаги живут среди них.\n\nНеизвестно даже примерное число гемофагов. Многие считают их легендой или слишком редким явлением, не заслуживающим внимания. Другие же верят в то, что гемофаги тайно правят целыми человеческими цивилизациями. Ходят слухи о вечных владыках, правящих миллиардами из своих чёрных, как ночь, космических крепостей и проводящих кровавые жертвоприношения на особых собраниях в глубинах самых густонаселённых городских миров.</Sanguophage.description>
  <!-- EN: Sanguophages are ageless, deathless super-humans powered by archotech-created archites in the bloodstream. They are beautiful and extremely intelligent. They can heal any injury, and never suffer from disease or poison. In combat, they can launch deadly spines and heal injured friends. The price is that sanguophages must consume hemogen derived from human blood to survive, and they must periodically deathrest for long periods. They're easily destroyed by fire, and slowed down by UV light. -->
  <Sanguophage.descriptionShort>Гемофаги — ксенотип людей, улучшенных архотеками. Архиты наделяют их способностями, которые невозможно получить обычными генетическими модификациями. Они умны и невероятно красивы. В бою они способны стрелять смертоносными шипами и лечить раненых союзников. Гемофаги не стареют, им не страшны болезни и яды. Гемофагам необходимо регулярно употреблять гемоген, получаемый из человеческой крови, и входить в продолжительный торпор. Их злейший враг — огонь, а на солнечном свету они становятся медлительными.</Sanguophage.descriptionShort>
  
  <!-- EN: waster -->
  <Waster.label>мусорщик</Waster.label>
  <!-- EN: Wasters are aggressive, immune to toxic pollution, almost impervious to disease, and can ingest as much psychite and wake-up drugs as they wish with no ill effects. Their toxin-adapted metabolism means they must consume some form of psychite - usually flake or yayo.\n\nOriginally engineered to prevent resettlement of post-apocalyptic deathworlds, wasters are living area-denial weapons. Waster pirates armed with toxic weapons are the bane of many frontier peoples, both on the rimworlds and in the depths of the urbworld hyperstructures. -->
  <Waster.description>Агрессивные ксенолюди, невосприимчивые к токсинам и загрязнению окружающей среды, обладающие иммунитетом почти ко всем болезням. Мусорщики способны употреблять неограниченное количество психина и бодрина без каких-либо побочных эффектов. Но в этом же кроется и основная проблема — для правильного обмена веществ мусорщикам постоянно требуется психин в какой-либо форме.\n\nИзначально выводившиеся для предотвращения заселения мёртвых пост-апокалиптических миров, мусорщики стали настоящим биооружием. Их пираты со своим токсичным арсеналом — настоящее проклятие как для жителей окраинных планет, так и для обитателей мегаструктур в городских мирах.</Waster.description>
  <!-- EN: Wasters are aggressive, immune to toxic pollution, almost impervious to disease, and can ingest as much psychite and wake-up drugs as they wish with no ill effects. Their toxin-adapted metabolism means they must consume some form of psychite - usually flake or yayo. -->
  <Waster.descriptionShort>Агрессивные ксенолюди, невосприимчивые к токсинам и загрязнению окружающей среды, обладающие иммунитетом почти ко всем болезням. Мусорщики способны употреблять неограниченное количество психина и бодрина без каких-либо побочных эффектов. Но в этом же кроется и основная проблема — для правильного обмена веществ мусорщикам постоянно требуется психин в какой-либо форме.</Waster.descriptionShort>
  
  <!-- EN: yttakin -->
  <Yttakin.label>иттакин</Yttakin.label>
  <!-- EN: Yttakin descend from colonists engineered to thrive on ultra-cold planets. Their great size and fur make them hardy in frozen environments. Yttakin share a psychic connection with the wildlife and can summon animals to their side during battles. They are not fast or energetic or precise, but can keep going when others would have collapsed long before.\n\nSince they migrated off their icy birthworld of Yttak, Yttakin settlements live on many planets. Their fur, roaring voices, and aversion to urban living sometimes leads naive outsiders to believe they are simple-minded animals. Quick-minded Yttakin are happy to make good use of such wrong beliefs, whether at the negotiating table or on the battlefield. -->
  <Yttakin.description>Иттакины происходят от людей, генетически модифицированных для колонизации сверххолодных планет. Их внушительный размер и мех помогают выживать в условиях суровых морозов. Иттакины обладают способностью психически воздействовать на животных, призывая их сражаться на своей стороне в битвах. Отсутствие ловкости, скорости и некоторую поверхностность восприятия они компенсируют нечеловеческой выносливостью.\n\nИттакины давно покинули свою родину, ледяной мир Иттак, и заселили множество других планет. Их мех, ревущие голоса и привычка избегать городов часто наталкивает наивных чужаков на мысли о том, что иттакины — не сложнее обычных животных. Те, в свою очередь, часто пользуются такими заблуждениями ради собственной выгоды как за столом переговоров, так и на поле боя.</Yttakin.description>
  <!-- EN: Yttakin descend from colonists engineered to thrive on ultra-cold planets. Their great size and fur make them hardy in frozen environments, and they have a unique ability to communicate vocally and psychically with animals. They are not fast or energetic or precise, but can keep going when others would have collapsed long before. -->
  <Yttakin.descriptionShort>Иттакины происходят от людей, генетически модифицированных для колонизации сверххолодных планет. Их внушительный размер и мех помогают выживать в условиях суровых морозов. Иттакины обладают способностью психически воздействовать на животных, призывая их сражаться на своей стороне в битвах. Отсутствие ловкости, скорости и некоторую поверхностность восприятия они компенсируют нечеловеческой выносливостью.</Yttakin.descriptionShort>
  
</LanguageData>