<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<ResearchProjectDefs>

  <ResearchProjectDef>
    <defName>ResearchMobileMineralSonar</defName>
    <label>M&amp;Co.: mobile mineral sonar</label>
    <description>   Your miners are getting bored of drilling galleries which never lead to the precious ore pockets. One of them was a deep-space miner in his youth and used to enjoy using Mining &amp; Co. sonar devices and spoke about it with a researcher.
You should give them some time to study the MiSoTech* core concept.

- Study the famous Mining &amp; Co. MiSoTech* to develop a mineral sonar able to scan and detect ore pockets in the heart of mountains.

* MiSoTech: Mineral Sonar Technology
    </description>
    <descriptionDiscovered>  By reverse-engineering the MiSoTech, you have developped an advanced sonar module able to detect all sort of ores through thick rock!

- You can now build mineral sonar modules at the electronic workbench.
- You can now build mobile mineral sonar. With this technology jewel, you will never have to dig galleries blindly!
- The mobile mineral sonar is a movable asset which requires a mineral sonar module and some energy packs.
    </descriptionDiscovered>
    <totalCost>350</totalCost>
    <prerequisites>
      <li>ElectricSmelting</li>
      <li>PowerII</li>
    </prerequisites>
  </ResearchProjectDef>

  <ResearchProjectDef>
    <defName>ResearchMineralSonarEnhancedScan</defName>
    <label>M&amp;Co.: mobile mineral sonar: enhanced scan</label>
    <description>   By doing some code refactoring in the MiSoTech* noise reduction algorithms, your researchers could improve the mobile mineral sonar efficiency.

- Improve the MiSoTech* to enhance the mobile mineral sonar efficiency.

* MiSoTech: Mineral Sonar Technology
    </description>
    <descriptionDiscovered>   MiSoTech* algorithms have been refactored and optimized. The spare CPU time has been reallocated to enhance the scan range and detection algorithms.

- Mobile mineral sonar scan range is increased (30 -> 50).
- Mobile mineral sonar detection chance is increased (30% -> 60%).

* MiSoTech: Mineral Sonar Technology
    </descriptionDiscovered>
    <totalCost>250</totalCost>
    <prerequisites>
      <li>ResearchMobileMineralSonar</li>
    </prerequisites>
    <researchMods>
      <li>
        <specialAction>MobileMineralSonar.Building_MobileMineralSonar.TryUpdateScanParameters</specialAction>
      </li>
    </researchMods>
  </ResearchProjectDef>

</ResearchProjectDefs>