<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<ModMetaData>
	<packageId>ChippedChap.BlueprintTotalsTooltip</packageId>
	<name>Blueprint Totals Tooltip</name>
	<author>ChippedChap</author>
	<supportedVersions><li>1.2</li><li>1.1</li></supportedVersions>
	<description>&lt;b&gt;Note:&lt;/b&gt; This mod requires HugsLib.

A UI mod that lets you seamlessly check how much your blueprints cost, even as you lay them down!

&lt;b&gt;Many thanks to these modders for providing translations to this mod!&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Proxyer - Japanese&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Zephyr  - Simplified and Traditional Chinese&lt;/b&gt;

The mod adds a tooltip that lists all the material costs and work left of blueprints visible on the screen. The visible blueprints are highlighted with a white transparent rectangle to help you see which blueprints are having their costs added up. 

To enable the tooltip, check the icon that looks like a clipboard on the bottom right corner of the screen. The highlighting rectangle and the tooltip should appear. You can use and assign a key to toggle this setting quickly.

If you want to find the costs of a certain set of blueprints, just select them and the selected blueprints will be highlighted and a tooltip showing their costs will be displayed. 

The tooltip by default will be positioned on the top right of the highlighting rectangle (as shown in the preview image). The position of the tooltip is configurable using the Mod Settings Menu and can be placed almost anywhere you like relative to the highlighting rectangle.

In addition, you can also change other things like the opacity of the highlighting rectangle, how far away from the edge of the screen a blueprint has to be to be considered visible, and how the tooltip decides if you have enough of a certain material.

A large percentage of development time was sunk into making the tracking of blueprints smooth and fast, but if your computer can't handle it, you can disable visibility tracking or change at what zoom visibility tracking stops.

Visibility tracking is optimized by updating visible blueprints only when it is necessary (when the camera moves or zooms, when new blueprints are added, ect.) If you find a special case where the tracked blueprints aren't updating right, please post &lt;b&gt;exactly&lt;/b&gt; what you did on the workshop page or as a GitHub issue so that it can be fixed.
	</description>
	<modDependencies>
		<li>
			<packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
			<displayName>Harmony</displayName>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
			<downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
		</li>
		<li>
			<packageId>UnlimitedHugs.HugsLib</packageId>
			<displayName>HugsLib</displayName>
			<downloadUrl>https://github.com/UnlimitedHugs/RimworldHugsLib/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/818773962</steamWorkshopUrl>
		</li>
	</modDependencies>
	<loadAfter>
		<li>UnlimitedHugs.HugsLib</li>
	</loadAfter>
</ModMetaData>