<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Defs>
	<RR_PawnBadge.BadgeDef>
		<defName>xcomRookie</defName>
		<label>Rookie</label>
		<description>A Rookie is a fresh Soldier who lacks a specialized class.

Rookies are only able to use Rifles as their primary weapons, and lack a secondary weapon, though they are able to equip any type of armor and are able to use items.</description>
		<icon>PawnBadge/01-rookie</icon>
	</RR_PawnBadge.BadgeDef>
	
	<RR_PawnBadge.BadgeDef>
		<defName>xcomSquaddie</defName>
		<label>Squaddie</label>
		<description>The Squaddie rank is the first primary rank of soldiers.

A soldier at this rank may specialise into one of the 5 classes. To achieve this rank, a Soldier needs about one kill worth of experience.</description>
		<icon>PawnBadge/02-squaddie</icon>
	</RR_PawnBadge.BadgeDef>
	
	<RR_PawnBadge.BadgeDef>
		<defName>xcomCorporal</defName>
		<label>Corporal</label>
		<description>The Corporal rank is the second rank available to soldiers.

To achieve this rank, a Soldier needs about six kills worth of experience.</description>
		<icon>PawnBadge/03-corporal</icon>
	</RR_PawnBadge.BadgeDef>
	
	<RR_PawnBadge.BadgeDef>
		<defName>xcomSergeant</defName>
		<label>Sergeant</label>
		<description>The Sergeant rank is the third rank available to soldiers.

A soldier at this rank unlocks a nickname, in addition to a new ability. To achieve this rank, a Soldier needs about twelve kills worth of experience.</description>
		<icon>PawnBadge/04-sergeant</icon>
	</RR_PawnBadge.BadgeDef>
	
	<RR_PawnBadge.BadgeDef>
		<defName>xcomLieutenant</defName>
		<label>Lieutenant</label>
		<description>The Lieutenant rank is the fourth rank available to soldiers.

To achieve this rank, a Soldier needs about twenty-four kills worth of experience.</description>
		<icon>PawnBadge/05-lieutenant</icon>
	</RR_PawnBadge.BadgeDef>
	
	<RR_PawnBadge.BadgeDef>
		<defName>xcomCaptain</defName>
		<label>Captain</label>
		<description>The Captain rank is the fifth rank available to soldiers.

To achieve this rank, a Soldier needs about fourty-two kills worth of experience.</description>
		<icon>PawnBadge/06-captain</icon>
	</RR_PawnBadge.BadgeDef>
	
	<RR_PawnBadge.BadgeDef>
		<defName>xcomMajor</defName>
		<label>Major</label>
		<description>The Major rank is the sixth rank for soldiers.

To achieve this rank, a Soldier needs about sixty kills worth of experience.</description>
		<icon>PawnBadge/07-major</icon>
	</RR_PawnBadge.BadgeDef>
	
	<RR_PawnBadge.BadgeDef>
		<defName>xcomColonel</defName>
		<label>Firefight</label>
		<description>The Colonel rank is the seventh and final rank available to soldiers.

To achieve this rank, a Soldier needs about eighty-five kills worth of experience.</description>
		<icon>PawnBadge/08-colonel</icon>
	</RR_PawnBadge.BadgeDef>
	
	<RR_PawnBadge.BadgeDef>
		<defName>xcomGrenadier</defName>
		<label>Grenadier</label>
		<description>Serving as our demolitions experts, the Grenadiers provide heavy ordnance delivery whenever and wherever we need it.

As their name suggests, Grenadiers have access to a unique grenade-only equipment slot that stacks with any other utility items the operative might be carrying: this is not just limited to frag grenades, but can be filled with any one of the specialized grenades XCOM can develop.

The Grenadier class is equipped with a minigun-style cannon and a grenade launcher, being able to choose to specialize in demolitions, focus more on making the most of their cannon or go for a combination of the two.</description>
		<icon>PawnBadge/grenadier</icon>
	</RR_PawnBadge.BadgeDef>
	
	<RR_PawnBadge.BadgeDef>
		<defName>xcomPsiOperative</defName>
		<label>Psi Operative</label>
		<description>A mysterious new branch of study for XCOM, the Psionic Operative utilizes their mental abilities to great effect to boost their allies and cripple the will of enemies.

The Psi Operative class uses Assault Rifles as primary weapons, and a hand-held Psi Amp as their secondary weapon, which they will automatically use when casting psionic abilities.</description>
		<icon>PawnBadge/psioperative</icon>
	</RR_PawnBadge.BadgeDef>
	
	<RR_PawnBadge.BadgeDef>
		<defName>xcomRanger</defName>
		<label>Ranger</label>
		<description>The Ranger serves as our primary reconnaissance unit, capable of moving independently in concealment while engaging enemies at close range using extensive training in swordsmanship.

The Ranger class can utilize either shotguns or rifles as primary weapons. As a secondary weapon, Rangers use a sword to deal a hard-hitting melee attack.</description>
		<icon>PawnBadge/ranger</icon>
	</RR_PawnBadge.BadgeDef>
	
	<RR_PawnBadge.BadgeDef>
		<defName>xcomSharpshooter</defName>
		<label>Sharpshooter</label>
		<description>Just like it sounds, our sharpshooters engage enemy targets with pinpoint accuracy from extreme range. They're also trained in pistol marksmanship for the occasional close encounter.

The Sharpshooter class utilizes high-caliber sniper rifles as primary weapons and pistols as secondaries.</description>
		<icon>PawnBadge/sharpshooter</icon>
	</RR_PawnBadge.BadgeDef>
	
	<RR_PawnBadge.BadgeDef>
		<defName>xcomSpecialist</defName>
		<label>Specialist</label>
		<description>Operating some of our most advanced equipment, Specialists deploy robotic drones on the battlefield that can be outfitted for combat or field medic duty.

Through their flying GREMLIN the Specialist can take on a variety of tactical support roles including healing, support buffs, boosting stats and remote hacking.

Specialists utilize the Assault Rifle and its upgraded forms as their primary weapon, and the GREMLIN is considered to be their secondary weapon.</description>
		<icon>PawnBadge/specialist</icon>
	</RR_PawnBadge.BadgeDef>
</Defs>