<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>Extended Human Body Simulation v1.0.0</name>
	<author>PhileasFogg</author>
	<url>https://ludeon.com/forums/index.php?topic=34214.0</url>
	<targetVersion>0.18.0</targetVersion>
	<description>Integrates these features into RimWorld:
- An extended simulation system for human bodies (fibulas, ulnas, etc.)
- Buyable artificial bones to replace missing ones
- Harvestable bodyparts and reingration of those

"Extended Human Body Simulation" is needed for "Disease overhauled" and "Crafted Mutants". Must be loaded before these two mods (above them in your mod list).


Credits and Thanks to...
 - Ykara, for his/her both fantastic mods, which I used as a basis for this mod: "EPOE (Expanded Prosthetics and Organ Engineering)" and "Harvest Everything!"
 - Marnador, for the RimWor(l)d font, used in the picture above.
 - Tynan, for this great game!
	
[Russian]

Мод Extended Human Body Simulation для Rimworld — является системным модом. Расширяет возможности хирургии, а именно: расширенные возможности по добавлению / удалению разных частей тела (3 глаза, 3 руки и тд)

Интегрирует новые функции в RimWorld:
- Расширенная система моделирования для органов человека (фибулы, ульны и т.д.).
- Покупка искусственных костей для замены отсутствующих.
- Убираемые тела и реинтеграция имплантов.

Мод "Extended Human Body Simulation" необходим модам "Disease overhauled" и "Crafted Mutants". Должен быть загружен перед этими двумя модами (над ними в вашем списке мод).
	
[Spanish]

Integra estas características a RimWorld:
	- Un sistema de simulación extendido para cuerpos humanos (fibulas, ulnas, etc.)
	- Huesos artificiales adquiribles para reemplazar los desaparecidos
	- Partes del cuerpo Harvestable y reingración de aquellos

"Extended Human Body Simulation" es necesario para "Disease overhauled" y "Crafted Mutants". Debe cargarse antes de estas dos modificaciones (encima de ellas en su lista de mods).

Créditos y gracias a ...
  - Ykara, por sus fantásticas modificaciones, que utilicé como base para este mod: "EPOE (Expanded Prosthetics and Organ Engineering)" y "Harvest Everything!"
  - Marnador, para la fuente RimWorld, utilizada en la imagen de arriba.
  - Tynan, por este gran juego!
	</description>
</ModMetaData>
