<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <WorkSpeedGlobal.label>Velocidad de trabajo general</WorkSpeedGlobal.label>
  <WorkSpeedGlobal.description>Un multiplicador sobre la velocidad general de cualquier trabajo.</WorkSpeedGlobal.description>

  <MiningSpeed.label>Velocidad de minería</MiningSpeed.label>
  <MiningSpeed.description>Un multiplicador sobre la velocidad a la que esta persona mina las rocas.</MiningSpeed.description>

  <MiningYield.label>mining yield</MiningYield.label>
  <MiningYield.description>The percentage yield a miner will achieve. This applies to both wall mining and deep drill mining. This doesn't affect the rate of mining rock chunks.</MiningYield.description>

  <SmoothingSpeed.label>Velocidad de alisar</SmoothingSpeed.label>
  <SmoothingSpeed.description>Un multiplicador sobre a la velocidad a la que esta persona alisar el suelo.</SmoothingSpeed.description>

  <ResearchSpeed.label>Velocidad de investigación</ResearchSpeed.label>
  <ResearchSpeed.description>Un multiplicador sobre a la velocidad a la que esta persona investiga.</ResearchSpeed.description>

  <AnimalGatherSpeed.label>animal gather speed</AnimalGatherSpeed.label>
  <AnimalGatherSpeed.description>The speed at which this person milks, shears, and otherwise gathers resources from animals.</AnimalGatherSpeed.description>

  <AnimalGatherYield.label>animal gather yield</AnimalGatherYield.label>
  <AnimalGatherYield.description>The percentage yield someone receives when they shear, milk, or otherwise gather resources from a living animal. Higher percentages reduce the chance of wasting the product.</AnimalGatherYield.description>

  <PlantWorkSpeed.label>Velocidad de agricultura</PlantWorkSpeed.label>
  <PlantWorkSpeed.description>Un multiplicador sobre a la velocidad a la que esta persona planta y cosecha las plantas.</PlantWorkSpeed.description>

  <PlantHarvestYield.label>plant harvest yield</PlantHarvestYield.label>
  <PlantHarvestYield.description>The yield someone gets when harvesting plants. Low yields give a chance that this person will accidentally waste the harvest.</PlantHarvestYield.description>

  <ConstructionSpeed.label>Velocidad de construcción</ConstructionSpeed.label>
  <ConstructionSpeed.description>Un multiplicador sobre a la velocidad a la que esta persona construye estructuras.</ConstructionSpeed.description>

  <ConstructSuccessChance.label>construct success chance</ConstructSuccessChance.label>
  <ConstructSuccessChance.description>The chance that this person will succeed in constructing something. Failing means wasting time and resources.</ConstructSuccessChance.description>

  <FixBrokenDownBuildingSuccessChance.label>repair success chance</FixBrokenDownBuildingSuccessChance.label>
  <FixBrokenDownBuildingSuccessChance.description>The chance that this person will successfully repair a broken down building using a component. Failing means wasting time and resources. Note that this only applies to repairing breakdowns, which is different from repairing damage.</FixBrokenDownBuildingSuccessChance.description>

</LanguageData>