<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
    <name>RocketMan - Performance Mod</name>
    <author>Krkr</author>
    <supportedVersions>
        <li>1.2</li>
    </supportedVersions>
    <packageId>NotooShabby.RocketMan</packageId>
    <modDependencies>
        <li>
            <packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
            <displayName>Harmony</displayName>
            <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
            <downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
        </li>
        <li>
            <packageId>UnlimitedHugs.HugsLib</packageId>
            <displayName>HugsLib</displayName>
            <downloadUrl>https://github.com/UnlimitedHugs/RimworldHugsLib/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
            <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/818773962</steamWorkshopUrl>
        </li>
    </modDependencies>
    <loadAfter>
        <li>brrainz.harmony</li>
        <li>UnlimitedHugs.HugsLib</li>
        <li>skyarkhangel.HSK</li>
    </loadAfter>
    <incompatibleWith>
        <li>rwmt.Multiplayer</li>
        <li>majorhoff.rimthreaded</li>
    </incompatibleWith>
    <description>
[BETA] RocketMan:

RocketMan is mod that is designed to improve RimWorld Performance.

Important note: RocketMan should be the last mod in your mod list.

Features:

1- Time dilation: time dilation is a feature of RocketMan where it throttles the tick rate of animals and world pawns from 60 Hz to 5 Hz. This allows you to have hundreds of world pawns and animals on your map with almost no performance impact. This removes the need for RuntimeGC since world Pawns are no longer an issue. This will lead to a huge performance impact on large maps and old colonies. (+150 TPS on avg)
2- Statistics caching: RimWorld; without RocketMan, will do the same calculations for stats every tick. RocketMan allows you to cache these results thus removing 90% of the vanilla overhead. This will result in a modest performance impact. (+30 TPS on avg)
3- GlowGrid rework: RimWorld has a very bad implementation of the lighting grid. It basically recalculates the entire light grid for the entire map any time a change occurs such as a light bubble being switched on/off or fire. RocketMan makes the updates only occur in the relevant areas. This will result in a smoother game experience and generally removing light related lag spikes. This will help greatly with mods that have lighting effects in them by eliminating staturing.
4- World Reachability Checks: RocketMan when first loading the game creates a table containing the reachability data for each planet tile. Thus making the process of finding if a tile is reachable from another tile almost O(1) or one operation.
5- Pathfinding Stability: RocketMan will detect pathfinding errors and fix them to some degree.
6- Corpse Removal: RocketMan will remove dead corpses from the map when some conditions are met. RocketMan will not remove corpses that are always within your sight or near to your base to preserve the game balance. It will remove corpses near the edge of the map or outside your base in 7 days on average. This removes entirely the need for RuntimeGC since RocketMan does the same function but in a smart manner. 
7- Game Log Removal: RocketMan will automatically trim your game log to insure smoother operations further removing the need for RuntimeGC.


Notes: 

1- RocketMan doesn't support RimThreaded and never will.
2- Bug reports with no logs will not get a response.

Github Link: https://github.com/kbatbouta/RocketMan

RocketMan is OpenSource and for anyone to use, modify, update.

Credits: 

The main developer: Karim (aka Krkr)
The Thumbnail: Trisscar.
The original concept of Stat caching: Notooshabby.

DISCLAIMER: I’m not responsible in any way for damage done by RocketMan to your saves. RocketMan has been tested for over 9 months. Any damage done to your save is probably your own fault since RocketMan has been tested for so long. 

Special Thanks goes to:

Madman666 the entire Dubwise server for the help and testing they provided!
Trisscar for their awesome thumbnail.
Dubwise for hosting me on their discord server.
Wiri for his awesome contribution.
Bad Vlad (ModderK) for their awesome feedback.
Brrainz for Harmony and ZombieLand which inspired my time dilation solution.

You can always ask questions on the Dubwise discord server: https://discord.gg/mKVDMqq4
    </description>
</ModMetaData>
