<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>Rumours And Deception</name>
  <author>SeveralPuffins</author>
  <targetVersion>0.16.0</targetVersion>
  <description>Have you ever wondered why your colonists don't talk about each other? Did no-one wonder about sending that shifty cannibal Alex to bury the dead? How come Ray likes the abrasive psycho that beat up her friend, just because she's never been insulted directly? And why is no-one ever apologetic about anything they've done?

If you want more social complexity, or just plain gossip and intrigue in your stories, then look no further! Rumours and Deception adds several new colonist social interactions, traits and thoughts that largely focus on people talking about people. 

New interactions:
- Chat about other colonists: Alice likes Bob. Bob hates Carol. Bob can now tell Alice this!
- Spread rumour: Colonists will tell nasty, unsubstantiated tales to each other, particularly about colonists that neither of them like.
- Share secret: A colonist can trust another enough to reveal something deep and personal, bringing them closer together.
- Reveal secret: There's no guarantee that all trust is well placed! Colonists that have been told a secret can go and gossip about it to their friends!
- Apologise: Colonists can try to make up with others that they've insulted or hurt.
- Make peace: Colonists may try and apologise on behalf of a third party.
- Culture clash: Not all insults are intended! One may insult another due to having a poor understanding of their background culture (for example, Tribal vs GlitterWorld culture clashes).


New traits:
- Compulsive liar: This colonist just can't help it- every conversation is an opportunity to make up some new, snide story about one of the others.
- Gushing: This colonist just cannot judge who to trust with their darkest secrets, exposing themselves to potential embarrassment.
- Gossip: This colonist talks about other people all the time. This extends to secrets, with which they can't be trusted.
- Manipulative: This colonist will use any social trick they know to make other people see things THEIR way. They are great negotiators, but can be divisive and isolating within a colony.
- Trustworthy: This colonist keeps secrets. They rarely spread rumours, and if they do they feel terrible about it.
- Peacemaker: This colonist can't stand to see their friends fighting. They will try to resolve other people's differences, and will get a mood boost if successful.

New events:
- Defection: A socially isolated colonist will suffer mood penalties and very regular mental breaks. If they remain friendless, they may, occasionally, walk off the map and join an ally (currently suspended while HugsLib updates).
- Splinter: In the unlikely event that a clique of friends forms within the colony that is largely hostile to the rest, they may choose to leave together and form a new map faction. They will take some of your colony's belongings with them as they go (currently suspended while HugsLib updates. Will be replaced with leaving caravan). 
- Brawl:    Even if cliques don't leave, they may still start fights! 

Compatibility:
As A16 has only just been released, this mod is untested against others, but should play nicely with most things. Let me know if it doesn't!

Updates:
14.11.2016: 
Based on initial feedback, I've made the following changes:
- Tweaked shared secret and spread rumour event likelihoods down. 
- Made revealing secrets depend on the colonist's opinion of the third party, making it less likely to reveal friends' secrets.
- Fixed a bug allowing for cheerful conversation with enemies.
- Fixed a bug where colonists gossip about people their visitors don't know.
- Made defection much less likely, but introduced regular mental breaks for socially isolated pawns.

05.12.2016: 
- Added menu options, allowing players to disable splits and defections. 
- Married/Engaged/Dating Colonists on either side of a defection will now split up.
- Split risk lowered.
- Introduced brawl events, so that even without splits there is a downside to a strongly divided colony.

21.12.2016:
- Updated to A16. New interaction events apply only to pawns on maps, and do not seem to influence caravan members on the world map. Events on hold until the HugsLib menu mod is A16 compatible!
</description>

</ModMetaData>