<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- <LanguageData>

  <!-- Added Shell to layers so can't double equip with items such as Vambraces -->

  <Apparello_chefglove.label>Oven Mitts</Apparello_chefglove.label>
  <Apparello_chefglove.description>A pair of heat resistant oven mitts for cooks.</Apparello_chefglove.description>

  <Apparello_Workglove.label>Leather Gloves</Apparello_Workglove.label>
  <Apparello_Workglove.description>A pair of hardened leather gloves, commonly used by most craftsmen.</Apparello_Workglove.description>

  <Apparello_ReinforcedGlove.label>Reinforced Gloves</Apparello_ReinforcedGlove.label>
  <Apparello_ReinforcedGlove.description>Tyke Bison allegedly hid one of these under his boxing glove during a match. Luckily not a single blow was exchanged before Tyke had already bitten his opponent's nose off. The hit with the powered glove could of killed the poor man.</Apparello_ReinforcedGlove.description>

  <Apparello_Motorglove.label>Leather Grips</Apparello_Motorglove.label>
  <Apparello_Motorglove.description>Fingerless leather gloves with real steady, gripping abilities. (Worn on both hands, 1st layer)</Apparello_Motorglove.description>

  <MedievalTimes_Gloves_Combat.label>Combat Gloves</MedievalTimes_Gloves_Combat.label>
  <MedievalTimes_Gloves_Combat.description>Mass produced combat gloves made of synthetics and metal inserts. Nano-stretch materials and contouring hyper-foam ensure a comfortable fit for any hand type while the nano-tactile receivers ensure a good no-slip grip. Military personal have often commented that the gloves feels like rubber covered in stickum. These gloves are truly a necessity for either hand to hand or ranged combat</MedievalTimes_Gloves_Combat.description>

  <Apparello_Snipeglove.label>Stabilizer Gloves</Apparello_Snipeglove.label>
  <Apparello_Snipeglove.description>The antiswerve-adjustor installed in these gloves has made it a particular favorite of snipers.</Apparello_Snipeglove.description>

  <Apparello_SoothingLove.label>Soothing Gloves</Apparello_SoothingLove.label>
  <Apparello_SoothingLove.description>Basic leather gloves rigged up with an intricate injection device with beautiful purple liquid inside. Soothes your nerves and lets you act in stressful situations.</Apparello_SoothingLove.description>

  <Apparello_docglove.label>Doctor's Cutters</Apparello_docglove.label>
  <Apparello_docglove.description>Rubbery and clinical. It has very sharp scissors strapped on it. What could possibly go wrong?</Apparello_docglove.description>

  <Apparello_docglovetwo.label>Doctor's Pincers</Apparello_docglovetwo.label>
  <Apparello_docglovetwo.description>Rubbery and clinical. It has very claspy pincers strapped on it.</Apparello_docglovetwo.description>

  <Apparello_Snipeglovetwo.label>Discharger Gloves</Apparello_Snipeglovetwo.label>
  <Apparello_Snipeglovetwo.description>The microscopic exoskeleton in the gloves gives the wearer a quick and steady grip when squeezing the trigger.</Apparello_Snipeglovetwo.description>

  <Apparello_CalmingLove.label>Calmax Gloves</Apparello_CalmingLove.label>
  <Apparello_CalmingLove.description>Basic leather gloves rigged up with an intricate injection device with glowing green liquid inside. Calms your nerves and lets you act in stressful situations.</Apparello_CalmingLove.description>

  <MedievalTimes_Gauntlets_Techno.label>Techno Gauntlets</MedievalTimes_Gauntlets_Techno.label>
  <MedievalTimes_Gauntlets_Techno.description>Custom made by Interstellar Industries, these high end combat gauntlets are made almost entirely of Nanite recursive synthetics and metal plating. These little alpha's come with Omega-weave electric stranding, thermo-dynamic assist functions and even nano-tactile receivers to ensure a good no-slip grip. Even with all that they found room for MilCo's patented Aim-Assist+.  Nano-stretch materials and contouring hyper-foam ensure a comfortable fit for any hand type. These gloves are a favourite of any soldier lucky or rich enough that they can get their hands in them. Rarely seen outside of the most luxurious of glitter-worlds. These gloves are truly a godsend for either hand to hand or ranged combat</MedievalTimes_Gauntlets_Techno.description>

  <Apparello_Gamerglove.label>Power Gloves</Apparello_Gamerglove.label>
  <Apparello_Gamerglove.description>When you need your melee strikes to hit harder, you wear a pair of hex-cell fueled power gloves.</Apparello_Gamerglove.description>


</LanguageData> -->