<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>

	<name>Core SK - Fertile Fields</name>
	<author>Rainbeau Flambe and Jamaican Castle</author>
	<url>https://ludeon.com/forums/index.php?topic=46165</url>
	<supportedVersions><li>1.1</li><li>1.2</li><li>1.3</li><li>1.4</li></supportedVersions>
	<packageId>jamaicancastle.RF.fertilefields</packageId>
	<loadBefore>
		<li>skyarkhangel.HSK</li>
	</loadBefore>
	<description>Updated 10/21/22 by Jamaican Castle

=====

Fertile Fields is now 1.4 compatible! The name remains unchanged because otherwise everyone's FindMod patches would have to change and nobody wants that.

Fertile Fields allows you to transform and improve your colony's terrain, harvest raw materials from the land, and use them to enhance your environment.

- New in 1.1 -

Multi-terraforming tools, distinguished by the red ? icon, allow you to terraform multiple existing terrains to a single terrain of your choice with one designation. If it takes more than one step to go from the existing terrain to your chosen terrain, additional steps will be queued up for your colonists to work on.

Plant scraps have been rebalanced and made less obtrusive. Yields of plant scraps from many plants have been decreased, especially crops with low yields and decorative plants. Plants harvested in the wild or from hydroponics also have 50% lower plant scrap yields. A new fueled generator has been added that consumes 75 plant scraps per day for 1000W of power.

Growing zones have two new toggleable options: return to soil and automatically redesignate. The first option causes plants harvested there to not drop plant scraps, but to deplete soil less often. (This is generally less efficient than harvesting the scraps and refertilizing, but saves a lot of labor and storage space.) The second option triggers automatic rebuilding of any soil that depletes.

All terraforming-related resources (including plant scraps) now stack to 200. Fertilizer is less valuable when sold to caravans.

Terrains that share an affordance type with a basic terrain (such as soft sand for sand) can be transformed directly into that type. This mostly affects mod-added terrain.

=====

Terraforming

The Terraforming tab of the architect menu allows you to modify terrain to suit the needs of your colony. Transforming tiles to less fertile or useful terrain will generally yield resources such as sand, dirt, clay, or rock. Transforming tiles to more fertile terrain requires resources.

Multi-terraformers, shown with a red ? icon, will transform any terrain underneath them into the selected terrain. This may take multiple steps; if so, extra steps are built automatically after the first one is completed.

If you right-click on a multi-terraformer, you can select a single terraformer that will transform only one specific type of terrain into the selected terrain. More information about each transformation can be found in its single terraformer's description.

The Terraforming technology unlocks the ability to perform more sweeping modifications of terrain: removing shallow water and marsh, transforming deep water into shallow water (or vice versa), and placing or breaking up solid stone terrain.

=====

Farming

The Farming tab of the architect menu allows you to enhance the fertility of your soil and the usefulness of your farms. Compost bins and barrels allow you to transform raw compost, created at the butcher's table, into fertilizer that can transform regular soil into rich soil.

The Farming technology expands your options by allowing you to place dirt on smooth stone or ice terrain to form topsoil, which can be fertilized. Rich soil, meanwhile, can be tilled for an even greater improvement in productivity.

Fertile soil used in a growing zone will eventually degrade into less fertile soil. You can use excess plant material to mitigate this, or harvest these plant scraps to make fertilizer, as animal feed, or to fuel generators.

=====

Construction

Clay can be fired at a smithy to create bricks for walls, floors, and other constructions. In addition to being dug up, these clay can be ground from dirt or sand (and sand from rocks) at a stonecutter's table.

The rock mill is a new production bench that acts as an electrically powered stonecutter's table.

=====

See also: the readme.txt in the mod's About folder.

=====

Compatibility

Terrains from Dub's Hygiene, CuproPanda's Quarry, Crashlanding, Nature's Pretty Sweet, Biomes!, and Tiberium Rim can be modified by Fertie Fields terrain transformations, where appropriate. (Note that this does *not* include Tiberium terrain in Tiberium Rim, which must be decrystalized first.)

Fertile Fields is compatible with Seeds Please!.

Glass production from Glass+Lights and Dub's Skylights will use sand from Fertile Fields.

Vanilla Furniture Expanded - Production will remove the rock mill from the build menu, since it's redundant with that mod's electrical stonecutting table. Existing rock mills will still function.

Fertile Fields is compatible with Vegetable Garden, but will overwrite certain VGP Garden Tools that overlap with Fertile Fields tools. In addition, many VGP tools are located in the Farming tab.

=====

Credits

Fertile Fields 1.0 and earlier by Rainbeau Flambe/dburgdorf.

German language translation files were provided by Ryder32x and Erdnussbrot. Korean language translation files were provided by Ludeon forums user NEPH. French language translation files were provided by Steam user Redstylt. Russian files were provided by Steam user fox_kirya.

The C# code related to compost bins derives from Dismarzero's "Vegetable Garden." Other aspects of the mod's code have benefited in no small measure from NotFood's suggestions and contributions. Scrap-fueled generator XML and graphic by Pelador. Hygiene production compatibility patches by dninemfive.

The mod uses the Harmony patch library by Pardeike.

=====

License

If you're a modpack maker and want to include "Fertile Fields" in your pack, or if you're a modder and want to use "Fertile Fields" as the basis of a derivative mod, please feel free to do so. I ask only that you let me know about it.</description>
</ModMetaData>
