<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<LanguageData>
  <BasicSettings>Basic Settings</BasicSettings>
  <AdvancedSettings>Advanced Settings</AdvancedSettings>
  <DebugLog>Log debug messages</DebugLog>
  <DebugLogTooltips>Turn on debug log. Do not use this on normal game play as it's very spammy.</DebugLogTooltips>
  <LongDistanceThreshold>"Long Distance" Threshold</LongDistanceThreshold>
  <LongDistanceThresholdTooltips>When the vanilla job is less than this distance, it will not be substituted.

Nearby job search will only activate if vanilla job is farther away than this distance.
  </LongDistanceThresholdTooltips>
  <MaxSearchRadius>Nearby job search max radius</MaxSearchRadius>
  <MaxSearchRadiusTooltips>Max radius of the area to search nearby jobs.

Nearby job search will not go beyond this radius.
  </MaxSearchRadiusTooltips>
  <PriorityBoost>Max priority difference between vanilla and nearby jobs</PriorityBoost>
  <PriorityBoostTooltips>We boost the priority of nearby jobs.

Nearby jobs will not be considered if the difference between their riority and the vanilla job is higher than this value.
  </PriorityBoostTooltips>
  <VanillaChancePercentage>Chance to randomly ignore nearby search and stick to vanilla job</VanillaChancePercentage>
  <VanillaChancePercentageTooltips>Chance to skip nearby job search and stick to vanilla behavior

If this value is 100%, we never do nearby job search and always use vanilla behavior

If this value is 0% we always do nearby job search as long as vanilla gave a long distance job.

Set this to a small percentage so that colonist won't be stuck at the same area for too long.
  </VanillaChancePercentageTooltips>
  <ClickPlusToEdit>Click the "+" to edit</ClickPlusToEdit>
  <ExcludedLongDistanceWorkTypes>Do not substitute these work types at long distance</ExcludedLongDistanceWorkTypes>
  <ExcludedLongDistanceWorkTypesTooltips>If enabled, any long distance work of these selected types will not be substituted with nearby work.

Note: some work types are already not affected, even if they might be listed here and not selected.
  </ExcludedLongDistanceWorkTypesTooltips>
  <ExcludedNearbyWorkTypes>Do not prefer these work types nearby</ExcludedNearbyWorkTypes>
  <ExcludedNearbyWorkTypesTooltips>If enabled, any nearby work of these selected types will not be preferred over long distance works.

Note: some work types are already not affected, even if they might be listed here and not selected.
  </ExcludedNearbyWorkTypesTooltips>
</LanguageData>
