<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>Character Editor</name>
  <author>void</author>
  <url></url>
  <supportedVersions>
	<li>1.0</li>  
	<li>1.1</li>
	<li>1.2</li>
	<li>1.3</li>
	<li>1.4</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <packageId>void.charactereditor</packageId>
  <modDependencies>
	<li>
		<packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
		<displayName>Harmony</displayName>
		<steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
	</li>	
  </modDependencies>
  <loadAfter>
  	<li>brrainz.harmony</li>
	<li>Ludeon.RimWorld</li>
	<li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Royalty</li>
	<li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Ideology</li>
	<li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Biotech</li>
	<li>UnlimitedHugs.HugsLib</li>
  </loadAfter>
  <description>v1.4.1240 build on 2023-01-07 for RimWorld v1.4.3580
Editor for humanlike pawns on map and for crashlanding (colonists, enemies, dead pawns)


MOD FEATURES
• editor for pawns on map and for crashlanding
• editable: body, head, hair, skin color, apparel color, gender, name, age, skills, passion, traits, backstory, health, needs, thoughts, attraction, relations, favorite color
• list for all available pawns, on map, in world, animals, etc
• create, edit, remove, find, load, save pawns
• edit or shift pawn inventory items
• equip, edit or place weapons, apparel, items
• change faction, race, mental state, inspiration
• recruit, resurrect, heal or hurt pawns
• redress, undress pawns
• teleport pawns
• change or edit ideology
• give or remove titles
• add or remove psy abilities
• add or remove xenotypes and genes
• edit records


MOD LOAD ORDER
Harmony
Core
Royalty (optional)
Ideology (optional)
Biotech (optional)
HugsLib (optional)
...
Character Editor


MOD SETTINGS
• ARGB/HDR [Enable/Disable] (image of selected pawn)
• Create with race specific clothes [Enable/Disable]
• Create nude [Enable/Disable]
• Create no start weapon [Enable/Disable]
• Create no start inventory [Enable/Disable]
• Editor pauses game [Enable/Disable]
• Show editor tabs [Enable/Disable]
• Show pawn list [Enable/Disable]
• Mini view [Enable/Disable]
• Show in main tabs [Enable/Disable]
• Architect menu objects [Enable/Disable]
• Optional map settings [Enable/Disable]
• Automatic Apparelcheck [Enable/Disable]
• Stay in cascet [Enable/Disable]
• Show dead logo [Enable/Disable]
• Use sorted pawn list [Enable/Disable]
• Use name files [Enable/Disable]
• Hotkeys for UI and Teleport
• Resolution (image of selected pawn)
• Stack Limit [1..9999] (max value for the inventory slider)
• Num capsule slots [10..100]
• Custom saved armor changes
• Custom saved weapon changes
• Custom saved item changes
• Custom pawns [90 slots]


HOW TO USE
a) start the editor from the crashlanding screen
b) start the editor from the main tabs after the map has loaded (near to menu)
c) start the editor from mod settings
d) start the editor by entering 'Zombrella' or 'Zombgrella' cascet with pawn
e) start the editor by pressing hotkey button (set a hotkey in settings)


HOW TO CHANGE GRADIENT COLOR
1. Precondition Gradient Hair mod is active.
2. Click on the Hair-Label to open the color picker dialog.
3. Select your Color for ColorA and ColorB.


COMPATIBLE MODS
should be compatible to almost every mod


HINTS
• To see add / remove pawn buttons - click on the star button left of the bio tab. that will show you all extended functions for pawn creation and more. click it again to hide them.
• Click on the 'star' button on the right corner of the pawn image, to activate randomizers.
• To choose the color with color picker, click on the hair label or apparel label or skin label.
• There are 90 slots for pawns. Saved items are limited to 5. Gradient Hair is saved, when available.
• When starting editor while pawn is selected, then selected pawn will be autom. selected in editor.


HINTS FOR ITEM STAT EDITING
• editable stats were added since 2019-07-18T01:33, that is fully optional and just for fun
• stat changes are instant for the current game session
• you can rollback all stat changes by clicking on reset all to default
• when you want to keep your changes after game restart, than you can use the save button
• should also work with combat extended, but the functionality is limited
• the editable changes for weapons is a lite version of the weaponry mod
• the editable changes for armors is from my unreleased armory mod
• you can buy the items instead of adding them to a pawn, by clicking on the item texture


LANGUAGES
• Most of the ui elements are auto translated to all in-game languages.
• Full language support for german, english, french, polish, spanish, russian, japanese, simplified chinese


SPECIAL THANKS TO
• Proxyer for japanese translation
• 黄俊浩 for simplified chinese translation


CHANGES OF LAST UPDATE
• 2023-01-07 build 1240
- fixed bug causing editor ui not starting, when starting to new worlds and then clicking on escape instead of continue
- added visual effect for moving objects from map to interstellar container
- changed recruit button - recruit now should be able to recruit even unwaveringly loyal pawns
- changed maxvalue for slotcount from 100 to 400
• 2023-01-07 build 1239
- fixed bug that prevented animal gears from being worn
- fixed scribe_deep instead of scribe_values for pawn name in capsule ui
- performance update for capsule ui
• 2023-01-05 build 1238
- fixed hotkeys not saved for keys (like Kp-) without preexisting keycode in the keyprefs
- stability checks for the extended view
• 2023-01-05 build 1237
- 'Humanoid Alien Races ~ Dev' modname added for the check if Humanoid Alien Races mod is active
• 2023-01-05 build 1236
- fixed save button in capsule ui not working
- fixed missing toggle button between interstellar view and rescue-pod view (click on the title in the capsule ui dialog to switch, while playing on map)
- fixed scribe_def bug when clicking on save game
• 2022-12-31 build 1235
- when starting to new worlds, the current colony animals will be taken with you
- fixed bug: taken scenario items gets removed from scenario when scenario is started multiple times in a row using the load button
• 2022-12-30 build 1234
- fixes for scenario capsule problems, still not complete but almost
• 2022-12-30 build 1233
- fixed key not found bug due to old saved custom items
• 2022-12-30 build 1232
- changed mod enum visibility
• 2022-12-30 build 1231
- fix for key not found during creation of defaults
• 2022-12-29 build 1230
- fixed facial animation not loading when clicked on load pawn slot
• 2022-12-29
- fixed copy/paste of some lists doesn't work
- fixed in apparel+ when opening by clicking on existing pawn apparel, then setting all filters to 'all' then selecting an apparel with style - the stuff is set to none and the dialog box crashes
- fixed hotkeys not saving
- changed item, weapon, apparel dialogs
- fully editable genes, except conditional stats
- bodysize gene properties now editable
- traits from genes are color highlighted
- support for capsule dialog style items
- changes and fixes in capsule dialog
- added stackables in capsule dialog will be merged
- window position of most dialog windows is saved
- more parameters for objects are editable now
- pawns can be created and placed from the object dialog
- race properties of pawns are editable in the object dialog
- animal capsule now also allows to take humanlikes
</description>
</ModMetaData>