<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>Character Editor</name>
  <author>void</author>
  <url></url>
  <supportedVersions>
	<li>1.0</li>  
	<li>1.1</li>
	<li>1.2</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <packageId>void.charactereditor</packageId>
  <modDependencies>
	<li>
		<packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
		<displayName>Harmony</displayName>
		<steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
	</li>
	<li>
		<packageId>UnlimitedHugs.HugsLib</packageId>
		<displayName>HugsLib</displayName>
		<steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/818773962</steamWorkshopUrl>
	</li>
  </modDependencies>
  <loadAfter>
  	<li>brrainz.harmony</li>
	<li>Ludeon.RimWorld</li>
	<li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Royalty</li>
	<li>UnlimitedHugs.HugsLib</li>
  </loadAfter>
  <description>last update:2020-09-26
Editor for humanlike pawns on map and for crashlanding (colonists, enemies, dead pawns).


MOD FEATURES
• editor for pawns on map and for crashlanding
• editable: body, head, hair, skin color, apparel color, gender, name, age, skills, passion, traits, backstory, health, needs, thoughts, attraction, relations
• create, edit, remove, find, load, save pawns
• edit pawn inventory
• equip or edit weapons, apparel, items
• change faction, race, mental state, inspiration
• recruit, resurrect, heal pawns
• redress, undress pawns
• teleport pawns


MOD LOAD ORDER
Harmony
Core
Royalty (optional)
HugsLib
...
Character Editor


MOD SETTINGS
• Show in main tabs [Enable/Disable]
• Show pawn list [Enable/Disable]
• Show editor tabs [Enable/Disable]
• Show dead logo [Enable/Disable]
• Optional map settings [Enable/Disable]
• Show weapon [Enable/Disable]
• Stay in cascet [Enable/Disable]
• Fast image refresh [Enable/Disable]
• Architect menu objects [Enable/Disable]
• Extended color space [Enable/Disable]
• Editor pauses game [Enable/Disable]
• Auto remove incompatible apparel [Enable/Disable]
• Use name files [Enable/Disable]
• Stack Limit [1..9999] (max value for the inventory slider)
• Hotkey (Button to change the hotkey for character editor)
• Character Editor UI (Button to trigger UI from mod options menu)
• Custom pawns [90 slots]
• Saved Armor Changes
• Saved Weapon Changes
• Saved Item Changes


HOW TO USE
a) start the editor from the crashlanding screen
b) start the editor from the main tabs after the map has loaded (near to menu)
c) start the editor from mod settings
d) start the editor by entering 'Zombrella' or 'Zombgrella' cascet with pawn
e) start the editor by pressing hotkey HOME/POS1 Button


HOW TO CHANGE GRADIENT COLOR
1. Precondition Gradient Hair mod is active.
2. Click on the Hair-Label to open the color picker dialog.
3. Select your Color for ColorA or ColorB.


COMPATIBLE MODS
should be compatible to every mod which adds hairdefs, bodydefs.


HINTS
• To choose the color with color picker, click on the hair label or apparel label or skin label.
• Click on alien symbol to toggle between (in-game used) portrait view and renderer from character editor.
• There are 30 slots for pawns. Saved items are limited to 3. Gradient Hair is saved, when available.
• 'Show weapon' has no effect on alien view
• When starting editor while pawn is selected, then the selected pawn will be autom. selected in editor.


HINTS FOR ITEM STAT EDITING
• editable stats were added since 2019-07-18T01:33, that is fully optional and just for fun
• stat changes are instant for the current game session
• you can rollback all stat changes by clicking on reset all to default
• when you want to keep your changes even after game restart, than you can use the save button
• should also work with combat extended, but the functionality is limited (i will not spend weeks for making everything compatible to combat extended)
• the editable changes for weapons is a lite version of the weaponry mod
• the editable changes for armors is from my unreleased armory mod
• you can buy the items instead of adding them to a pawn, by clicking on the item texture


LANGUAGES
• Most of the ui elements are auto translated to all in-game languages.
• Full language support for german, english, french, russian, japanese.


SPECIAL THANKS TO
• Proxyer for japanese translation
• 黄俊浩 for simplified chinese translation


LAST UPDATE 
• 2020-09-07 bugfixes. pawn slot saving format changed. records, relation, works, title, etc. will now be saved too. added automatic conversion for old pawns saved in slots. pawn slots can now be deleted, when [CTRL] is hold during choosing the pawnname from slot. some pawns could probably be not convertable. thought dialog added. social view buttons currently suspended - they are next on to do. changed person view. added chooseable gradients (precondition gradient hair mod is active). changing race fixed. activated namelist with female names [betatest] (about 400 new names). royal titles can now be set and removed. added buttons near to sliders for direct material selection. added facial animation eye support. probably changed something else too, but i forgot it. :)
• 2020-09-08 fixed bug on pawn generation that made pawns incapable of working (needs bug). fixed bugs on dropping, placing, spawning and not spawning pawn. fixed wild animal creation. fixed unintended placement of pawns from slot. removed autosavecolor, because it caused wrong color settings. alpha colors will be saved by game as long as extended colors are not active.
• 2020-09-09 fixed naked texture path finder. fixed change race bug. label size for physical parts increased.
• 2020-09-12 guilty tracker was removed since the rimworld update 1.2.2753 - issue fixed
• 2020-09-13 social tab + relation changes
• 2020-09-13 fixed not initialized work settings when loading/saving to slot
• 2020-09-13 moved facial stuff button to the left side. added birthday dialog (can be accessed by clicking on birthday icon). setting bio age under 18 in the birthday dialog will remove the adulthood backstory. optimized social tab class.
• 2020-09-14 added mod option 'Auto remove incompatible apparel', 'Use name files'. translated some labels. optimized search text behaviour. added mod selector for hair mini view.
• 2020-09-19 added bio age config to the birthday dialog
• 2020-09-26 all initially created pawns will get a weapon. pawns from mods with weapons will get the weapons of their mod. fixed - turret guns will no longer show up as ranged weapon. fixed - redress of initial pawns in v1.1.
• 2020-09-26 increased number of slots to 90. fixed - info dialogs from inventory tab will be displayed in the same layer. fixed - pawns without story tracker will not get a weapon.
</description>
</ModMetaData>