<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>Character Editor</name>
  <author>void</author>
  <url></url>
  <modVersion>1.5.9</modVersion>
  <supportedVersions>
	<li>1.0</li>  
	<li>1.1</li>
	<li>1.2</li>
	<li>1.3</li>
	<li>1.4</li>
	<li>1.5</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <packageId>void.charactereditor</packageId>
  <modDependencies>
	<li>
		<packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
		<displayName>Harmony</displayName>
		<steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
	</li>	
  </modDependencies>
  <loadAfter>
  	<li>brrainz.harmony</li>
	<li>Ludeon.RimWorld</li>
	<li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Royalty</li>
	<li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Ideology</li>
	<li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Biotech</li>
	<li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Anomaly</li>
	<li>UnlimitedHugs.HugsLib</li>
  </loadAfter>
  <description>v1.5.9 build on 2024-04-21 for RimWorld v1.5.4069
Editor for humanlike pawns on map and for crashlanding (colonists, enemies, dead pawns)


MOD FEATURES
• editor for pawns on map and for crashlanding
• editable: body, head, hair, skin color, apparel color, gender, name, age, skills, passion, traits, backstory, health, needs, thoughts, attraction, relations, favorite color
• list for all available pawns, on map, in world, animals, etc
• create, edit, remove, find, load, save pawns
• edit or shift pawn inventory items
• equip, edit or place weapons, apparel, items
• change faction, race, mental state, inspiration
• recruit, resurrect, heal or hurt pawns
• redress, undress pawns
• teleport pawns
• change or edit ideology
• give or remove titles
• add or remove psy abilities
• add or remove xenotypes and genes
• edit records
• edit mutations


MOD LOAD ORDER
Harmony
Core
Royalty (optional)
Ideology (optional)
Biotech (optional)
Anomaly (optional)
HugsLib (optional)
...
Character Editor


MOD SETTINGS
• ARGB/HDR [Enable/Disable] (image of selected pawn)
• Create with race specific clothes [Enable/Disable]
• Create nude [Enable/Disable]
• Create no start weapon [Enable/Disable]
• Create no start inventory [Enable/Disable]
• Editor pauses game [Enable/Disable]
• Show editor tabs [Enable/Disable]
• Show pawn list [Enable/Disable]
• Mini view [Enable/Disable]
• Show in main tabs [Enable/Disable]
• Architect menu objects [Enable/Disable]
• Optional map settings [Enable/Disable]
• Automatic Apparelcheck [Enable/Disable]
• Stay in cascet [Enable/Disable]
• Show dead logo [Enable/Disable]
• Use sorted pawn list [Enable/Disable]
• Use name files [Enable/Disable]
• Hotkeys for UI and Teleport
• Resolution (image of selected pawn)
• Stack Limit [1..9999] (max value for the inventory slider)
• Num capsule slots [10..100]
• Custom saved armor changes
• Custom saved weapon changes
• Custom saved item changes
• Custom pawns [90 slots]


HOW TO USE
a) start the editor from the crashlanding screen
b) start the editor from the main tabs after the map has loaded (near to menu)
c) start the editor from mod settings
d) start the editor by entering 'Zombrella' or 'Zombgrella' cascet with pawn
e) start the editor by pressing hotkey button (set a hotkey in settings)


HOW TO CHANGE GRADIENT COLOR
1. Precondition Gradient Hair mod is active.
2. Click on the Hair-Label to open the color picker dialog.
3. Select your Color for ColorA and ColorB.


COMPATIBLE MODS
should be compatible to almost every mod


HINTS
• To see add / remove pawn buttons - click on the star button left of the bio tab. that will show you all extended functions for pawn creation and more. click it again to hide them.
• Click on the 'star' button on the right corner of the pawn image, to activate randomizers.
• To choose the color with color picker, click on the hair label or apparel label or skin label.
• There are 90 slots for pawns. Saved items are limited to 5. Gradient Hair is saved, when available.
• When starting editor while pawn is selected, then selected pawn will be auto-selected in editor.


HINTS FOR ITEM STAT EDITING
• stat changes are instant for the current game session
• you can rollback all stat changes by clicking on reset all to default
• when you want to keep your changes after game restart, than you can use the save button
• should also work with combat extended, but the functionality is limited
• the editable changes for weapons is a lite version of the weaponry mod
• the editable changes for armors is from my unreleased armory mod
• you can buy the items instead of adding them to a pawn, by clicking on the item texture


LANGUAGES
• Most of the ui elements are auto-translated to all in-game languages.
• Full language support for german, english, french, polish, spanish, russian, japanese, simplified chinese


SPECIAL THANKS TO
• Proxyer for japanese translation
• 黄俊浩 for simplified chinese translation


CHANGES OF LAST UPDATE
• 2024-04-16 build 0
- mod updated for RimWorld 1.5.4066
• 2024-04-18 build 1
- fixed compatibility to NL Facial Animation mod
- added heterochromia iridum
• 2024-04-18 build 2
- fixed bodysize bug, occurring when a bodysize gene was applied to a pawn
• 2024-04-18 build 3
- fixed problem with translation label's not being set
- fixed problems that could occur when choosing pregnancy health conditions in the wrong way
- added extra buttons in full heal dialog
- added confirmation dialog on save pawn (can be suppressed)
• 2024-04-18 build 4
- after fixing health conditions dialog
• 2024-04-18 build 5
- fixed graphical updates not being drawn on change, such as those for alien race addons
- slider color in main view will show up again
• 2024-04-19 build 6
- fixed selected race button is now considered when adding a pawn with selected pawntype 'all'
- fixed bug occurring on cloning a pawn, making the portrait of the clon-originator become invisible
- fixed bug occurring on loading pawn, making the portrait of one of the previous pawns become invisible
• 2024-04-19 build 7
- fixed bug caused by the recent change to selecting races
• 2024-04-20 build 8
- added editable mutations
• 2024-04-21 build 9
- mutations are saveable to slots
- increased stability for slot loading
- mod info can be shown on slot loading
</description>
</ModMetaData>