<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>Character Editor</name>
  <author>void</author>
  <url></url>
  <supportedVersions>
	<li>1.3</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <packageId>void.charactereditor</packageId>
  <modDependencies>
	<li>
		<packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
		<displayName>Harmony</displayName>
		<steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
	</li>
	<li>
		<packageId>UnlimitedHugs.HugsLib</packageId>
		<displayName>HugsLib</displayName>
		<steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/818773962</steamWorkshopUrl>
	</li>
  </modDependencies>
  <loadAfter>
  	<li>brrainz.harmony</li>
	<li>Ludeon.RimWorld</li>
	<li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Royalty</li>
	<li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Ideology</li>
	<li>UnlimitedHugs.HugsLib</li>
  </loadAfter>
  <description>last update:2021-08-19
Editor for humanlike pawns on map and for crashlanding (colonists, enemies, dead pawns).


MOD FEATURES
• editor for pawns on map and for crashlanding
• editable: body, head, hair, skin color, apparel color, gender, name, age, skills, passion, traits, backstory, health, needs, thoughts, attraction, relations
• create, edit, remove, find, load, save pawns
• edit pawn inventory
• equip or edit weapons, apparel, items
• change faction, race, mental state, inspiration
• recruit, resurrect, heal pawns
• redress, undress pawns
• teleport pawns


MOD LOAD ORDER
Harmony
Core
Royalty (optional)
Ideology (optional)
HugsLib
...
Character Editor


MOD SETTINGS
• Show in main tabs [Enable/Disable]
• Show pawn list [Enable/Disable]
• Show editor tabs [Enable/Disable]
• Show dead logo [Enable/Disable]
• Optional map settings [Enable/Disable]
• Show weapon [Enable/Disable]
• Stay in cascet [Enable/Disable]
• Fast image refresh [Enable/Disable]
• Architect menu objects [Enable/Disable]
• Extended color space [Enable/Disable]
• Editor pauses game [Enable/Disable]
• Auto remove incompatible apparel [Enable/Disable]
• Use name files [Enable/Disable]
• Stack Limit [1..9999] (max value for the inventory slider)
• Hotkey (Button to change the hotkey for character editor)
• Character Editor UI (Button to trigger UI from mod options menu)
• Custom pawns [90 slots]
• Saved Armor Changes
• Saved Weapon Changes
• Saved Item Changes


HOW TO USE
a) start the editor from the crashlanding screen
b) start the editor from the main tabs after the map has loaded (near to menu)
c) start the editor from mod settings
d) start the editor by entering 'Zombrella' or 'Zombgrella' cascet with pawn
e) start the editor by pressing hotkey HOME/POS1 Button


HOW TO CHANGE GRADIENT COLOR
1. Precondition Gradient Hair mod is active.
2. Click on the Hair-Label to open the color picker dialog.
3. Select your Color for ColorA or ColorB.


COMPATIBLE MODS
should be compatible to every mod which adds hairdefs, bodydefs.


HINTS
• To choose the color with color picker, click on the hair label or apparel label or skin label.
• Click on alien symbol to toggle between (in-game used) portrait view and renderer from character editor.
• There are 90 slots for pawns. Saved items are limited to 3. Gradient Hair is saved, when available.
• 'Show weapon' has no effect on alien view
• When starting editor while pawn is selected, then the selected pawn will be autom. selected in editor.


HINTS FOR ITEM STAT EDITING
• editable stats were added since 2019-07-18T01:33, that is fully optional and just for fun
• stat changes are instant for the current game session
• you can rollback all stat changes by clicking on reset all to default
• when you want to keep your changes even after game restart, than you can use the save button
• should also work with combat extended, but the functionality is limited (i will not spend weeks for making everything compatible to combat extended)
• the editable changes for weapons is a lite version of the weaponry mod
• the editable changes for armors is from my unreleased armory mod
• you can buy the items instead of adding them to a pawn, by clicking on the item texture


LANGUAGES
• Most of the ui elements are auto translated to all in-game languages.
• Full language support for german, english, french, russian, japanese.


SPECIAL THANKS TO
• Proxyer for japanese translation
• 黄俊浩 for simplified chinese translation


LAST UPDATE
• 2021-08-14
- traits with skills now change skillpoints when added
- fix for statmodifer bug in trait dialog
- translation fix for incapable of
- fix: traits from loaded pawn from slot does not affect skillpoints
- fix when race label is null
- adding backstory with focus now updates the info of the pawn
- skillgains from traits and backstories are shown as tooltip, when you mouse move over the green or red bar
- added polish translation
- removing or copy paste traits now also updated the pawn stat info (for focus etc.)
• 2021-08-15
- polish translation corrections
- increased robustness for tooltip getter for skillgains
- changed - apparel checker, checks more layers now (this avoids apparel that cause draw errors on pawns)
• 2021-08-16 (1.3 changes only)
- star: added plus button to the extended functions
- bio tab: added shift button
- renderer: fix for render textures for animals, once again
- on ideo change: update of pawn stat info
- alpha color: reduced min value for apparel on direct wearables changes, because apparel got already invisible at half of the slider.
full alpha value is still available in color picker dialog and apparel change dialog.
• 2021-08-17
- bio tab: fix for skill level input cap
- ported 1.3 changes from 16th to 1.2
- added facial animation support
- facial animation settings are now saved to slots
- fixed some button positions
- bio tab: shift object should no longer destroy old already weared objects
- toggle nude: now dresses or undresses completely to or from inventory
- toggle hat: now moves the hat from or to inventory
- load pawn into another pawn list automatically sets the appropriate faction
- adding pawn should no longer create multiple pawn samples in list
- fix for randomized names and faces: loading pawn from slot should be consistent now
- click on pawn in pawnlist now autoselects the appropriate pawn on map
- facial animation savegame fix (settings of facial animation should now be persistent)
• 2021-08-18
- performance update (huge lists will no longer drop the fps)
- grouped shapes for head, hair, body
- fix: facial animation should no longer conflict with other races
- hair can be changed on mouseover in hair selector dialog
- fix: toggle hat or nude only applies to the selected pawn
- fix: cycling through clothes should in 99% of cases (no longer destroy clothes from other layer nor jump to other layer). its almost safe now.
- added cycling through weapons
- fix: new generated clothes by cycling through clothes will be using stuff specific color
- fix: dualwield weapons can be choosen without destroying the secondary weapon
- ported changes from 1.3 to 1.2
• 2021-08-19
- fixed: renderer issues on toggle hat, toggle apparel
- dead logo is displayed for dead pawns in list
- changed capturer, + higher render texture resolution for selected pawn
- fixes for inventory tab
- fixes for ideo exceptions on dead pawns
- inventory tab: moved randomizers
- fix: dualwield secondary weapon will not drop, when cycling through weapons
- fixed several graphic update issues, when something was changed on pawn and wasn't correctly shown
</description>
</ModMetaData>