<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Defs>
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef Abstract="true" Name="UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>DefensivePositionsUpdateFeature</defName>
		<modNameReadable>Defensive Positions</modNameReadable>
		<modIdentifier>DefensivePositions</modIdentifier>
		<linkUrl>https://ludeon.com/forums/index.php?topic=25535</linkUrl>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
	
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>DefensivePositions_1_2_0</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>1.2.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>img:images/keypad|caption: Colonists can now be assigned to squads for quick selection using the numeric keys. Additionally, there are now hotkeys for handling all colonists- selecting everyone, undrafting everyone, and sending everyone off to their defensive position. Keys can be reassigned in Options &gt; Keyboard configuration.|img:images/assign_squad|caption:Assign a new squad by selecting your colonists, holding Control and pressing a keypad number from 1 to 9.|img:images/select_squad|caption:Select all colonists belonging to a squad by pressing the key you assigned.|img:images/send_everyone|caption:By pressing 0 on the keypad you can send all your colonists to their assigned defensive positions without selecting them.|img:images/select_everyone|caption:The keypad period key allows you to select all colonists with one keystroke.|img:images/undraft_everyone|caption:Press keypad divide (slash) to release all drafted colonists.|Finally, colonists will now automatically man turrets and mortars if you set their defensive position on the interaction circle of the gun. Happy defending!</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
	
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>DefensivePositions_1_8_0</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>1.8.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>- Defensive Positions is now compatible with Zetrith's Multiplayer mod.|- The shift key can now be used to queue movement orders. This can be enabled via a setting in Options &gt; Mod Options.</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
	
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>DefensivePositions_1_9_1</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>1.9.1</assemblyVersion>
		<content>
- Caravans can now be assigned to squads from the world map.|
- Pressing a squad key repeatedly will cycle through all places its members are found in. Also works for caravans and on multiple maps.
		</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
	
</Defs>