<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<ModMetaData>
	<name>Nature's Pretty Sweet</name>
	<author>skyarkhangel</author>
	<supportedVersions>
		<li>1.1</li>
	</supportedVersions>
	<packageId>skyarkhangel.NPS</packageId>
	<url>https://github.com/skyarkhangel/Hardcore-SK</url>
    <modDependencies>
        <li>
            <packageId>skyarkhangel.HSK</packageId>
            <displayName>Hardcore SK</displayName>
            <downloadUrl>https://github.com/skyarkhangel/Hardcore-SK</downloadUrl>
        </li>
    </modDependencies>
	<loadBefore>
	</loadBefore>
	<loadAfter>
		<li>skyarkhangel.HSK</li>
	</loadAfter>
	<incompatibleWith>
		<li>tkkntkkn.nps</li>
	</incompatibleWith>
	<description>
Its a fork. Special lite Hardcore SK version with removed some of "heavy" features like wet soil, graphics etc. Incompatible with NPS by tkkn and its patches.
KNOWN ISSUES: Could be problems when visit other maps and simultaneously play with severals home maps.
Try to play with one map.
	
Nature's Pretty Sweet adds additional terrain elements, weather and biomes. It also updates the map in response to weather, giving a more wild, untamed and alive feeling to the world.

Requires a new save. Some of the weather affects might cause a little bit of lag (at high speeds or if you're really zoomed out) but you can turn them off in the options.

Most new elements will generate in the standard biomes, but there are some biomes that guarantee new features, and a few elements are ONLY available in some biomes. Most of the elements were directly inspired by places I've camped in the US.

There are also new resources, items, dangers, natural protection from raids and other effects. Resources can be harvested to get items, which can be sold or consumed.

Added:

	Weather:
		Soil and sand will darken when wet. Wet sand and soil increase fertility. Deserts will see blooms after it rains.
		Puddles form after rainfall and snow melt.
		Rivers flood from rain, and are higher in the spring and lower in the fall.
		Water freezes in the winter.
		New weather:
			Dust Storms (deserts only)
			Cloudy
			Partially Cloudy
		New Effects:
			Lava Smoke
			Frost
			You can see pawns' breath in the cold

	New Biomes:
		Desert Salt Flats: 
			Description: Desert with a lot of salt flats.
			New plant: Salt weed, a special plant that grows only on salty earth. Separates salt from water.
			New items: Salt and salted meat.
			New floor: Salt the ground to prevent plants from growing for one year. Create a barrier around your base to protect from giant snails and fire.
			New weather: Dust storms. Dry and wet versions.
			Inspired by: Badlands Saltflats from Death Valley
		Redwood Forest:
			Description: Temperate area with a lot of rain and fog, redwood trees and old growth forest.
			New trees: 
				Redwoods, huge trees that take hundreds of years to grow and yields very large amounts of wood.
				Old Growth Oaks, larger than your average oak.
				Old Growth Hazel, larger than your average hazel.
			New item: Red wood. Valuable, beautiful, fire resistant wood.
			New weather: thick fog.
			Inspired by: Redwood National Park in California
		Volcanic Fields:
			Description: Tropical. Tons of lava rock, rich soil, steam vents and lava. VERY DANGEROUS.
			New animals: Fire salamandars and  lava pet rocks. Lava pet rocks naturally radiate heat. Very very very slow moving. Once tamed, can be cooled off and hauled to a room to heat it.
			New item: Lava rock. A black stone that can be used for crafting.
			New power source: steam vents. Just like geysers, but temporary. You can use the cheap vent generator to get power from a steam vent.
			New terrains: 
				Lava: Destroys/burns items, burns pawns. Hardens and cools into lava rock.
				Lava rock. Plants cannot grow on lava rock, but there are more steam vents. You can mine lava rock here, and it is where pet lava rocks grow.
			New building material: Lava rock blocks.
			New terrain: Lava. Impassable terrain, but it generates heat.
			Inspired by: Hawai'i Volcanoes National Park
		Desert Oasis:
			Description: Lush, life filled area that is affected by desert temperatures.
			New element: Cold springs (see below)
			New element: Wash. A dried riverbed that will flood in the spring.
			Inspired by: Big Bend National Park in Texas

	Reworked Terrains:
		Beaches
			Tides - very large bodies of waters will rise and fall like tides and waves.
			Junk, shells and treasure might be left behind on the shore. They will wash away if not collected before the next tide.
			New animals: giant crabs
			Inspired by: A combination of beaches in Florida and beaches in the pacific northwest.
		River banks
			River banks will flood in the spring and recede in the fall
			Rivers will flood after a large rain storn or snow melt.
			Rivers will leave behind rich soil after flooding.			
			
	New elements:
		Hot springs:
			Spawns in all biomes except...
				Desert (all)
				Volcanic Fields
				Icesheet
			Surrounded by rich soil and healroots
			Usually spawns next to a river/creek/etc.
			Resting in a hot spring will temporarily reduce pain and exhaustion. 
			Gives off a small amount of heat.
			Inspired by Arkansas Hot Springs
		Cold spring:
			Spawns in all biomes except...
				Desert (except for the desert oasis)
				Volcanic Fields
				Icesheet
				Tundra
			Surrounded by rich soil and ambrosia
			Usually spawns next to a river/creek/etc.
			Resting in a cold spring will temporarily reduce pain and give joy. 
			Gives off a small amount of chill.
			Inspired by Crystal Springs and Blue Springs, FL
	</description>
</ModMetaData>