<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>DontBlockDoorMod[1.0]</name>
  <author>tikubonn</author>
  <url>https://twitter.com/tikubonn</url>
  <description>This mod fixes a pandemic that has plagued many a world on the Rim: doors being wedged open. Whether it's prisoners escaping, invaders rushing in, or temperature leaking out, unwanted open doors have led to disasters in many colonies. My mod prevents items from being dropped on the same tile as a door, allowing it to close just as intended. After installing this mod, please avoid placing stockpiles on the same tile as a door. This may cause a bug that will have colonists confused between whether to store an item on that tile or not. 
This mod was made possible by Harmony (https://github.com/pardeike/Harmony) . I would like to thank its developer for creating such a useful resource! Please read the included file, "Harmony.LICENSE." This mod was also released under the MIT License. All such files are included with the mod for those so concerned.

2018 03/24: since this update, this MOD move the item to another place when built door upon it.
2018 03/24: since this update, anybody won't haul item to stockpile area's cell that overlapped by door. anybody won't haul the product to floor that is overlapped the door. and I fixed small bug.

これはRimWorldのシステムを少し改変し、ドアの上にアイテムを置けなくするようにするMODです(´・ω・`)
昨晩、襲撃者に資材が詰まって開けっぱなしだった扉から侵入され、お家が全焼しまい悲しくなったのでこのMODをつくりました(´・ω・`)
導入すると、何人たりともドアの上にアイテムが置けなくなります(´・ω・`)
溢れてしまった資材のせいで、ドア開けっぱなしなんてことはなくなると思います(´・ω・`)やるじゃん
ただ、このMODを導入している場合、ドアの上に備蓄ゾーンを設定しないように注意してください、永遠に資材運びするか、不具合が発生する可能性があります(´・ω・`)

2018 03/24: アイテムの上に扉が建設された際に、そのアイテムを扉の外に再配置するよう改良しました(´・ω・`)
2018 03/24: 備蓄ゾーンの上に扉が配置されている場合に、扉の上にアイテムを運搬しないように改良しました。また、製作作業の成果物を扉の上に運搬してしまわないように改良しました(´・ω・`)生き物の解体とストーンカッターで正常に動作していることを確認したので、他の精密加工台などでも同様の振る舞いをすると思います。それと扉をアイテムの上に建設した際にアイテムが壁にめり込んでしまうしょうもないバグを修正しました。

このMODはHarmony(https://github.com/pardeike/Harmony)を利用しています。
Harmonyのライセンスは同梱されているファイルHarmony.LICENSEを参照ください。
また、このMODはMITライセンスの下で提供されています。
このMODのライセンスは同梱されているファイルLICENSEをご参照ください。</description>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.0</li>
  </supportedVersions>
</ModMetaData>
