<LanguageData>

	<!-- Settings -->
	<ALConfigCuriosityEatingLabel>Prevent animals from eating random stuff</ALConfigCuriosityEatingLabel>
	<ALConfigCuriosityEatingTooltip>It mostly prevents your animals from eating drugs without a nutrition and stuff outside their allowed zones. They would still eat your food if it is in their allowed zone.</ALConfigCuriosityEatingTooltip>
	
	<ALConfigHostilePredatorsLabel>Predators hunting your pawns are considered hostile by your entire faction</ALConfigHostilePredatorsLabel>
	<ALConfigHostilePredatorsTooltip>This does not change threat response of your pawns, it only makes them able to recognize a threat.</ALConfigHostilePredatorsTooltip>
	
	<ALConfigEggConversionLabel>Convert eggs ruined by temperature into unfertilized chicken eggs</ALConfigEggConversionLabel>
	<ALConfigEggConversionTooltip>This does not affect already ruined eggs.</ALConfigEggConversionTooltip>
	
	<ALConfigMeatConversionLabel>Convert any generic animal meat into chicken meat upon butchering</ALConfigMeatConversionLabel>
	<ALConfigMeatConversionTooltip>This does not affect already butchered meat.</ALConfigMeatConversionTooltip>
	
	<ALConfigMedicalAlertsLabel>Medical alerts for animals</ALConfigMedicalAlertsLabel>
	<ALConfigMedicalAlertsTooltip>Shows right-hand alerts for when colony animals are injured, need rescuing or in critical medical condition.</ALConfigMedicalAlertsTooltip>
	
	<ALConfigTamenessDecayThresholdLabel>Wildness threshold for tameness decay {0}%. Vanilla: 10.1%.</ALConfigTamenessDecayThresholdLabel>
	<ALConfigTamenessDecayThresholdTooltip>Set to 100% to prevent losing tameness for all animals.</ALConfigTamenessDecayThresholdTooltip>
	
	<ALConfigTrainingDecaySpeedFactorLabel>Training decay speed {0}. Vanilla: 100%.</ALConfigTrainingDecaySpeedFactorLabel><!-- No % after wildcard is intentional. -->
	<ALConfigTrainingDecaySpeedFactorTooltip>Set to 1% to make it as slow as possible.</ALConfigTrainingDecaySpeedFactorTooltip>
	
	<ALConfigTradeHintsLabel>Tags for animals in trade and caravan interfaces</ALConfigTradeHintsLabel>
	<ALConfigTradeHintsTooltip>Shows animal's sex, training and wool growth.</ALConfigTradeHintsTooltip>
	
	<ALConfigAnimalsCanUseFoodDispenserLabel>Allow animals to use nutrient paste dispenser</ALConfigAnimalsCanUseFoodDispenserLabel>
	<ALConfigAnimalsCanUseFoodDispenserTooltip>Animals would be capable of pressing that button. Warining: contains a minor detour (extremely unlikely chance to have a conflict). If animals still don't use the dispenser, check if the building iself is in the allowed area.</ALConfigAnimalsCanUseFoodDispenserTooltip>
	
	<ALConfigHaulingMTBLabel>Hauling MTB {0}h. Vanilla: 1.5h.</ALConfigHaulingMTBLabel>
	<ALConfigHaulingMTBTooltip>'MTB' stands for 'Mean Time Between'. Setting to 0 drastically increases productiveness, but can affect performance with large amount of trained animals.</ALConfigHaulingMTBTooltip>
	
	<ALConfigShowExtraDisplayStatsLabel>Show extra stats for pawns</ALConfigShowExtraDisplayStatsLabel>
	<ALConfigShowExtraDisplayStatsTooltip>Shows some stats that vanilla misses, like resource production.</ALConfigShowExtraDisplayStatsTooltip>
	
	<ALConfigAlwaysShowRelationsLabel>Always show animal relations</ALConfigAlwaysShowRelationsLabel>
	<ALConfigAlwaysShowRelationsTooltip>By default, only relations with named animals are displayed. This allows to see all of them.</ALConfigAlwaysShowRelationsTooltip>

	<!-- Extra stats -->
	
	<WoolType>Wool type</WoolType>
	<Stat_Race_WoolType_Desc>The type of wool this creature will yield when sheared.</Stat_Race_WoolType_Desc>
	<WoolAmount>Wool amount</WoolAmount>
	<Stat_Race_WoolAmount_Desc>The amount of wool yielded when shearing this creature and time it takes to grow wool.</Stat_Race_WoolAmount_Desc>
	
	<MilkType>Milk type</MilkType>
	<Stat_Race_MilkType_Desc>The type of milk this creature will yield when milked.</Stat_Race_MilkType_Desc>
	<MilkAmount>Milk amount</MilkAmount>
	<Stat_Race_MilkAmount_Desc>The amount of milk yielded when milking this creature and time it takes to produce milk.</Stat_Race_MilkAmount_Desc>
	<MilkFemale>Milk female only</MilkFemale>
	<MilkFemaleExplanation>Some species may produce milk regardless of sex, but for most only females can be milked.</MilkFemaleExplanation>
	
	<EggType>Eggs type</EggType>
	<Stat_Race_EggType_Desc>The type of eggs this creature will lay.</Stat_Race_EggType_Desc>
	<EggAmount>Eggs amount</EggAmount>
	<Stat_Race_EggAmount_Desc>The amount of eggs in a clutch and how long it takes to produce them.</Stat_Race_EggAmount_Desc>
	<EggFemale>Eggs female only</EggFemale>
	<EggFemaleExplanation>Some species may produce eggs regardless of sex, but for most only females can do that.</EggFemaleExplanation>
	<EggNeedFertilization>Eggs must be fertilized</EggNeedFertilization>
	<EggNeedFertilizationExplanation>Some species may produce unfertilized eggs, but many others would not.</EggNeedFertilizationExplanation>
	<EggIncubation>Eggs incubation</EggIncubation>
	<EggIncubationExplanation>How much times it takes for an egg to hatch.</EggIncubationExplanation>
	
	<TimeToMature>Mature age</TimeToMature>
	<TimeToMatureExplanation>How much times it takes to reach reproductive age, age when it can produce milk/wool, or last defined life stage for species that can't reproduce. They are the same age for most species.</TimeToMatureExplanation>
	
	<GestationPeriod>Gestation period</GestationPeriod>
	<GestationPeriodExplanation>How much times it takes to produce a new offspring.</GestationPeriodExplanation>	
	<LitterSize>Litter size</LitterSize>
	<LitterSizeExplanation>How many offsprings can be produced at once.</LitterSizeExplanation>

    <!-- Medical Alerts for Animals -->
    <AnimalNeedsTreatment>Animal needs treatment</AnimalNeedsTreatment>
    <AnimalsNeedTreatment>Animals need treatment</AnimalsNeedTreatment>
    <AnimalNeedsTreatmentDesc>These animals need medical treatment. Without it, they may die of their wounds, or their wounds may become permanent.\n\n{0}</AnimalNeedsTreatmentDesc>

    <AnimalNeedsRescue>Animal needs rescue</AnimalNeedsRescue>
    <AnimalsNeedRescue>Animals need rescue</AnimalsNeedRescue>
    <AnimalsNeedRescueDesc>These animals are incapacitated on the ground:\n\n{0}\nSend a colonist to rescue them and carry them back to bed.\n\n(To rescue, select a colonist, then right click on the victim and select Rescue.)</AnimalsNeedRescueDesc>

    <AnimalsWithLifeThreateningDisease>Medical emergency (animals)</AnimalsWithLifeThreateningDisease>
    <AnimalsWithLifeThreateningDiseaseAmputationDesc>Animals are at risk of death because of severe illness:\n\n{0}\nIf possible, consider amputating or replacing infected limbs in order to keep animals alive.</AnimalsWithLifeThreateningDiseaseAmputationDesc>
    <AnimalsWithLifeThreateningDiseaseDesc>Animals are at risk of death because of severe illness:\n\n{0}\nMake sure that they get the best medical care possible.</AnimalsWithLifeThreateningDiseaseDesc>

</LanguageData>