<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<LanguageData>
	<!-- settings -->
	<fulfill_outdoors_head>Need of Outdoors</fulfill_outdoors_head>
	<fulfill_outdoors_label>Pawns are encouraged to fulfill their need of outdoors by seeking recreation outdoors</fulfill_outdoors_label>
	<fulfill_outdoors_note>NOTE: Don't place the same joy giving sources both indoors and outdoors, to avoid indecisiveness.</fulfill_outdoors_note>
	<clean_head>Opportunistic jobs</clean_head>
	<clean_before_working_label>Pawns are encouraged to clean the room before operating a station in it</clean_before_working_label>
	<clean_before_working_note>NOTE: Don't expect pawns who cannot clean to suddenly begin cleaning.</clean_before_working_note>
	<bill_job_pathing_label>Calculate accurate path to the building for bill jobs</bill_job_pathing_label>
	<bill_job_pathing_note>It'll help to avoid making unreasonable hooks around when your pawns need to bring resources first, but it may be costly on CPU</bill_job_pathing_note>
	<clean_after_tending_label>Pawns are encouraged to clean the room after tending to a patient</clean_after_tending_label>
	<clean_after_tending_note>NOTE: Don't expect pawns who cannot clean to suddenly begin cleaning.</clean_after_tending_note>
	<meal_stacking_head>Meal stacking</meal_stacking_head>
	<meal_stacking_label>Pawns avoid mixing negative thoughts when stacking meals</meal_stacking_label>
	<meal_stacking_note>That way pawns will never mix disgusting meals with normal ones</meal_stacking_note>
	<dont_count_odd_label>Count odd meat (ex.: insect) as normal, allowing to stack it with normal meals</dont_count_odd_label>
	<dont_count_odd_note>Insect meat isn't so bad...</dont_count_odd_note>
	<gen_ingredients_head>Meal generation</gen_ingredients_head>
	<gen_ingredients_label>Add random ingredients to randomly generated meals</gen_ingredients_label>
	<gen_ingredients_note>Ex.: gifted by story teller, sold by a trader, looted from corpse. Only mood neutral components are used. With this option on, the game will never be the same</gen_ingredients_note>
	<add_to_que_label>Add former task to queue</add_to_que_label>
	<add_to_que_note>That way pawns will not change their mind after performing an opportunistic task, but sometimes it can cause confusion if a job was already taken</add_to_que_note>
	<hauling_over_bills_label>Pawns are encouraged to haul ingredients for a bill to a stockpile</hauling_over_bills_label>
	<hauling_over_bills_note>When working on a bill, pawns will prefer hauling ingredients to a stockpile, instead of taking a small fraction, required for a recipe</hauling_over_bills_note>
	<fulfill_needs_head>Fulfillment of needs</fulfill_needs_head>
	<drugs_use_potential_mood_label>Pawns are encouraged to take account of potential mood in drug policies</drugs_use_potential_mood_label>
	<drugs_use_potential_mood_note>Pawns will not use drugs if "potential" mood is above a limit, preventing overuse of drugs to achieve a set mood level.</drugs_use_potential_mood_note>
	<miscellaneous_head>Miscellaneous</miscellaneous_head>
	<extended_recipe_label>Recipes display complete list of ingredients</extended_recipe_label>
	<extended_recipe_note>Instead of just vague "ingredients"</extended_recipe_note>
	<advanced_head>Advanced behaviors</advanced_head>
	<advanced_inbetween_cleaning_label>Pawns will clean rooms in between hauling ingredients and crafting</advanced_inbetween_cleaning_label>
	<advanced_inbetween_cleaning_note>Basic behavior would let them clean only before hauling</advanced_inbetween_cleaning_note>
	<advanced_haul_all_ings_label>Pawns are encouraged to pick up all ingredients before hauling them to the crafting place</advanced_haul_all_ings_label>
	<advanced_haul_all_ings_note>Pawns will take all necessary ingredients to their hauling inventory before delivering them to the crafting place</advanced_haul_all_ings_note>
	<prefer_spoiling_ingredients_label>Pawns are encouraged to use ingredients and materials that are closer to spoiling.</prefer_spoiling_ingredients_label>
	<prefer_spoiling_ingredients_note>WARNING: A large amount of items to choose from may cause lag when this option is enabled.</prefer_spoiling_ingredients_note>
	<UnloadThing>Unload</UnloadThing>
	<UnloadThingCancel>Cancel unload</UnloadThingCancel>
	<manual_unload_label>Enable a button in colonist's inventory to mark items for hauling to stockpile</manual_unload_label>
	<manual_unload_note>If there are no stockpiles to haul to, the colonist will drop the item near him</manual_unload_note>
	<put_back_to_inv_label>Pawns will put items back in their inventory when interrupted</put_back_to_inv_label>
	<put_back_to_inv_note>When pawns are holding an inventory item in their hands, they'll put them back if action was interrupted</put_back_to_inv_note>
	<pick_proper_amount_label>Pawns will stop taking more sweets than they can eat</pick_proper_amount_label>
	<pick_proper_amount_note>No more chocolate lying around</pick_proper_amount_note>
	<Category>Category</Category>
	<fun_police_label>Pawns are encouraged to fulfill secondary needs during joy assignment, or if woken early</fun_police_label>
	<fun_police_note>Pawns will try to top off their joy need only after it goes below 80%, they'll prefer to pick up a spare meal to their inventory, and fulfill all their hygiene needs (if dubs mod is present)</fun_police_note>
	<numbers_head>Tweakable numbers (0 = Unlimited)</numbers_head>
	<op_clean_number_label>Filth limit for pre-task cleaning</op_clean_number_label>
	<adv_clean_number_label>Filth limit for pre-bill cleaning</adv_clean_number_label>
	<doc_clean_number_label>Filth limit for post-tending cleaning</doc_clean_number_label>
	<skip_snow_clean_label>Pawns are discouraged from clearing snow from areas when it's snowing or raining</skip_snow_clean_label>
	<skip_snow_clean_note>When raining just in case if it's a tricky weather</skip_snow_clean_note>
	<prefer_spoiling_meals_label>Pawns are encouraged to eat meals that are closer to spoiling</prefer_spoiling_meals_label>
	<prefer_spoiling_meals_note>WARNING: A large amount of items to choose from may cause lag when this option is enabled.</prefer_spoiling_meals_note>
	<allow_feeding_with_plants_label>Allow and encourage pawns to feed animals with hay.</allow_feeding_with_plants_label>
	<allow_feeding_with_plants_note> Animals will also be encouraged to prefer non-human food.</allow_feeding_with_plants_note>
	<give_sick_joy_drugs_label>Pawns are encouraged to give allowed social drugs or joy-giving food to sick pawns</give_sick_joy_drugs_label>
	<give_sick_joy_drugs_note>Why talk if you can give them a chocolate bar?</give_sick_joy_drugs_note>
	<social_relax_economy_label>Change how pawns use drugs when relaxing socially to prevent them from "wasting joy"</social_relax_economy_label>
	<social_relax_economy_note>Normally pawns sit down for a hour or two before actually consuming the drug, wasting the effect</social_relax_economy_note>
	<advanced_cleaning_ingest_label>Pawns are encouraged to clean before eating at a table or relaxing socially</advanced_cleaning_ingest_label>
	<advanced_cleaning_ingest_note>Pawns will clean around the table where they're planning to sit</advanced_cleaning_ingest_note>
	<mood_regen_label>Pawn's mood slowly moves towards 50% while they're asleep if possible</mood_regen_label>
	<mood_regen_note>Just let pawns "sleep on it" and they should be fine</mood_regen_note>
	<safe_wander_label>Pawns are encouraged to avoid bad weather when wandering aimlessly</safe_wander_label>
	<safe_wander_note>Just stop walking out into the toxic fallout, you idiots</safe_wander_note>
	<pathing_head>Pathing</pathing_head>
	<polite_wander_label>Any friendly pawns are encouraged to avoid wandering into bedrooms, prison cells and prison barracks</polite_wander_label>
	<polite_wander_note>This is just indecent or even dangerous, isn't it?</polite_wander_note>
	<ingest_any_drugs_label>Allow to take any drugs from inventory</ingest_any_drugs_label>
	<ingest_any_drugs_note>If it's ingestible, it should be possible to eat it without dropping on the ground</ingest_any_drugs_note>
	<DoCleanCompToggleLabel>Clean around this bench</DoCleanCompToggleLabel>
	<DoCleanCompToggleDescActive>Pawns will clean around this bench</DoCleanCompToggleDescActive>
	<DoCleanCompToggleDescInactive>Pawns will NOT clean around this bench</DoCleanCompToggleDescInactive>
	<advanced_inbetween_cleaning_gizmo_label>Show a toggle to be able switch which benches need cleaning</advanced_inbetween_cleaning_gizmo_label>
	<advanced_inbetween_cleaning_gizmo_note>It will be possible to disable cleaning around some benches</advanced_inbetween_cleaning_gizmo_note>
	<meditation_economy_label>Pawns will meditate only as much as they need</meditation_economy_label>
	<meditation_economy_note>Unless under meditation assignment, pawns will stop meditating if their psyfocus is full and they don't see meditation as a good source of joy (i. e. full or bored of it)</meditation_economy_note>
	<advanced_respect_capacity_label>-- pawns will not exceed inventory capacity</advanced_respect_capacity_label>
	<advanced_respect_capacity_note>For immersion reasons or whatever</advanced_respect_capacity_note>
</LanguageData>
