<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<LanguageData>

<!-- main tab gui -->
	<Kopp_CYM_PasteRowInList>This will replace every entry in the list with the one you copied. Are you sure you want to do that?</Kopp_CYM_PasteRowInList>
	<Kopp_CYM_DefaultSettingsOneTab>Only this page</Kopp_CYM_DefaultSettingsOneTab>
	<Kopp_CYM_DefaultSettingsAllTabs>All pages</Kopp_CYM_DefaultSettingsAllTabs>
	<Kopp_CYM_ConfirmationOneTab>Are you sure you want to set the settings of this page back to default?</Kopp_CYM_ConfirmationOneTab>
	<Kopp_CYM_ConfirmationAllTabs>Are you sure you want to set the settings of all pages back to default?\nIf new hediffs are found, they will be added, old ones will be removed.</Kopp_CYM_ConfirmationAllTabs>

	<Kopp_CYM_RowEasyLabel>Easy</Kopp_CYM_RowEasyLabel>
	<Kopp_CYM_RowEasyTooltip>If the immunity is ahead of the severity level by at least the value you specify, this type of medicine is chosen.</Kopp_CYM_RowEasyTooltip>

	<Kopp_CYM_RowStandardLabel>Standard</Kopp_CYM_RowStandardLabel>
	<Kopp_CYM_RowStandardTooltip>First, it is checked whether the medicine for 'immunity &lt;' should be used.\nThen, it is checked whether the medicine for 'problematic' should be used.\nThen whether the one for 'easy' should be used.\nIf none fits, this medicine is used.</Kopp_CYM_RowStandardTooltip>

	<Kopp_CYM_RowProblematicLabel>Problematic</Kopp_CYM_RowProblematicLabel>
	<Kopp_CYM_RowProblematicTooltip>If immunity is ahead of severity by the amount you specify or less, this type of medicine is chosen.</Kopp_CYM_RowProblematicTooltip>

	<Kopp_CYM_RowImmunityLabel>Immunity &lt;</Kopp_CYM_RowImmunityLabel>
	<Kopp_CYM_RowImmunityTooltip>If the immunity is lower than the set value, this medicine is used. Without this option every new hediff (with immunity/severity) gets probably tended with the medicine for problematic.</Kopp_CYM_RowImmunityTooltip>

	<Kopp_CYM_Copy>Copy</Kopp_CYM_Copy>
	<Kopp_CYM_Paste>Paste</Kopp_CYM_Paste>

	<Kopp_CYM_CopyWholePage>Copy whole page</Kopp_CYM_CopyWholePage>
	<Kopp_CYM_PasteIntoThisPage>Paste into this page</Kopp_CYM_PasteIntoThisPage>
	<Kopp_CYM_DefaultSettings>Default settings</Kopp_CYM_DefaultSettings>
	<Kopp_CYM_UpdateList>Update hediff list</Kopp_CYM_UpdateList>
	<Kopp_CYM_UpdateListFeedback>Removed {0} hediffs. Added {1} hediffs.</Kopp_CYM_UpdateListFeedback>

	<Kopp_CYM_ListNameColonist>Colonists</Kopp_CYM_ListNameColonist>
	<Kopp_CYM_ListNameImprisonedColonist>Imprisoned colonists</Kopp_CYM_ListNameImprisonedColonist>
	<Kopp_CYM_ListNameEnslavedColonist>Enslaved colonists</Kopp_CYM_ListNameEnslavedColonist>
	<Kopp_CYM_ListNameColonyAnimal>Colony animals</Kopp_CYM_ListNameColonyAnimal>
	<Kopp_CYM_ListNameNeutralAnimal>Neutral animals</Kopp_CYM_ListNameNeutralAnimal>
	<Kopp_CYM_ListNameNeutralFaction>Neutral factions</Kopp_CYM_ListNameNeutralFaction>
	<Kopp_CYM_ListNameHostileFaction>Hostile factions</Kopp_CYM_ListNameHostileFaction>

	<Kopp_CYM_ShowHelper>Help</Kopp_CYM_ShowHelper>

	<Kopp_CYM_ShowHidden>Hide/Unveil</Kopp_CYM_ShowHidden>
	<Kopp_CYM_Hide>Hide</Kopp_CYM_Hide>
	<Kopp_CYM_Unveil>Unveil</Kopp_CYM_Unveil>

	<Kopp_CYM_Operations>Operations</Kopp_CYM_Operations>


<!-- main tab gui helper -->
	<Kopp_CYM_HelperWhichMedicine1>1: The way how the mod decides which medicine to use to tend a hediff is quite simple:\nFirst, the mod checks if a medicine has been manually assigned to a pawns instance of a hediff. This can be done in the pawns health tab by clicking on the lowly visible button which is added for every tendable hediff. This will ignore the pawns settings. If no medicine is manually assigned, the settings in this gui come into play and we jump to (2).\nNote that if the gui settings select a better medicine than what the pawn allows, the best medicine the pawn allows is used.</Kopp_CYM_HelperWhichMedicine1>
	<Kopp_CYM_HelperWhichMedicine2>2: If the immunity is lower than the set value, this medicine is used. This should be useful for the first tend(s) where we are not sure how things will turn out.\n\nExample: Immunity is at 15%, the slider is set to 20%. So the immunity is lower than the set value, the statement is true and this medicine is used. If the slider is set to 10%, the statement is false and we jump to (3).</Kopp_CYM_HelperWhichMedicine2>
	<Kopp_CYM_HelperWhichMedicine3>3: If the immunity exceeds severity by less than the specified value (or not at all), this kind of medicine gets used.\n\nExample: Immunity is at 50%, severity is at 46%. So the immunity is 4% ahead of the severity. If the slider is set to 5%, the statement is true and this medicine gets used. If the slider is set to 3%, the statement is false and we jump to (4).</Kopp_CYM_HelperWhichMedicine3>
	<Kopp_CYM_HelperWhichMedicine4>4: If the immunity is ahead of the severity by at least the set value, this kind of medicine gets used.\n\nExample: Immunity is at 40%, severity is at 15%. So the immunity is 25% ahead of the severity. If the slider is set to 10%, the statement is true and this medicine gets used. If the slider is set to 30%, the statement is false and we jump to (5).</Kopp_CYM_HelperWhichMedicine4>
	<Kopp_CYM_HelperWhichMedicine5>5: If none of the previous statements were true, this medicine gets used.\n\nSome hediffs only have this option though: The ones that do not have a comp immunizable.</Kopp_CYM_HelperWhichMedicine5>
	<Kopp_CYM_HelperCopyPaste>You can copy a page, a column or a entry. Each of them can be pasted into another. E.g. you can copy a column and paste it into a row. Note that copying does not actually copy the content, but only saves which page/column/entry to copy. So if you copy, change and then paste something, the changes will also be pasted.</Kopp_CYM_HelperCopyPaste>
	<Kopp_CYM_HelperLeftButtons>If you click 'default settings' a dropdown menu will appear where you can select 'this page' or 'all pages'.\n\nThe 'update hediff list' is needed if you have added or removed mods that included tendable hediffs.\n\nThe operations button opens a new gui where you can specify the medicine for operations and one or two other options.</Kopp_CYM_HelperLeftButtons>
	<Kopp_CYM_HelperLabels>Some hediffs have the same label. If you hover over the label, you can see the defName. As it is impossible to know which hediff can affect which kind of pawn, each list contains every tendable hediff.\nYou can hide entries from the list by clicking on its label, then 'hide'. In this way, a list can be freed from unnecessary entries.</Kopp_CYM_HelperLabels>


<!-- pawns health tab -->
	<Kopp_CYM_TendOneTime>One tending</Kopp_CYM_TendOneTime>
	<Kopp_CYM_TendUntilHediffGone>Until hediff is gone</Kopp_CYM_TendUntilHediffGone>
	<Kopp_CYM_Clear>Clear</Kopp_CYM_Clear>


<!-- dialog operations -->
	<Kopp_CYM_OperationsHeadline>Settings for operations on </Kopp_CYM_OperationsHeadline>
	<Kopp_CYM_OperationsMaxCare>The maximum medical care for operations: </Kopp_CYM_OperationsMaxCare>
	<Kopp_CYM_OperationsWorseMed>Try to take the worst medicine, which promises maximum success.</Kopp_CYM_OperationsWorseMed>
	<Kopp_CYM_OperationsWorseMedTooltip>The surgery success chance depends on a few factors and is limited to 98%. This option ensures that the best allowed medicine is taken only if it is necessary, otherwise weaker if the 98% can be reached with it.</Kopp_CYM_OperationsWorseMedTooltip>
	<Kopp_CYM_OperationsOnlyWhenBestSuccess>Operate only when maximum success is expected.</Kopp_CYM_OperationsOnlyWhenBestSuccess>
	<Kopp_CYM_OperationsOnlyWhenBestSuccessTooltip>This option causes surgeries to only be started if the expected surgery success chance reaches the upper limit of 98%.</Kopp_CYM_OperationsOnlyWhenBestSuccessTooltip>


	</LanguageData>
