<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>Achtung!</name>
	<author>Andreas Pardeike</author>
	<supportedVersions>
		<li>1.0</li>
		<li>1.1</li>
	</supportedVersions>
	<modDependencies>
		<li>
			<packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
			<displayName>Harmony</displayName>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
			<downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
		</li>
	</modDependencies>
	<packageId>brrainz.achtung</packageId>
	<description>Command your colonists like a boss!

The Achtung! mod enhances how you control RimWorld. You will get more control on how to position your colonists and how they take job orders.

In a nutshell you can:

- position your drafted colonists along a line
- move them in formation
- give orders to multiple colonists at once
- force jobs so they get uninterrupted attention
- haul and repair outside allowed areas


EXAMPLES

(*) Save time by issuing a command with more than one colonist selected. For example: select three brawlers and right click an enemy, then choose "melee". Done.

(*) In combat, position colonists equally spaced in door openings. Select multiple drafted colonists and with the right mouse button drag a line. Achtung! will move your colonists to equally spaced positions in real time. 10 colonists into 10 doors? No problem!

(*) Fall back a few steps with a group of colonists? Easy. Select them and hold the configured key to move them relative to their current formation. You can even rotate the formation with the standard rotation keys.

(*) Make sure that wall and the sandbags are build before the raid arrives. No cloudwatching or eating allowed! Use the [Force] button that Achtung! adds to all "Prioritize..." menus and you can be sure that all assigned work will be done.

(*) Want one colonist harvest and another sow these three fields? Force them to their tasks and queue up non-adjacted fields by simply adding forced work on them (like ordinary jobs but without the shift key).

(*) Treat all injured colonists in their beds? Select a doctor, choose "Prioritize tending... [Force]" and increase the search range so nearby patients will be included (you will see a small "!" on all forced job). Then focus on other important stuff because you can be sure it's done.

The original three Achtung! commands "Clean Room", "Fight Fire" or "Sow Zone/Room" still exist because they do stuff a bit smarter than the build in prioritized work commands.


SETTINGS

Achtung uses the default way to access mod settings. There, you find switches to turn certain features on/off and you can change the default keys to your liking.


ADDING AND REMOVING:

Achtung can be added to any existing game. It usually does not modify save state for saved games to avoid a dependency on it. However, a side effect of the provided custom jobs is that when save the game and your colonists are actively running an Achtung job this will be saved too thus creating a dependency to Achtung. Workaround: open the saved game with Achtung, cancel all Achtung jobs and save it again. This will "clean" the save and remove the dependency.


FEEDBACK

Please send me feedback and rate and recommend my mod whenever possible. The three main places to do so are

Ludeon Forums: https://ludeon.com/forums/index.php?topic=22130.0

Steam Workshop:
http://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/comments/730936602

GitHub:
https://github.com/pardeike/RimWorld-Achtung-Mod/releases


LICENSE

Free. As in free beer. Copy, learn and be respectful.
Powered by Harmony Patch Library


CONTACT

Andreas Pardeike
Email: andreas@pardeike.net
Steam: pardeike
Twitter: @pardeike</description>
</ModMetaData>