<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Defs>
  <ConceptDef>
      <defName>PrisonLabor_Indroduction</defName>
      <label>Prison labor</label>
      <priority>45</priority>
      <needsOpportunity>True</needsOpportunity>
      <highlightTags>
        <li>ITab-Prisoner-Closed</li>
      </highlightTags>
      <helpText>You can force your prisoners to labor.\n\nTo do so you must select "Force to work" option from "Prisoner" pane\n\nPrisoners will work on orders and bills that are in allowed area. Make sure prisoners can reach their work.\n\nThey can only cook, mine, cut plants, haul, clean, or grow plants, that not require special skills.\n\nPrisoner sometimes refuses to work. Reasons can be different. He can be injured, hungry, tired, or not motivated enough.\n\nHINT: You can assign work types in "Work" pane.\n\nHINT: If you put a stove in a prison cell make sure they can reach raw food.\n\nHINT: You can let prioners moving through doors by leaving them open.</helpText>
    </ConceptDef>
    <ConceptDef>
      <defName>PrisonLabor_Motivation</defName>
      <label>Motivating prisoners</label>
      <priority>100</priority>
      <needsOpportunity>True</needsOpportunity>
      <helpText>One of yours prisoners stopped working.\nHe won't work any longer, unless he gets motivated.\n\nYou can check status of motivation in "Needs" tab.\n\nMake sure you have enough wardens (check "Work" tab), or draft one of your colonist and order him to stand around your prisoners.\n\nLow motivation of prisoners can lead to revolts.</helpText>
    </ConceptDef>
    <ConceptDef>
      <defName>PrisonLabor_Growing</defName>
      <label>Growing by prisoners</label>
      <priority>100</priority>
      <needsOpportunity>True</needsOpportunity>
      <helpText>Prisoners can only grow plants that don't require any special skills like potato or cotton. They can however gather any plant that is ordered to harvest.</helpText>
    </ConceptDef>
    <ConceptDef>
      <defName>PrisonLabor_Management</defName>
      <label>Prison labor management</label>
      <priority>100</priority>
      <needsOpportunity>True</needsOpportunity>
      <helpText>You can manage your prison labor in several ways.\n\nYou can assign work types to prisoners by accessing "Work" tab.\n\nYou can restrict when prisoners should work, rest, or sleep by accessing "Restrict" tab.\n\nYou can restrict work to "Prisoners only". For work orders that covers area you can choose "Labor area" tool from "Architect"->"Orders" panel.\nFor bills there is an option "Prisoners only".</helpText>
    </ConceptDef>
    <ConceptDef>
      <defName>PrisonLabor_Timetable</defName>
      <label>Prisoners time restrictions</label>
      <priority>100</priority>
      <needsOpportunity>True</needsOpportunity>
      <helpText>You can make time restrictions for prisoners.\n\n"Work" time will force them to work even when they're hungry or tired.\n\n"Joy" time will let them rest from job and get motivation bonus.\n\n"Sleep" time will force them to stay in prison cell.\n\n"Anything" is default setting.</helpText>
    </ConceptDef>
</Defs>
