<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Defs>
	<!-- <HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>Hospitality_1_0_17</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>1.0.17</assemblyVersion>
		<content>- New: Added setting for minimum group size|- New: Traveling guests will never have mental breaks|- New: Guest tab shows the amount of guests and beds|- Fix: Guests now only get entertained when they're inside of the guest area|- Fix: Returning visitors get their needs reset|img:images/Skirmish|caption:As you may know, I'm working hard on my own game. We've just updated the free version and I need YOUR opinion! Click the link above to check it out. Thanks!</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef> -->

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
		<modNameReadable>Hospitality</modNameReadable>
		<modIdentifier>Hospitality</modIdentifier>
		<linkUrl>https://www.patreon.com/orionmods</linkUrl>
		<!-- <linkUrl>https://extra-nice.net/help-with-skirmish/</linkUrl> -->
		<defName>Hospitality_1_3_0</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>1.3.0.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>
		 - New: Guests now eventually optimize their apparel, so they will wear what you gift them if appropriate
		|- New: Added debug action to remove broken groups (so you don't have to edit your savegame)
		|- New: Alert when guests have nothing to eat
		|- Fix: Guests walking outside of their area if not absolutely necessary
		|- Fix: Guests won't hang around in bed all day anymore
		|- Fix: Art is now properly preserved when creating guest beds
		|- Tweak: Improved code for guests restocking their food
		|- Tweak: Guests now use vanilla gifting system, but with Hospitality score for chance
		|- Many more fixes and tweaks (see change notes)
		|img:images/Patron
		|caption:Keeping Hospitality up to date takes a lot of time. To sustain my mod development, I'm running a Patreon page that I need your help with. You can also join my community for direct support, questions, and friendly chit-chat. So if you feel curious, grateful, or generous, please take a look by clicking the link above!
		|If this mod update causes issues, don't hesitate to contact me (and remember to include the Ctrl-F12 error log!).</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<!--HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>ModName_1_2_0</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>1.2.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>First paragraph.|img:Things/Item/Meal/Fine,Things/Item/Meal/Lavish,Things/Item/Meal/Simple|caption:This is a caption.|Another paragraph with &lt;b&gt;rich text&lt;/b&gt;.</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef-->
</Defs>