<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <!-- BigCats -->

  <Cougar.label>Cougar</Cougar.label>
<Corpse_Cougar.label>Cougar</Corpse_Cougar.label>

  <Cougar.description>One of the most dangerous big cats, cougars are solitary hunters with long, sharp teeth and 발톱. They stalk prey from hidden positions before pouncing.\n\nWhile humans are not their normal diet, they won't turn down a 식사 of vulnerable human 고기.</Cougar.description>

  <Panther.label>Panther</Panther.label>
<Corpse_Panther.label>Panther</Corpse_Panther.label>

  <Panther.description>An agile and powerful big cat native to the jungles of old Earth. As solitary am덤불 predators, panthers are masters of taking down both large and small prey. Onlookers tend to focus on their graceful movements, while those in closer contact usually notice their skull-crushing strength.</Panther.description>

  <Lynx.label>Lynx</Lynx.label>
<Corpse_Lynx.label>Lynx</Corpse_Lynx.label>

  <Lynx.description>A wildcat larger than a housecat, but smaller than a cougar. Lynxes survive on a diet of small birds and animals. Their very warm fur keeps them safe from the brutally cold temperatures of their northern territories.</Lynx.description>

  <Tiger.label>호랑이</Tiger.label>
<Corpse_Tiger.label>호랑이</Corpse_Tiger.label>

  <Tiger.description>The 호랑이 is the largest cat species, most recognisable for their pattern of dark vertical stripes on reddish-orange fur with a lighter underside. 호랑이s are apex predators, primarily preying on ungulates such as deer and bovids. They are territorial and generally solitary but social animals, often requiring large contiguous areas of habitat that support their prey requirements.</Tiger.description>

  <WhiteTiger.label>백호</WhiteTiger.label>
<WhiteCorpse_Tiger.label>백호</WhiteCorpse_Tiger.label>

  <WhiteTiger.description>The 백호 is a pigmentation variant of the 호랑이. The 백호s are distinctive due to the color of their fur. The white fur caused by a lack of the pigment pheomelanin, which is found in 호랑이s with orange color fur.</WhiteTiger.description>

  <SnowLeopard.label>눈표범</SnowLeopard.label>
<Corpse_SnowLeopard.label>눈표범</Corpse_SnowLeopard.label>

  <SnowLeopard.description>An agile and powerful big cat native to the cold biomes. As solitary am덤불 predators, 눈표범s are masters of taking down both large and small prey. Onlookers tend to focus on their graceful movements, while those in closer contact usually notice their skull-crushing strength.</SnowLeopard.description>

  <Jaguar.label>재규어</Jaguar.label>
<Corpse_Jaguar.label>재규어</Corpse_Jaguar.label>

  <Jaguar.description>The 재규어 is the third-largest feline after the 호랑이 and the lion.</Jaguar.description>


</LanguageData>