<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>Facial Stuff 1.1</name>
	<author>Killface</author>
	<url/>
	<supportedVersions>
		<li>1.1</li>
	</supportedVersions>
	<packageId>killface.facialstuff</packageId>
	<loadAfter>
		<li>rimofmadness.vampires</li>
		<li>brrainz.harmony</li>
		<li>erdelf.HumanoidAlienRaces</li>
		<li>skyarkhangel.HSK</li>
	</loadAfter>
	<loadBefore>
		<li>EdB.PrepareCarefully</li>
	</loadBefore>
	<modDependencies>
		<li>
			<packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
			<displayName>Harmony</displayName>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
			<downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
		</li>
		<li>
			<packageId>erdelf.HumanoidAlienRaces</packageId>
			<displayName>Humanoid Alien Races 2.0</displayName>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=839005762</steamWorkshopUrl>
		</li>
	</modDependencies>
	<description>This mod aims to provide more visual individuality for your colonists
- hands and feet, animated (also for animals, unfinished)
- smooth weapon animations and changed offsets
- 30+ different beards for males, some of them combinable
- edited vanilla hair styles with 10 steps of hair loss
- new eyes and brows for both sexes
- animated eye &amp; mouth textures
- alternate eye and jaw textures for pawns with implants or removed parts
- 10 newly defined skin colors instead of the vanilla 6
- hair genetics according to real life (including the effects of eumelanin &amp; pheomelanin)
- includes selected trending hair colors of 5501
- possibility to show hair under hats (hair cut textures can be cached on disk, deactivated by default)
- multiple visibility options for head gear on map
- multiple visibility options for apparel layers in rooms/private rooms
- adds the ability to change the head and body type for all Humans (needs activation in the mod options)
- fully compatible with Children &amp; Pregnancy, Vampires, Werewolves and Prepare Carefully
- all features can be disabled in the mod options menu

For modders:
- Walk cycle editor. Check out the develop mode in the mod options
- A tab for positioning the hands on weapons, also activated with the dev mode; can export directly to xml.

+ hair textures with beards from the &apos;Spoonshortage&apos;s Rimworld Hairstyles 1.2&apos; and &apos;Nackblad Inc Rimhair 1.1&apos; mods are replaced by shaved versions
  This mod contains no hair packs itself any more. Please subscribe to the hair mods of your liking.

Patches the PawnRenderer via Harmony and returns &apos;false&apos; thus being incompatible to mods doing the same.
    Look out for the FS "Alien Faces" addon if you're using erdelf's Humanoid Alien Framework.

    Unfortunately no hands on lightsabers, as the OversizedWeapons prefixes the required method.

    Thanks and Credits:
    Korean translation by LazyRichard
    Portuguese Brazilian translation by PredatorianBR
    Spanish translation by 53N4
    ----------------------------
    Initial Face Editor code adapted from "Clutter" by mrofa (available at the Ludeon forums)
    Hands based on "Clutter Weapon Hands" by mrofa.
    Body, gender and head changer code adapted from Change Dresser by Kiame Vivacity
    Prepare Carefully saving / loading code adapted from Psychology by {WOBBLY} The Word-Mule
    Inspiration for the new renderer and all of its benefits by {WOBBLY} The Word-Mule and ChJees
    ----------------------------
    Special thanks to DoctorVanGogh and erdelf for help with transpilers, NotFood for the new Dresser patch
    and Brrainz for Harmony and help with transpilers
	</description>
</ModMetaData>