<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>DontBlockDoorMod</name>
  <author>tikubonn</author>
  <packageId>tikubonn.dontblockdoor</packageId>
  <url>https://twitter.com/tikubonn</url>
  <description><![CDATA[<size=17><color=#75bbfd>What is Dont Block Door?</color></size>

this MOD fixes a pandemic that has plagued many a world on the Rim: doors being wedged open. whether it's prisoners escaping, invaders rushing in, or temperature leaking out, unwanted open doors have led to disasters in many colonies. my MOD prevents items from being dropped on the same tile as a door, allowing it to close just as intended. after installing this MOD, please avoid placing stockpiles on the same tile as a door.

<size=17><color=#75bbfd>What is Dont Block Door?</color></size>

これは RimWorldのシステムを少し改変し、ドアの上にアイテムを置けなくするようにするMODです(´・ω・`)昨晩、襲撃者に資材が詰まって開けっぱなしだった扉から侵入され、お家が全焼しまい悲しくなったのでこのMODをつくりました(´・ω・`)導入すると、何人たりともドアの上にアイテムが置けなくなります(´・ω・`)溢れてしまった資材のせいで、ドア開けっぱなしなんてことはなくなると思います(´・ω・`)やるじゃん

<size=17><color=#75bbfd>Copyright</color></size>

(c) 2018-2021 tikubonn

This MOD include Harmony.dll that released under the MIT License.

<size=17><color=#75bbfd>Update History</color></size>

2018/3/24: 
since this update, this MOD move the item to another place when built door upon it.
アイテムの上に扉が建設された際に、そのアイテムを扉の外に再配置するよう改良しました。

2018/3/24: 
since this update, anybody won't haul item to stockpile area's cell that overlapped by door. anybody won't haul the product to floor that is overlapped the door. and I fixed small bug.
備蓄ゾーンの上に扉が配置されている場合に、扉の上にアイテムを運搬しないように改良しました。また、製作作業の成果物を扉の上に運搬してしまわないように改良しました。生き物の解体とストーンカッターで正常に動作していることを確認したので、他の精密加工台などでも同様の振る舞いをすると思います。それと扉をアイテムの上に建設した際にアイテムが壁にめり込んでしまうしょうもないバグを修正しました。

2019/8/6:
finished support.
サポートを終了しました。

2020/2/18:
this MOD has supported for RimWorld 1.1 unstable experimentally.
試験的にRimWorld 1.1テスト版に対応しました。

2020/2/25:
changed Harmony version 1.x to 2.x, so rewrote source code too much. this MOD has supported multiple version 1.0 and 1.1. but I finished update this MOD for RimWorld 1.0.
Harmony を最新版の 2.0 に更新し、それに伴い多くのコードを修正しました。この MOD はこのバージョン以降 RimWorld 1.0 と 1.1 双方のバージョンで使用できるようになりました。ただしこれ以降 RimWorld 1.0 用の更新は終了します。ご留意ください。

2020/3/1:
updated Harmony 2.0.0.6 to 2.0.0.8.
Harmony のバージョンを 2.0.0.6 から 2.0.0.8 に更新しました。

2020/3/3:
since this version, if you use this MOD in RimWorld 1.1, this MOD has required Harmony (https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=2009463077).
RimWorld 1.1 でこの MOD を使用する場合、この MOD は前提 MOD として Harmony (https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=2009463077) を要求するようになりました。

2020/7/30:
this MOD has supported for RimWorld 1.2 experimentally, so I finished support old versions(1.0 ~ 1.1).
RimWorld 1.2 に試験的に対応しました。それに伴い過去バージョン(1.0 ~ 1.1)への対応を終了しました。

2020/8/1:
I refactored all versions source code for continuation updating. fixed a bug in a processing when load a save data.
更新を継続しやすくするために、すべてのバージョンのソースコードを整理しました。セーブデータ読み込み時に発生する不具合を修正しました。

2020/9/13:
Fixed some source codes for fix bug. Maybe ok, but it could be not perfect work, because information is a little.
何かしらの条件でマップ外の座標のアイテムを読み込もうとし、エラーが発生してしまう不具合を、暫定的に修正しました。多分大丈夫だとは思いますが、寄せられた情報が少なかったため、完璧な修正ができたかはわかりません。

2021/7/9:
this MOD has supported for RimWorld 1.3 unstable experimentally.
試験的にRimWorld 1.3テスト版に対応しました。
]]></description>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.3</li>
  </supportedVersions>
	<modDependencies>
		<li>
			<packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
			<displayName>Harmony</displayName>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
			<downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
		</li>
	</modDependencies>
	<loadBefore></loadBefore>
	<loadAfter>
		<li>brrainz.harmony</li>	
</loadAfter>
	<incompatibleWith></incompatibleWith>
</ModMetaData>
