<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>[JPT] Open The Windows</name>
	<author>jptrrs</author>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.0</li>
  </supportedVersions>
	<description>
Introducing a revolutionary device to light, ventilate and defend your base: the WINDOW! Your base designs are never going to be same.

Let NATURAL LIGHT in! Once your pawns realize they've been cut off from nature's light cycles, they're going to crave it! The outdoors need levels are going to decay 3x faster* if they are stuck indoors without windows. You are going to need them all over the place! But you better plan well. Be prepared to set aside some land, because the windows can only pump light in if they have acess to wide open areas. So say goodbye to the infinite hallways of rooms glued to one another in unhealty bunkers and welcome to the real-world architecture needs! Also, if you are playing with "Dub's Skylights", all light coming from your skylights count as natural light.

Circulate AIR! Your windows can act as vents. But you will need to research glass-making before you can build windows that can filter air or light independently. More advanced windows can ventilate even with their shutters closed, even if at a lower rate. If you're playing with "Glass+Lights", all research and production chains will be integrated (and it's windows are replaced for these ones).

SHOOT through the windows! Who needs embrasures when you can use a window that opens and closes? That's right: your pawns can shoot while ducking behind a window, with a cover value equivalent to sandbags. When the enemies get too close, the window can be closed and it will become equivalent to a wall. Let them come! Of course, they might decide to charge the windows themselves, and they are weaker than a regular wall. You might find yourself with a breach on your hands! But don't worry, there's a fortified window you can install on more sensitive locations. They just won't come cheap!

Enjoy BEAUTIFUL landscapes! If you're playing with "Nature is Beautiful" (or it's rebalanced version), the windows will calculate their own beauty stat by summing up all the beauty on their outside field of view. This means your rooms will actually benefit from having a garden next door! For balancing reasons, we've inculded a "beauty sensitivity reduction" factor*.

Have fun! And if you like this mod, please rate it on Steam and/or buy me a coffee!

*These adjustments are customizable on the mod's options panel, so you can totally have it your way!
  </description>
	<url>https://steamcommunity.com/id/jptrrs/myworkshopfiles/?appid=294100</url>
</ModMetaData>