<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <!-- A-1 PHALANX -->

  <Gun_Phalanx.label>A-1 Phalanx</Gun_Phalanx.label>
  <Gun_Phalanx.description>A close-in weapon to be used with no loss of stopping power in comparison with a soldier's assault 소총. The Phalanx enjoys a ballistics advantage over most heavy pistols. Civilian variants are often purchased by colonists on planets that have particularly dangerous big-game animals.</Gun_Phalanx.description>


  <!-- A-1BW BLACK WIDOW -->

  <Gun_BlackWidow.label>A-1BW Black Widow</Gun_BlackWidow.label>
  <Gun_BlackWidow.description>Accurate and deadly blaster. Effective against armor, shields, and biotic barriers.</Gun_BlackWidow.description>


  <!-- A-6 CERBERUS HARRIER -->

  <Gun_Harrier.label>A-6 Cerberus Harrier</Gun_Harrier.label>
  <Gun_Harrier.description>These Cerberus blaster are fully automatic. Cerberus gunsmiths reined in the recoil issues, resulting in a gun that stays on target but delivers slightly less punch per round than a standard Mattock. As such, the weapon is typically utilized by Cerberus’s elite troopers who train constantly to craft every burst count.</Gun_Harrier.description>


  <!-- A-2S PREDATOR -->

  <Gun_Predator.label>A-2S Predator</Gun_Predator.label>
  <Gun_Predator.description>Very rare blaster 샷건. Deals high damage at short range; less effective at long range. Effective against armor, shields and biotic barriers. It is of human design but is only used by krogan, due to the fact that the kickback from a single shot has enough force to break a human's arm. Protected by Fabrication Rights Management (FRM) technology, this weapon is nearly impossible to reproduce and is prohibitively expensive.</Gun_Predator.description>


  <!-- A-3S HURRICANE -->

  <Gun_Hurricane.label>A-3S Hurricane</Gun_Hurricane.label>
  <Gun_Hurricane.description>Very rare blaster 샷건. Deals high damage at short range; less effective at long range. Effective against armor, shields and biotic barriers. It is of human design but is only used by krogan, due to the fact that the kickback from a single shot has enough force to break a human's arm. Protected by Fabrication Rights Management (FRM) technology, this weapon is nearly impossible to reproduce and is prohibitively expensive.</Gun_Hurricane.description>


  <!-- A-10 AVENGER -->

  <Gun_AvengerA.label>A-10 Avenger</Gun_AvengerA.label>
  <Gun_AvengerA.description>A common, versatile, military-grade assault blaster. Accurate when fired in short bursts, and deadly when fired on full auto.</Gun_AvengerA.description>


</LanguageData>